<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
<updated>2020-08-26T17:19:53+03:00</updated>
<id>https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml</id>
<title type="html">Adowsom</title>
<subtitle>Duct Tape is like the force. There's a dark side and a light side, and it holds the universe together.</subtitle>
<author>
 <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
 <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
 <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
</author>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Sushant Singh Case : CBI जांच की मंजूरी, सामने आया Shweta Singh Kirti का ये रिएक्शन वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/sushant-singh-case-cbi-shweta-singh-kirti.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sushant Singh Case : CBI जांच की मंजूरी, सामने आया Shweta Singh Kirti का ये रिएक्शन वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:15:09+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:15:09+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/sushant-singh-case-cbi-shweta-singh-kirti</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/sushant-singh-case-cbi-shweta-singh-kirti.html">&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court has handed over the investigation of Sushant Singh Rajput case to the CBI. As soon as this news is received, there is a wave of happiness from Sushant’s family to the fans. People are giving their reactions on social media. Meanwhile, Sushant’s sister Shweta Singh Kirti also expressed happiness by tweeting. He thanked the fans of Ishwar and Sushant. He has written that this is the first step towards truth    &lt;br /&gt;सुशांत सिंह राजपूत केस की जांच सुप्रीम कोर्ट ने CBI को सौंप दी है. ये खबर मिलते ही सुशांत के परिवार से लेकर चाहनेवालों तक में खुशी की लहर है. सोशल मीडिया पर लोग अपने रिऐक्शंस दे रहे हैं. इस बीच सुशांत की बहन श्वेता सिंह कीर्ति ने भी ट्वीट करके खुशी जताई. उन्होंने ईश्वर और सुशांत के फैन्स का शुक्रिया अदा किया. उन्होंने लिखा है कि सच की तरफ ये पहला कदम है    &lt;br /&gt;#SushantSinghCase #ShwetaSinghKirti  #oneindiahindi&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The Supreme Court has handed over the investigation of Sushant Singh Rajput case to the CBI. As soon as this news is received, there is a wave of happiness from Sushant’s family to the fans. People are giving their reactions on social media. Meanwhile, Sushant’s sister Shweta Singh Kirti also expressed happiness by tweeting. He thanked the fans of Ishwar and Sushant. He has written that this is the first step towards truth सुशांत सिंह राजपूत केस की जांच सुप्रीम कोर्ट ने CBI को सौंप दी है. ये खबर मिलते ही सुशांत के परिवार से लेकर चाहनेवालों तक में खुशी की लहर है. सोशल मीडिया पर लोग अपने रिऐक्शंस दे रहे हैं. इस बीच सुशांत की बहन श्वेता सिंह कीर्ति ने भी ट्वीट करके खुशी जताई. उन्होंने ईश्वर और सुशांत के फैन्स का शुक्रिया अदा किया. उन्होंने लिखा है कि सच की तरफ ये पहला कदम है #SushantSinghCase #ShwetaSinghKirti #oneindiahindi</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPX0A1VFFFoGnHQy1/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPX0A1VFFFoGnHQy1/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">[Pops in Seoul] The seven charismatic boys! ENOi(이엔오아이)’s Interview for ‘Where Are You’</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/pops-in-seoul-the-seven-charismatic-boys-enoi-s-interview-for-where-ar.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[Pops in Seoul] The seven charismatic boys! ENOi(이엔오아이)’s Interview for ‘Where Are You’" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:12:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:12:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/pops-in-seoul-the-seven-charismatic-boys-enoi-s-interview-for-where-ar</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/pops-in-seoul-the-seven-charismatic-boys-enoi-s-interview-for-where-ar.html">&lt;p&gt;The seven charismatic boys with captivating visuals!  &lt;br /&gt;Radiating diverse charms with their fierce performance!  &lt;br /&gt;ENOi’s song &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; hopes to walk on a flower road with fans  &lt;br /&gt;Interview &amp;amp; Balloon Q&amp;amp;A  &lt;br /&gt;About &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot;  &lt;br /&gt;Things to focus on in &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot;  &lt;br /&gt;About the killing part of &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot;  &lt;br /&gt;Direction of the &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; M/V  &lt;br /&gt;Things to watch for in the  &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; M/V  &lt;br /&gt;Did the M/V express your aim well?  &lt;br /&gt;매혹적인 비주얼을 가진 카리스마 넘치는 일곱 소년들!  &lt;br /&gt;강렬한 퍼포먼스로 다양한 매력이 뿜뿜!  &lt;br /&gt;이엔오아이(ENOi)의 노래 W.A.Y(Where Are You)&quot;은 팬들과 함께 꽃길을 걷고 싶은 바람을 담았습니다  &lt;br /&gt;인터뷰 &amp;amp; 풍선 Q&amp;amp;A  &lt;br /&gt;신곡 &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 에 대해  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 에서 집중해야 할 사항들은?  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 의 킬링 파트애 대해서  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 뮤비의 방향성  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 뮤비에서 주목해야 할 점들은?  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 뮤비에서 목표한 것들을 잘 표현했는가?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">The seven charismatic boys with captivating visuals! Radiating diverse charms with their fierce performance! ENOi’s song &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; hopes to walk on a flower road with fans Interview &amp;amp; Balloon Q&amp;amp;A About &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; Things to focus on in &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; About the killing part of &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; Direction of the &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; M/V Things to watch for in the &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; M/V Did the M/V express your aim well? 매혹적인 비주얼을 가진 카리스마 넘치는 일곱 소년들! 강렬한 퍼포먼스로 다양한 매력이 뿜뿜! 이엔오아이(ENOi)의 노래 W.A.Y(Where Are You)&quot;은 팬들과 함께 꽃길을 걷고 싶은 바람을 담았습니다 인터뷰 &amp;amp; 풍선 Q&amp;amp;A 신곡 &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 에 대해 &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 에서 집중해야 할 사항들은? &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 의 킬링 파트애 대해서 &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 뮤비의 방향성 &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 뮤비에서 주목해야 할 점들은? &quot;W.A.Y (Where Are You)&quot; 뮤비에서 목표한 것들을 잘 표현했는가?</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPEvX1VEcB0b7fSwR/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPEvX1VEcB0b7fSwR/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Jodhpur सभा के बीच में कुत्तों के भौंकने पर पूर्व विधायक ने दिया विवादित बयान वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/jodhpur.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jodhpur सभा के बीच में कुत्तों के भौंकने पर पूर्व विधायक ने दिया विवादित बयान वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:12:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:12:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/jodhpur</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/jodhpur.html">&lt;p&gt;Video of Bhairaram Seoul, former MLA of Osian Assembly of Jodhpur, went viral on social media. In the video, Bhairaram is seen addressing Seoul villagers while addressing, there is a sound of some dogs barking in the middle while some dogs are also seen in the video, former MLA Bhairaram Seoul stops talking with the villagers and says There is no need to worry that this is a Congressman, he has a habit of doing this and continues to do so  &lt;br /&gt;जोधपुर के ओसियां विधानसभा के पूर्व विधायक भैराराम सियोल का वीडियो सोशल मीडिया पर वायरल. वीडियो में भैराराम सियोल ग्रामीण लोगों को संबोधित करते दिख रहे हैं संबोधित करते समय बीच में कुछ कुत्तों के भौंकने की आवाज आती है भोंकते हुए कुछ कुत्ते वीडियो में देख भी रहे हैं पूर्व विधायक भैराराम सियोल अपनी बात ग्रामीणों के साथ करते हुए रुकते हैं और कहते हैं कि यह तो कांग्रेसी है इससे घबराने की जरूरत नहीं है इनकी तो आदत है ऐसा करने की और ऐसा यह करते रहते हैं  &lt;br /&gt;#Rajasthan #Jodhpur #BhairaramSeoul&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Video of Bhairaram Seoul, former MLA of Osian Assembly of Jodhpur, went viral on social media. In the video, Bhairaram is seen addressing Seoul villagers while addressing, there is a sound of some dogs barking in the middle while some dogs are also seen in the video, former MLA Bhairaram Seoul stops talking with the villagers and says There is no need to worry that this is a Congressman, he has a habit of doing this and continues to do so जोधपुर के ओसियां विधानसभा के पूर्व विधायक भैराराम सियोल का वीडियो सोशल मीडिया पर वायरल. वीडियो में भैराराम सियोल ग्रामीण लोगों को संबोधित करते दिख रहे हैं संबोधित करते समय बीच में कुछ कुत्तों के भौंकने की आवाज आती है भोंकते हुए कुछ कुत्ते वीडियो में देख भी रहे हैं पूर्व विधायक भैराराम सियोल अपनी बात ग्रामीणों के साथ करते हुए रुकते हैं और कहते हैं कि यह तो कांग्रेसी है इससे घबराने की जरूरत नहीं है इनकी तो आदत है ऐसा करने की और ऐसा यह करते रहते हैं #Rajasthan #Jodhpur #BhairaramSeoul</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPXVb1VHTrKH1o-P2/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPXVb1VHTrKH1o-P2/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Guy Does Downhill Longboarding on Empty Street at High Speed</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/guy-does-downhill-longboarding-on-empty-street-at-high-speed.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Guy Does Downhill Longboarding on Empty Street at High Speed" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:11:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:11:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/guy-does-downhill-longboarding-on-empty-street-at-high-speed</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/guy-does-downhill-longboarding-on-empty-street-at-high-speed.html">&lt;p&gt;This guy did longboarding on a downhill on an empty street. He attained an extremely dangerous yet high speed while going down the lane. While turning, he used his glove’s to make a balance which even created spark on the ground. At last, he completed the entire trail without losing any balance at all.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">This guy did longboarding on a downhill on an empty street. He attained an extremely dangerous yet high speed while going down the lane. While turning, he used his glove’s to make a balance which even created spark on the ground. At last, he completed the entire trail without losing any balance at all.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPOj31VExU_ffDxUe/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPOj31VExU_ffDxUe/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Cape Town field hospital decommissioned as infection numbers drop in South Africa</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/cape-town-field-hospital-decommissioned-as-infection-numbers-drop-in-s.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cape Town field hospital decommissioned as infection numbers drop in South Africa" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:09:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:09:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/cape-town-field-hospital-decommissioned-as-infection-numbers-drop-in-s</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/cape-town-field-hospital-decommissioned-as-infection-numbers-drop-in-s.html">&lt;p&gt;South Africa has decommissioned the COVID-19 field hospital which was built inside the Cape Town International Convention Centre on August 21, marking   &lt;br /&gt;The 1,000-bed facility was constructed as an overflow to existing hospitals in the province as the COVID-19 infections rose in May.  &lt;br /&gt;The nation’s Premier Allan Winde was joined by the medical staff of the facility as he wheeled the last bed out of the facility signifying its closure.   &lt;br /&gt;Nurses sang as the jubilantly walked through the facility for the last time.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">South Africa has decommissioned the COVID-19 field hospital which was built inside the Cape Town International Convention Centre on August 21, marking The 1,000-bed facility was constructed as an overflow to existing hospitals in the province as the COVID-19 infections rose in May. The nation’s Premier Allan Winde was joined by the medical staff of the facility as he wheeled the last bed out of the facility signifying its closure. Nurses sang as the jubilantly walked through the facility for the last time.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPpn41VG1VNuKdCru/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPpn41VG1VNuKdCru/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Lucas Hernandez chambre le PSG dans les vestiaires du Bayern</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/lucas-hernandez-chambre-le-psg-dans-les-vestiaires-du-bayern.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lucas Hernandez chambre le PSG dans les vestiaires du Bayern" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:08:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:08:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/lucas-hernandez-chambre-le-psg-dans-les-vestiaires-du-bayern</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/lucas-hernandez-chambre-le-psg-dans-les-vestiaires-du-bayern.html">&lt;p&gt;Le Bayern Munich s’est imposé, hier soir (1-0), en finale de la Ligue des Champions face au Paris Saint-Germain. Vainqueurs de leur sixième sacre dans la compétition, les Bavarois ont bien fêté ça à l’image de Lucas Hernandez. Le défenseur français n’a d’ailleurs pas hésité à chambrer le club de la capitale française en célébrant dans le vestiaire avec la musique d’un célèbre rappeur dont le refrain est : «Panam, c’est la Champions League». Pour rappel, le champion du monde 2018 était courtisé par le PSG ces derniers mois alors qu’il n’a pas réussi à s’imposer au Bayern, en raison d’une grosse blessure notamment.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Le Bayern Munich s’est imposé, hier soir (1-0), en finale de la Ligue des Champions face au Paris Saint-Germain. Vainqueurs de leur sixième sacre dans la compétition, les Bavarois ont bien fêté ça à l’image de Lucas Hernandez. Le défenseur français n’a d’ailleurs pas hésité à chambrer le club de la capitale française en célébrant dans le vestiaire avec la musique d’un célèbre rappeur dont le refrain est : «Panam, c’est la Champions League». Pour rappel, le champion du monde 2018 était courtisé par le PSG ces derniers mois alors qu’il n’a pas réussi à s’imposer au Bayern, en raison d’une grosse blessure notamment.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ1FD1VGsEKbVmF9T/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ1FD1VGsEKbVmF9T/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Pulwama Terror Attack: NIA names Masood Azhar and his brother as plotters in the chargesheet</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/pulwama-terror-attack-nia-names-masood-azhar-and-his-brother-as-plotte.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pulwama Terror Attack: NIA names Masood Azhar and his brother as plotters in the chargesheet" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:06:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:06:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/pulwama-terror-attack-nia-names-masood-azhar-and-his-brother-as-plotte</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/pulwama-terror-attack-nia-names-masood-azhar-and-his-brother-as-plotte.html">&lt;p&gt;Pakistan-based terror mastermind Masood Azhar and his brother Rauf Asghar have been named as the key conspirators behind the 2019 Pulwama terror attack in a charge-sheet filed today by the National Investigation Agency. The charge-sheet names 19 accused and details how the planning and execution of the attack in Kashmir was done from Pakistan. According to the NIA Six of the terrorists named by the NIA were eliminated, seven have been arrested and five are still missing of which three are Pakistanis. Over 40 soldiers were killed when a suicide bomber rammed a car full of explosives into a security convoy at Pulwama on February 14 last year.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Pakistan-based terror mastermind Masood Azhar and his brother Rauf Asghar have been named as the key conspirators behind the 2019 Pulwama terror attack in a charge-sheet filed today by the National Investigation Agency. The charge-sheet names 19 accused and details how the planning and execution of the attack in Kashmir was done from Pakistan. According to the NIA Six of the terrorists named by the NIA were eliminated, seven have been arrested and five are still missing of which three are Pakistanis. Over 40 soldiers were killed when a suicide bomber rammed a car full of explosives into a security convoy at Pulwama on February 14 last year.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQDOV1VHOKBTbaNOJ/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQDOV1VHOKBTbaNOJ/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Pour inciter les clients à retourner dans les restaurants, une ville des Yvelines offre des coupons de 20 euros aux habitants pour alléger l’addition - VIDEO</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/pour-inciter-les-clients-retourner-dans-les-restaurants-une-ville-des.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pour inciter les clients à retourner dans les restaurants, une ville des Yvelines offre des coupons de 20 euros aux habitants pour alléger l’addition - VIDEO" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:05:08+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:05:08+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/pour-inciter-les-clients-retourner-dans-les-restaurants-une-ville-des</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/pour-inciter-les-clients-retourner-dans-les-restaurants-une-ville-des.html">&lt;p&gt;Pour inciter les clients à retourner dans les restaurants, une ville des Yvelines offre des coupons de 20 euros aux habitants pour alléger l’addition - VIDEO&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Pour inciter les clients à retourner dans les restaurants, une ville des Yvelines offre des coupons de 20 euros aux habitants pour alléger l’addition - VIDEO</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPYOW1VFJDkR_-ptp/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPYOW1VFJDkR_-ptp/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Gold Hallmark Center: देश में लाखों लोगों को मिलेगा रोज़गार, जानिए कैसे ? वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/gold-hallmark-center.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gold Hallmark Center: देश में लाखों लोगों को मिलेगा रोज़गार, जानिए कैसे ? वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:05:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:05:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/gold-hallmark-center</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/gold-hallmark-center.html">&lt;p&gt;Gold has been considered a good investment till now. But soon gold will now remove unemployment of people. Gold will employ millions of people. Yes, the central government is preparing to open a gold hallmark center in every block of the country soon. With the opening of the center, fake gold sold in villages will be banned. This big decision has been taken by the government. Its complete planning has been done.    &lt;br /&gt;सोना अब तक अच्छी इनवेस्टमेंट माना जाता रहा है। लेकिन जल्द ही सोना अब लोगों की बेरोजगारी को दूर करेगा। सोना लाखों लोगों को रोजगार देगा। जी हां केंद्र सरकार जल्द ही देश के हर ब्लॉक में सोने का हॉलमार्क सेंटर खोलने की तैयारी में है. सेंटर के खुलने से गांवों में बिक रहे फर्जी सोने पर रोक लगेगी. सरकार ने ये बड़ा फैसला लिया गया है।  इसकी पूरी प्लानिंग कर ली गई है।    &lt;br /&gt;#Gold #unemployment #gold hallmark center&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Gold has been considered a good investment till now. But soon gold will now remove unemployment of people. Gold will employ millions of people. Yes, the central government is preparing to open a gold hallmark center in every block of the country soon. With the opening of the center, fake gold sold in villages will be banned. This big decision has been taken by the government. Its complete planning has been done. सोना अब तक अच्छी इनवेस्टमेंट माना जाता रहा है। लेकिन जल्द ही सोना अब लोगों की बेरोजगारी को दूर करेगा। सोना लाखों लोगों को रोजगार देगा। जी हां केंद्र सरकार जल्द ही देश के हर ब्लॉक में सोने का हॉलमार्क सेंटर खोलने की तैयारी में है. सेंटर के खुलने से गांवों में बिक रहे फर्जी सोने पर रोक लगेगी. सरकार ने ये बड़ा फैसला लिया गया है। इसकी पूरी प्लानिंग कर ली गई है। #Gold #unemployment #gold hallmark center</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4nc1VGzEqm9xEgU/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4nc1VGzEqm9xEgU/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Ryan Newman thanks Daytona’s first responders</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/ryan-newman-thanks-daytona-s-first-responders.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ryan Newman thanks Daytona’s first responders" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:03:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:03:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/ryan-newman-thanks-daytona-s-first-responders</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/ryan-newman-thanks-daytona-s-first-responders.html">&lt;p&gt;Ryan Newman couldn’t meet with Daytona International Speedway’s first responders in person, so he showed his gratitude over the radio prerace for attending to him after his Daytona 500 crash.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Ryan Newman couldn’t meet with Daytona International Speedway’s first responders in person, so he showed his gratitude over the radio prerace for attending to him after his Daytona 500 crash.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPGKW1VGFTeCf4-En/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPGKW1VGFTeCf4-En/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">50 People Pick The Most Instagrammable Place In Their State</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/50-people-pick-the-most-instagrammable-place-in-their-state.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="50 People Pick The Most Instagrammable Place In Their State" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:02:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:02:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/50-people-pick-the-most-instagrammable-place-in-their-state</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/50-people-pick-the-most-instagrammable-place-in-their-state.html">&lt;p&gt;Today on Culturally Speaking, we asked 50 people from 50 states where they head to craft the perfect envy-inducing Instagram post. Something cosmopolitan like a selfie with the Manhattan skyline from Brooklyn Bridge Park? Or maybe more like the stunning landscape of the badlands in the Dakotas? Tune in and take notes for the next time you need that rush of likes lighting up your notifications.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">Today on Culturally Speaking, we asked 50 people from 50 states where they head to craft the perfect envy-inducing Instagram post. Something cosmopolitan like a selfie with the Manhattan skyline from Brooklyn Bridge Park? Or maybe more like the stunning landscape of the badlands in the Dakotas? Tune in and take notes for the next time you need that rush of likes lighting up your notifications.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPIUj1VGC_-COvC1f/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPIUj1VGC_-COvC1f/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Lohanthony Makes YouTube Return in Video Denouncing Homosexuality</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/lohanthony-makes-youtube-return-in-video-denouncing-homosexuality.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lohanthony Makes YouTube Return in Video Denouncing Homosexuality" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:02:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:02:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/lohanthony-makes-youtube-return-in-video-denouncing-homosexuality</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/lohanthony-makes-youtube-return-in-video-denouncing-homosexuality.html">&lt;p&gt;Former YouTube star Lohanthony was known for his fun, flamboyant personality which gained him popularity online in videos about pop culture and social media drama. But after a hiatus from posting videos, he posted two this week proclaiming his newfound faith in Christianity and he seemingly denounced homosexuality as well as his past behavior as a gay man. Many fans believe he underwent conversion therapy.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="fun" />
  <summary type="html">Former YouTube star Lohanthony was known for his fun, flamboyant personality which gained him popularity online in videos about pop culture and social media drama. But after a hiatus from posting videos, he posted two this week proclaiming his newfound faith in Christianity and he seemingly denounced homosexuality as well as his past behavior as a gay man. Many fans believe he underwent conversion therapy.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ84F1VH7oWOr11-E/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ84F1VH7oWOr11-E/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Get to know Dellin Betances - a big man with a big heart</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/get-to-know-dellin-betances-a-big-man-with-a-big-heart.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Get to know Dellin Betances - a big man with a big heart" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:01:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:01:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/get-to-know-dellin-betances-a-big-man-with-a-big-heart</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/get-to-know-dellin-betances-a-big-man-with-a-big-heart.html">&lt;p&gt;Mets pitcher Dellin Betances has been one of baseball’s best relief pitchers, but there’s so much more to him than that.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Mets pitcher Dellin Betances has been one of baseball’s best relief pitchers, but there’s so much more to him than that.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPhnM1VFhwqL32j6r/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPhnM1VFhwqL32j6r/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Qurbatain Episode 14 HUM TV Drama 24 August 2020</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/qurbatain-episode-14-hum-tv-drama-24-august-2020.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Qurbatain Episode 14 HUM TV Drama 24 August 2020" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:00:26+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:00:26+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/qurbatain-episode-14-hum-tv-drama-24-august-2020</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/qurbatain-episode-14-hum-tv-drama-24-august-2020.html">&lt;p&gt;Qurbatain, Episode 14, Official HD Video - 24 August 2020  &lt;br /&gt;Qurbatain is HUM TV’s newest presentation that revolves around friendship, lust and deceit. It is an intertwined story of two friends Areeba and Zamal and highlights how low one can stoop to gain a luxurious life but at what cost. Areeba, raised by a single mother belongs to a low-middle class family while Zamal belongs to an upper-class family. Lured by wealth and luxurious life, Areeba takes some dreadful steps that put an irreparable dent on the sacred bond of friendship and her morality, but little does she know what fate has in store for her.   &lt;br /&gt;Starring:  &lt;br /&gt;Anmol Baloch, Shehbaz Hamid Shigri, Komal Sajid, Arij Moheuddin, Kashif Mahmood, Munazzah Arif, Tahira Imam, Abbas Ashraf Awan, Laiba Sarfaraz, Leyla Zuberi, Ahmed Taha Ghani, Kamran Hussain, Halima, Zain Afzal and others.  &lt;br /&gt;Directed By: Kamran Akbar Khan   &lt;br /&gt;Written By: Rizwan Ahmed  &lt;br /&gt;Produced By: Momina Duraid Productions  &lt;br /&gt;#Qurbatain #HUMTV #AnmolBaloch #ShehbazHamidShigri #KomalSajid #ArijMoheuddin  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">Qurbatain, Episode 14, Official HD Video - 24 August 2020 Qurbatain is HUM TV’s newest presentation that revolves around friendship, lust and deceit. It is an intertwined story of two friends Areeba and Zamal and highlights how low one can stoop to gain a luxurious life but at what cost. Areeba, raised by a single mother belongs to a low-middle class family while Zamal belongs to an upper-class family. Lured by wealth and luxurious life, Areeba takes some dreadful steps that put an irreparable dent on the sacred bond of friendship and her morality, but little does she know what fate has in store for her. Starring: Anmol Baloch, Shehbaz Hamid Shigri, Komal Sajid, Arij Moheuddin, Kashif Mahmood, Munazzah Arif, Tahira Imam, Abbas Ashraf Awan, Laiba Sarfaraz, Leyla Zuberi, Ahmed Taha Ghani, Kamran Hussain, Halima, Zain Afzal and others. Directed By: Kamran Akbar Khan Written By: Rizwan Ahmed Produced By: Momina Duraid Productions #Qurbatain #HUMTV #AnmolBaloch #ShehbazHamidShigri #KomalSajid #ArijMoheuddin</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ63R1VG_uN-4YCCa/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ63R1VG_uN-4YCCa/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Fausto Alzati WANZtalks</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/fausto-alzati-wanztalks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fausto Alzati WANZtalks" />
  <published>2020-08-26T17:00:22+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T17:00:22+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/fausto-alzati-wanztalks</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/fausto-alzati-wanztalks.html">&lt;p&gt;En este episodio diecinueve nos acompaña Fausto Alzati, poeta, actor y tatuador. Escucha esta plática donde hablamos sobre el arte de la poesía, el budismo y lo que significa mejorarse a uno mismo al aceptar que nuestro presente es la consecuencia de nuestras decisiones.  &lt;br /&gt;Síguenos para más episodios de WANZtalks en Spotify  &lt;br /&gt;Para escuchar éste y más episodios de WANZtalks ve a:  &lt;br /&gt;Invitada @faustosexto  &lt;br /&gt;Host @ramiromf  &lt;br /&gt;Somos @wearenotzombies  &lt;br /&gt;WANZTalks es el podcast de We Are Not Zombies en donde tendremos Pláticas DeMentes con creadores y protagonistas de la escena cultural mexicana nacional e internacional.  &lt;br /&gt;Sobre la Temporada Dos:  &lt;br /&gt;Este podcast fue grabado previo a los acontecimientos suscitados por el COVID-19.   &lt;br /&gt;Reconocemos la seriedad de la situación actual y la necesidad de seguir creando, por ello reafirmamos nuestro compromiso con la comunidad de We Are Not Zombies de que al hacer WANZtalks buscamos proponer un espacio para expandir nuestra mente, con el objetivo de impulsar la creatividad y la conciencia colectiva desde donde podremos reimaginar, reinventar y reconstruir nuestra realidad.  &lt;br /&gt;Con mucho amor, la WANZ Fam❤️&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="creation" />
  <summary type="html">En este episodio diecinueve nos acompaña Fausto Alzati, poeta, actor y tatuador. Escucha esta plática donde hablamos sobre el arte de la poesía, el budismo y lo que significa mejorarse a uno mismo al aceptar que nuestro presente es la consecuencia de nuestras decisiones. Síguenos para más episodios de WANZtalks en Spotify Para escuchar éste y más episodios de WANZtalks ve a: Invitada @faustosexto Host @ramiromf Somos @wearenotzombies WANZTalks es el podcast de We Are Not Zombies en donde tendremos Pláticas DeMentes con creadores y protagonistas de la escena cultural mexicana nacional e internacional. Sobre la Temporada Dos: Este podcast fue grabado previo a los acontecimientos suscitados por el COVID-19. Reconocemos la seriedad de la situación actual y la necesidad de seguir creando, por ello reafirmamos nuestro compromiso con la comunidad de We Are Not Zombies de que al hacer WANZtalks buscamos proponer un espacio para expandir nuestra mente, con el objetivo de impulsar la creatividad y la conciencia colectiva desde donde podremos reimaginar, reinventar y reconstruir nuestra realidad. Con mucho amor, la WANZ Fam❤️</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SODx-1VFq3ALmiLd1/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SODx-1VFq3ALmiLd1/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">IPL 2020 : Dream 11 wins Title sponsor race for IPL season 13 beating BYJUs, Tata वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/ipl-2020-dream-11-wins-title-sponsor-race-for-ipl-season-13-beating-by.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IPL 2020 : Dream 11 wins Title sponsor race for IPL season 13 beating BYJUs, Tata वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:58:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:58:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/ipl-2020-dream-11-wins-title-sponsor-race-for-ipl-season-13-beating-by</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/ipl-2020-dream-11-wins-title-sponsor-race-for-ipl-season-13-beating-by.html">&lt;p&gt;Dream11 on Tuesday (August 18) has bagged the title sponsorship rights for IPL 2020 for Rs 222 crore. The fantasy sports platform overcame stiff challenge from corporate giants Tata Sons, and online education platforms Byjus and Unacademy. The ANI quoted IPL Governing Council Chairman Brijesh Patel as saying that the Dream11 tide over other contenders. BCCI had made it clear in their bidding conditions that companies that have a minimum turnover of Rs 300 crore can participate in the bidding. The contract will run from August 18 to December 31, 2020.    &lt;br /&gt;चीनी स्मार्टफोन निर्माता कंपनी वीवो के आईपीएल स्पॉन्सरशिप से हटने के बाद नए स्पॉन्सर की तलाश पूरी हो गई है. यूएई में इस साल आईपीएल के 13वें सीजन के आयोजन के लिए ड्रीम 11 को 222 करोड़ में स्पॉन्सरशिप दी गई है. IPL के चेयरमैन बृजेश पटेल ने PTI से कहा कि Dream 11 ने 222 करोड़ रुपये में IPL 2020 सीजन के लिए स्पॉन्सरशिप राइट्स खरीदे हैं. बता दें कि ये बोली VIVO के सालाना 440 करोड़ रुपये से 218 करोड़ रुपये कम है. ड्रीम 11 ने चीनी कंपनी VIVO की जगह लगभग साढ़े चार महीने के लिए टाइटल प्रायोजन का अधिकार हासिल किया. आपको बता दें, इस रेस में अन्य कम्पनियां भी थी. पता चला कि टाटा समूह ने अंतिम बोली नहीं लगाई.    &lt;br /&gt;#VIVO    #IPL2020   #Dream11&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Dream11 on Tuesday (August 18) has bagged the title sponsorship rights for IPL 2020 for Rs 222 crore. The fantasy sports platform overcame stiff challenge from corporate giants Tata Sons, and online education platforms Byjus and Unacademy. The ANI quoted IPL Governing Council Chairman Brijesh Patel as saying that the Dream11 tide over other contenders. BCCI had made it clear in their bidding conditions that companies that have a minimum turnover of Rs 300 crore can participate in the bidding. The contract will run from August 18 to December 31, 2020. चीनी स्मार्टफोन निर्माता कंपनी वीवो के आईपीएल स्पॉन्सरशिप से हटने के बाद नए स्पॉन्सर की तलाश पूरी हो गई है. यूएई में इस साल आईपीएल के 13वें सीजन के आयोजन के लिए ड्रीम 11 को 222 करोड़ में स्पॉन्सरशिप दी गई है. IPL के चेयरमैन बृजेश पटेल ने PTI से कहा कि Dream 11 ने 222 करोड़ रुपये में IPL 2020 सीजन के लिए स्पॉन्सरशिप राइट्स खरीदे हैं. बता दें कि ये बोली VIVO के सालाना 440 करोड़ रुपये से 218 करोड़ रुपये कम है. ड्रीम 11 ने चीनी कंपनी VIVO की जगह लगभग साढ़े चार महीने के लिए टाइटल प्रायोजन का अधिकार हासिल किया. आपको बता दें, इस रेस में अन्य कम्पनियां भी थी. पता चला कि टाटा समूह ने अंतिम बोली नहीं लगाई. #VIVO #IPL2020 #Dream11</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPRge1VF0VHLhOB7h/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPRge1VF0VHLhOB7h/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Emma’s determination to make cremation jewellery accessible for everyone</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/emma-s-determination-to-make-cremation-jewellery-accessible-for-everyo.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Emma’s determination to make cremation jewellery accessible for everyone" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:58:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:58:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/emma-s-determination-to-make-cremation-jewellery-accessible-for-everyo</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/emma-s-determination-to-make-cremation-jewellery-accessible-for-everyo.html">&lt;p&gt;“Handling people’s ashes is such an honour, but also such a responsibility, and I work really hard to make sure people get exactly what they want,&quot; says Emma.  &lt;br /&gt;“I’ve handled the ashes of people’s parents and grandparents, and one woman even asked me to create something to hold the ashes of her baby.  &lt;br /&gt;“I’ve had people crying at the front door with joy when they collect things, and then I start crying along with them, it means so much.”  &lt;br /&gt;For every item of cremation jewellery, no matter the shape or style, Emma charges just £10.  &lt;br /&gt;“I want this to be something everyone can have,” says Emma, of Chesterfield.  &lt;br /&gt;“I’d do it for free if I could.”&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">“Handling people’s ashes is such an honour, but also such a responsibility, and I work really hard to make sure people get exactly what they want,&quot; says Emma. “I’ve handled the ashes of people’s parents and grandparents, and one woman even asked me to create something to hold the ashes of her baby. “I’ve had people crying at the front door with joy when they collect things, and then I start crying along with them, it means so much.” For every item of cremation jewellery, no matter the shape or style, Emma charges just £10. “I want this to be something everyone can have,” says Emma, of Chesterfield. “I’d do it for free if I could.”</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPz8h1VGdLGvWnVAE/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPz8h1VGdLGvWnVAE/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">First Day In Office- Expectation Vs Reality - POPxo</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/first-day-in-office-expectation-vs-reality-popxo.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Day In Office- Expectation Vs Reality - POPxo" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:55:09+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:55:09+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/first-day-in-office-expectation-vs-reality-popxo</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/first-day-in-office-expectation-vs-reality-popxo.html">&lt;p&gt;We all can relate to the moment when you show up all excited, filled with expectations on your first day at a new job. The excitement on the face of HR, the enthusiasm of co-workers on seeing you, the helpful nature of the office staff, the cool, swanky cabin and we’ve all expected this and so much more from our first day at a new job. But guess what, the reality of the first day at a new job rarely meets its high expectations. Watch today’s episode of POPxo Expectation Vs Reality to see our relatable take on how your reality fares in comparison to your first at a new job.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="fun" />
  <summary type="html">We all can relate to the moment when you show up all excited, filled with expectations on your first day at a new job. The excitement on the face of HR, the enthusiasm of co-workers on seeing you, the helpful nature of the office staff, the cool, swanky cabin and we’ve all expected this and so much more from our first day at a new job. But guess what, the reality of the first day at a new job rarely meets its high expectations. Watch today’s episode of POPxo Expectation Vs Reality to see our relatable take on how your reality fares in comparison to your first at a new job.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPYDQ1VFcQbO2Ogmg/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPYDQ1VFcQbO2Ogmg/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Mali में सेना के विद्रोह के बाद President ने दिया इस्तीफा, संसद भंग वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/mali-president.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mali में सेना के विद्रोह के बाद President ने दिया इस्तीफा, संसद भंग वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:55:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:55:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/mali-president</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/mali-president.html">&lt;p&gt;In a televised address, Mr Keïta said he was also dissolving the government and parliament.&quot;I want no blood to be spilled to keep me in power,&quot; he added.It comes hours after he and Prime Minister Boubou Cissé were taken to a military camp near the capital Bamako, drawing condemnation from regional powers and France.&quot;If today, certain elements of our armed forces want this to end through their intervention, do I really have a choice?&quot; said Mr Keïta.  &lt;br /&gt;पश्चिमी अफ्रीका के देश माली में राजनीतिक संकट पैदा हो गया है। विद्रोही सैनिकों ने तख्तापलट करते हुए राष्ट्रपति इब्राहिम बॉबकर कीता और प्रधानमंत्री बाउबो सिसे को गन पॉइंट पर गिरफ्तार किया है। राष्ट्रपति ने इसके बाद अपना इस्तीफा देते हुए संसद भंग कर दी। उन्होंने कहा कि वह खून खराबा नहीं चाहते हैं। इसका एक वीडियो भी सामने आया है। माली में राष्ट्रपति को हटाने के लिए कई दिनों से प्रदर्शन हो रहे थे। माली की सेना ने मंगलवार सुबह से ही विद्रोह शुरू कर दिया था।   &lt;br /&gt;#Mali #MaliRevolt #MaliPresidentResign #OneindiaHindi&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">In a televised address, Mr Keïta said he was also dissolving the government and parliament.&quot;I want no blood to be spilled to keep me in power,&quot; he added.It comes hours after he and Prime Minister Boubou Cissé were taken to a military camp near the capital Bamako, drawing condemnation from regional powers and France.&quot;If today, certain elements of our armed forces want this to end through their intervention, do I really have a choice?&quot; said Mr Keïta. पश्चिमी अफ्रीका के देश माली में राजनीतिक संकट पैदा हो गया है। विद्रोही सैनिकों ने तख्तापलट करते हुए राष्ट्रपति इब्राहिम बॉबकर कीता और प्रधानमंत्री बाउबो सिसे को गन पॉइंट पर गिरफ्तार किया है। राष्ट्रपति ने इसके बाद अपना इस्तीफा देते हुए संसद भंग कर दी। उन्होंने कहा कि वह खून खराबा नहीं चाहते हैं। इसका एक वीडियो भी सामने आया है। माली में राष्ट्रपति को हटाने के लिए कई दिनों से प्रदर्शन हो रहे थे। माली की सेना ने मंगलवार सुबह से ही विद्रोह शुरू कर दिया था। #Mali #MaliRevolt #MaliPresidentResign #OneindiaHindi</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPXBJ1VHSASiX5IlU/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPXBJ1VHSASiX5IlU/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Popularité : Castex chute sévèrement</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/popularit-castex-chute-s-v-rement.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Popularité : Castex chute sévèrement" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:55:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:55:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/popularit-castex-chute-s-v-rement</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/popularit-castex-chute-s-v-rement.html">&lt;p&gt;Pour Jean Castex, l’état de grâce aura été fugitif. Le Premier ministre perd 7 points de popularité en un mois dans la baromètre Ifop/JDD.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Pour Jean Castex, l’état de grâce aura été fugitif. Le Premier ministre perd 7 points de popularité en un mois dans la baromètre Ifop/JDD.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPxot1VGX6EMCultU/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPxot1VGX6EMCultU/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Pokemon Sword &amp;amp; Shield Episode 33 English Subbed : ‘Would You Like To Do a Pokémon Trade?’</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/pokemon-sword-shield-episode-33-english-subbed-would-you-like-to-do-a.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pokemon Sword &amp;amp; Shield Episode 33 English Subbed : ‘Would You Like To Do a Pokémon Trade?’" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:54:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:54:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/pokemon-sword-shield-episode-33-english-subbed-would-you-like-to-do-a</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/pokemon-sword-shield-episode-33-english-subbed-would-you-like-to-do-a.html">&lt;p&gt;At the Pokémon Exchange Event in Kuchiba City, which Satoshi and Go are attending, Koromo (the self-proclaimed &quot;Bug Poké Queen&quot; of the Sinnoh Region) is determined to get Go’s Kairos. Since Go isn’t willing to trade, he tries to help her catch a wild Kairos, with interesting results courtesy of Rocket-Dan and a Heracros.  &lt;br /&gt;pokemon   &lt;br /&gt;pokemon sword  &lt;br /&gt;pokemon shield  &lt;br /&gt;episode 33  &lt;br /&gt;pokemon journeys&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">At the Pokémon Exchange Event in Kuchiba City, which Satoshi and Go are attending, Koromo (the self-proclaimed &quot;Bug Poké Queen&quot; of the Sinnoh Region) is determined to get Go’s Kairos. Since Go isn’t willing to trade, he tries to help her catch a wild Kairos, with interesting results courtesy of Rocket-Dan and a Heracros. pokemon pokemon sword pokemon shield episode 33 pokemon journeys</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPGkR1VEg2Hucon5F/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPGkR1VEg2Hucon5F/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Neighbours Soap Scoop! Shane turns nasty with Roxy</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/neighbours-soap-scoop-shane-turns-nasty-with-roxy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Neighbours Soap Scoop! Shane turns nasty with Roxy" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:53:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:53:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/neighbours-soap-scoop-shane-turns-nasty-with-roxy</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/neighbours-soap-scoop-shane-turns-nasty-with-roxy.html">&lt;p&gt;Coming up on Neighbours… Shane unleashes a harsh verbal tirade against Roxy after she finds his stash of drugs.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">Coming up on Neighbours… Shane unleashes a harsh verbal tirade against Roxy after she finds his stash of drugs.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPLfH1VEyCp5Q-Nps/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPLfH1VEyCp5Q-Nps/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">First Thing Trump’s USPS cuts are ‘a crisis for US democracy’</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/first-thing-trump-s-usps-cuts-are-a-crisis-for-us-democracy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Thing Trump’s USPS cuts are ‘a crisis for US democracy’" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:51:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:51:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/first-thing-trump-s-usps-cuts-are-a-crisis-for-us-democracy</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/first-thing-trump-s-usps-cuts-are-a-crisis-for-us-democracy.html">&lt;p&gt;Good morning,Nancy Pelosi has recalled the House of Representatives from its summer recess early, to vote on a bill to prevent the United States Postal Service downgrading its operations or service from early-2020 levels, in response to what the Democratic House speaker called the “sabotage” of the mail system by the Trump administration. Donald Trump admitted last week that he was blocking funding to the USPS in a bid to disrupt mail-in voting at November’s presidential election. Postal workers told the Guardian that changes implemented by the new postmaster general, the Trump loyalist Louis DeJoy, were already causing major delays. Barack Obama has condemned Trump’s explicit “kneecapping” of the mail, while on Sunday, Bernie Sanders added his voice to the widespread warnings, calling the situation “a crisis for American democracy” in an interview with NBC:What you are witnessing is a president of the United States who is doing everything he can to suppress the vote, make it harder for people to engage in mail-in balloting at a time when people will be putting their lives on the line by having to go out to a polling station and vote. The Covid-19 death toll in the US is now more than 170,000. Teachers in states currently hit hard by the coronavirus, such as Georgia and Florida, remain fearful of plans to press ahead with the reopening of schools. But Jared Kushner has no such concerns: the president’s son-in-law said on Sunday that his own children would “absolutely” be returning to school, despite the risks. Students at Johns Hopkins will not be on campus in the fall but, as Kari Paul reports, the Baltimore university is inviting them to collaborate in reconstructing an accurate replica of the campus within the popular videogame Minecraft. The pandemic has highlighted the homelessness that already exists in Austin, Texas, reports Alexandra Villarreal.   &lt;br /&gt;All data is taken from the source:   &lt;br /&gt;Article Link:   &lt;br /&gt;#trump #duluthnewstribune #virginiabeachnews #news #nytimes #cnn #newsnow&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Good morning,Nancy Pelosi has recalled the House of Representatives from its summer recess early, to vote on a bill to prevent the United States Postal Service downgrading its operations or service from early-2020 levels, in response to what the Democratic House speaker called the “sabotage” of the mail system by the Trump administration. Donald Trump admitted last week that he was blocking funding to the USPS in a bid to disrupt mail-in voting at November’s presidential election. Postal workers told the Guardian that changes implemented by the new postmaster general, the Trump loyalist Louis DeJoy, were already causing major delays. Barack Obama has condemned Trump’s explicit “kneecapping” of the mail, while on Sunday, Bernie Sanders added his voice to the widespread warnings, calling the situation “a crisis for American democracy” in an interview with NBC:What you are witnessing is a president of the United States who is doing everything he can to suppress the vote, make it harder for people to engage in mail-in balloting at a time when people will be putting their lives on the line by having to go out to a polling station and vote. The Covid-19 death toll in the US is now more than 170,000. Teachers in states currently hit hard by the coronavirus, such as Georgia and Florida, remain fearful of plans to press ahead with the reopening of schools. But Jared Kushner has no such concerns: the president’s son-in-law said on Sunday that his own children would “absolutely” be returning to school, despite the risks. Students at Johns Hopkins will not be on campus in the fall but, as Kari Paul reports, the Baltimore university is inviting them to collaborate in reconstructing an accurate replica of the campus within the popular videogame Minecraft. The pandemic has highlighted the homelessness that already exists in Austin, Texas, reports Alexandra Villarreal. All data is taken from the source: Article Link: #trump #duluthnewstribune #virginiabeachnews #news #nytimes #cnn #newsnow</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPO501VEvcsC4seeI/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPO501VEvcsC4seeI/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Feel Good Today : 93 साल की दादी का जबरदस्त डांस,ठुमके देख लोगों ने बजाई सीटियां वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/feel-good-today-93.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Feel Good Today : 93 साल की दादी का जबरदस्त डांस,ठुमके देख लोगों ने बजाई सीटियां वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:50:09+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:50:09+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/feel-good-today-93</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/feel-good-today-93.html">&lt;p&gt;The whole country is under stress due to Corona virus.But today we are going to show you a video that will refresh your mood..In this video, a 93-year-old grandmother of Kolkata is seen making a tremendous dance.Seeing the tremendous bangs of grandmother, her family members could not stop herself from blowing the whistle.   &lt;br /&gt;कोरोना वायरस के चलते पूरा देश तनाव में है…लेकिन आज हम आपको एक ऐसा वीडियो दिखाने जा रहे हैं जो आपके मूड को तरोताजा कर देगा..इस वीडियो में कोलकाता की 93 साल की एक बुजुर्ग दादी जबरदस्त ठुमके लगाती नजर आ रही हैं.. दादी के जबरदस्त ठुमकों को देख उनके लोग परिवार के लोग भी सीटी बजाने से खुद को नहीं रोक पाए.दादी के डांस का ये वीडियो. सोशल मीडिया पर काफी तेजी से वायरल हो रहा है.  &lt;br /&gt;#FeelGood #Kolkata&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The whole country is under stress due to Corona virus.But today we are going to show you a video that will refresh your mood..In this video, a 93-year-old grandmother of Kolkata is seen making a tremendous dance.Seeing the tremendous bangs of grandmother, her family members could not stop herself from blowing the whistle. कोरोना वायरस के चलते पूरा देश तनाव में है…लेकिन आज हम आपको एक ऐसा वीडियो दिखाने जा रहे हैं जो आपके मूड को तरोताजा कर देगा..इस वीडियो में कोलकाता की 93 साल की एक बुजुर्ग दादी जबरदस्त ठुमके लगाती नजर आ रही हैं.. दादी के जबरदस्त ठुमकों को देख उनके लोग परिवार के लोग भी सीटी बजाने से खुद को नहीं रोक पाए.दादी के डांस का ये वीडियो. सोशल मीडिया पर काफी तेजी से वायरल हो रहा है. #FeelGood #Kolkata</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPMTw1VEqf4bH1tWF/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPMTw1VEqf4bH1tWF/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">There Will be More Riots in Minneapolis After Chauvin is Almost Surely Acquitted</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/there-will-be-more-riots-in-minneapolis-after-chauvin-is-almost-surely.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="There Will be More Riots in Minneapolis After Chauvin is Almost Surely Acquitted" />
  <published>2020-08-26T16:48:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T16:48:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/there-will-be-more-riots-in-minneapolis-after-chauvin-is-almost-surely</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/there-will-be-more-riots-in-minneapolis-after-chauvin-is-almost-surely.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Website:   &lt;br /&gt;Merch:   &lt;br /&gt;Support via donation:  &lt;br /&gt;Patreon:   &lt;br /&gt;Subscribestar:   &lt;br /&gt;My books:  &lt;br /&gt;Blogger:   &lt;br /&gt;Wordpress:   &lt;br /&gt;My other platforms:  &lt;br /&gt;Twitter:   &lt;br /&gt;Gab:   &lt;br /&gt;Facebook:   &lt;br /&gt;Minds:   &lt;br /&gt;Bitchute:   &lt;br /&gt;Dailymotion:   &lt;br /&gt;Brighteon:   &lt;br /&gt;LBRY:   &lt;br /&gt;BTC: 17q1BfF2up8orEKN8DQgpEPX83RfbAZ5QL  &lt;br /&gt;ETH: 0x956e7aF6706C3b5E2cf7e15c16c7018c4f42aF79  &lt;br /&gt;LTC: LQNJed6vDhR4U4LB7g8jGep4UQ7yeqJdPw&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Website: Merch: Support via donation: Patreon: Subscribestar: My books: Blogger: Wordpress: My other platforms: Twitter: Gab: Facebook: Minds: Bitchute: Dailymotion: Brighteon: LBRY: BTC: 17q1BfF2up8orEKN8DQgpEPX83RfbAZ5QL ETH: 0x956e7aF6706C3b5E2cf7e15c16c7018c4f42aF79 LTC: LQNJed6vDhR4U4LB7g8jGep4UQ7yeqJdPw</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ2ay1VGvFm3zVEsI/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ2ay1VGvFm3zVEsI/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 </feed>