<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
<updated>2020-08-28T17:20:56+03:00</updated>
<id>https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml</id>
<title type="html">Adowsom</title>
<subtitle>Duct Tape is like the force. There's a dark side and a light side, and it holds the universe together.</subtitle>
<author>
 <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
 <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
 <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
</author>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Biar Makin Harmonis, Adam Suseno Setuju Main TikTok Bareng Inul Daratista</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/biar-makin-harmonis-adam-suseno-setuju-main-tiktok-bareng-inul-daratis.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Biar Makin Harmonis, Adam Suseno Setuju Main TikTok Bareng Inul Daratista" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:17:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:17:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/biar-makin-harmonis-adam-suseno-setuju-main-tiktok-bareng-inul-daratis</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/biar-makin-harmonis-adam-suseno-setuju-main-tiktok-bareng-inul-daratis.html">&lt;p&gt;Pedangdut Inul Daratista mengungkap alasannya sering main TikTok bareng suaminya, Adam Suseno. Dia bilang awalnya cuma buat mengisi waktu luang.  &lt;br /&gt;Link Terkait:   &lt;br /&gt;Ibu satu anak ini juga tidak menyangka respons publik begitu bagus akan konten TikTok buatannya.  &lt;br /&gt;#InulDaratista #AdamSuseno  &lt;br /&gt;==================================  &lt;br /&gt;Homepage:   &lt;br /&gt;Facebook Fan Page:   &lt;br /&gt;Instagram:   &lt;br /&gt;Twitter:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="people" />
  <summary type="html">Pedangdut Inul Daratista mengungkap alasannya sering main TikTok bareng suaminya, Adam Suseno. Dia bilang awalnya cuma buat mengisi waktu luang. Link Terkait: Ibu satu anak ini juga tidak menyangka respons publik begitu bagus akan konten TikTok buatannya. #InulDaratista #AdamSuseno ================================== Homepage: Facebook Fan Page: Instagram: Twitter:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPnYU1VFyK-_FaoCV/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPnYU1VFyK-_FaoCV/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Pakistan batsman Asif Ali almost hits Keemo Paul with his bat during a CPL Match वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/pakistan-batsman-asif-ali-almost-hits-keemo-paul-with-his-bat-during-a.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pakistan batsman Asif Ali almost hits Keemo Paul with his bat during a CPL Match वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:16:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:16:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/pakistan-batsman-asif-ali-almost-hits-keemo-paul-with-his-bat-during-a</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/pakistan-batsman-asif-ali-almost-hits-keemo-paul-with-his-bat-during-a.html">&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s Asif Ali has found himself in trouble because of his aggressive gesture to Keemo Paul during the 2020 Caribbean Premier League match between Jamaica Tallawahs and Guyana Amazon Warriors.Ali, who plays for Tallawahs, was sent back to the dugout for three by Keemo Paul after his miscued drive was caught brilliantly by Chris Green at long-on.   &lt;br /&gt;सीपीएल 2020 के एक मैच में पाकिस्तानी बल्लेबाज ने गुस्से में ऐसी हरकत कर दी है, जिसकी सब तरफ आलोचना हो रही है। जमैका तल्लावाह और गयाना अमेजन वॉरियर्स के बीच खेले जा रहे मैच में पाकिस्तानी बल्लेबाज आसिफ अली में गुस्से में अपने बल्ले को ऐसे घुमाया कि वह कीमो पॉल को लगने से बाल-बाल बच गया। सीपीएल में आसिफ अली जमैका की तरफ से और कीमो गयाना की तरफ से खेल रहे हैं।  &lt;br /&gt;#CPL2020  #AsifAli #KeemoPaul&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Pakistan’s Asif Ali has found himself in trouble because of his aggressive gesture to Keemo Paul during the 2020 Caribbean Premier League match between Jamaica Tallawahs and Guyana Amazon Warriors.Ali, who plays for Tallawahs, was sent back to the dugout for three by Keemo Paul after his miscued drive was caught brilliantly by Chris Green at long-on. सीपीएल 2020 के एक मैच में पाकिस्तानी बल्लेबाज ने गुस्से में ऐसी हरकत कर दी है, जिसकी सब तरफ आलोचना हो रही है। जमैका तल्लावाह और गयाना अमेजन वॉरियर्स के बीच खेले जा रहे मैच में पाकिस्तानी बल्लेबाज आसिफ अली में गुस्से में अपने बल्ले को ऐसे घुमाया कि वह कीमो पॉल को लगने से बाल-बाल बच गया। सीपीएल में आसिफ अली जमैका की तरफ से और कीमो गयाना की तरफ से खेल रहे हैं। #CPL2020 #AsifAli #KeemoPaul</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQRbi1VHu6YoTouTH/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQRbi1VHu6YoTouTH/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Neha Mehta Thank Cast And Crew Of Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/neha-mehta-thank-cast-and-crew-of-taarak-mehta-ka-ooltah-chashmah.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Neha Mehta Thank Cast And Crew Of Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:16:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:16:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/neha-mehta-thank-cast-and-crew-of-taarak-mehta-ka-ooltah-chashmah</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/neha-mehta-thank-cast-and-crew-of-taarak-mehta-ka-ooltah-chashmah.html">&lt;p&gt;Neha Mehta who played the character of Anjali in Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah has quit the comedy sitcom after 12 years. Her exiting the show shocked her fans as she was one of the key members of the cast and was loved for her acting. Now addressing her exit Neha took to her social media account where she thanked the cast and crew of Taarak Mehta. &quot;Hello everyone, and thank you for everything. I’ve worked 12 amazing years at this amazing show (Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah), and I am forever thankful for the beautiful career I’ve had. To my amazing respected Asit Kumar Modi Ji, co-stars, tmkoc whole team, I appreciate the hard work you’ve done completing some of our beautiful journey. I’ve never had so much fun before. I am so glad to be part of this show, but I will miss the spontaneity of the work and generosity of such brilliant colleagues. Thank you again and all the best for the future. Show must go on.&quot; Reportedly, Belan Wali Bahu fame Sunayana Fozdar will be replacing Neha in the show. Meanwhile, following Neha’s footsteps, Gurucharan Singh who essayed Roshan Singh Sodhi’s role also bid adieu the show in the wake of the global pandemic. This is the second time Gurucharan has left the show, previously he exited due to creative difference but he was back within a year. After Gurucharan’s exit Balwinder Singh Suri has replaced him, a source close to the show revealed, &quot;Balwinder has already begun shooting on the sets from this week. The makers waited for Gurucharan Singh to come back and join the show but considering his father’s health, the actor has decided to take a break from the show and be with him. Hence, they got Balwinder on board and started shooting with him for future episodes.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="people" />
  <summary type="html">Neha Mehta who played the character of Anjali in Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah has quit the comedy sitcom after 12 years. Her exiting the show shocked her fans as she was one of the key members of the cast and was loved for her acting. Now addressing her exit Neha took to her social media account where she thanked the cast and crew of Taarak Mehta. &quot;Hello everyone, and thank you for everything. I’ve worked 12 amazing years at this amazing show (Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah), and I am forever thankful for the beautiful career I’ve had. To my amazing respected Asit Kumar Modi Ji, co-stars, tmkoc whole team, I appreciate the hard work you’ve done completing some of our beautiful journey. I’ve never had so much fun before. I am so glad to be part of this show, but I will miss the spontaneity of the work and generosity of such brilliant colleagues. Thank you again and all the best for the future. Show must go on.&quot; Reportedly, Belan Wali Bahu fame Sunayana Fozdar will be replacing Neha in the show. Meanwhile, following Neha’s footsteps, Gurucharan Singh who essayed Roshan Singh Sodhi’s role also bid adieu the show in the wake of the global pandemic. This is the second time Gurucharan has left the show, previously he exited due to creative difference but he was back within a year. After Gurucharan’s exit Balwinder Singh Suri has replaced him, a source close to the show revealed, &quot;Balwinder has already begun shooting on the sets from this week. The makers waited for Gurucharan Singh to come back and join the show but considering his father’s health, the actor has decided to take a break from the show and be with him. Hence, they got Balwinder on board and started shooting with him for future episodes.&quot;</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQPlx1VHrxm6tNXzI/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQPlx1VHrxm6tNXzI/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Kimberly Guilfoyle at the RNC ‘The best is yet to come’ USA TODAY</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/kimberly-guilfoyle-at-the-rnc-the-best-is-yet-to-come-usa-today.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kimberly Guilfoyle at the RNC ‘The best is yet to come’ USA TODAY" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:15:09+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:15:09+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/kimberly-guilfoyle-at-the-rnc-the-best-is-yet-to-come-usa-today</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/kimberly-guilfoyle-at-the-rnc-the-best-is-yet-to-come-usa-today.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kimberly Guilfoyle at the RNC ‘The best is yet to come’ USA TODAY&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Kimberly Guilfoyle at the RNC ‘The best is yet to come’ USA TODAY&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Kimberly Guilfoyle at the RNC 'The best is yet to come' USA TODAY&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">Kimberly Guilfoyle at the RNC ‘The best is yet to come’ USA TODAY Kimberly Guilfoyle at the RNC ‘The best is yet to come’ USA TODAY Kimberly Guilfoyle at the RNC 'The best is yet to come' USA TODAY</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQHPh1VHXxJ12mF17/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQHPh1VHXxJ12mF17/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">La Rolls-Royce Phantom V passe par la case Rétrofit</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/la-rolls-royce-phantom-v-passe-par-la-case-r-trofit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="La Rolls-Royce Phantom V passe par la case Rétrofit" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:14:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:14:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/la-rolls-royce-phantom-v-passe-par-la-case-r-trofit</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/la-rolls-royce-phantom-v-passe-par-la-case-r-trofit.html">&lt;p&gt;Lunaz, spécialiste britannique du rétrofit, ajoute la Rolls-Royce Phantom V à son catalogue. Ce chef d’œuvre du XXe siècle a été totalement desossé puis restauré à l’état neuf pour se transformer en véhicule électrique avec plus de 480 km d’autonomie pour un prix de vente de 556.000 euros.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="auto" />
  <summary type="html">Lunaz, spécialiste britannique du rétrofit, ajoute la Rolls-Royce Phantom V à son catalogue. Ce chef d’œuvre du XXe siècle a été totalement desossé puis restauré à l’état neuf pour se transformer en véhicule électrique avec plus de 480 km d’autonomie pour un prix de vente de 556.000 euros.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPoIJ1VHdN2wO71ZK/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPoIJ1VHdN2wO71ZK/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Brendon Gibbens Has a Fleet of Surfcraft For Skyward Journeys QUIVERS</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/brendon-gibbens-has-a-fleet-of-surfcraft-for-skyward-journeys-quivers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brendon Gibbens Has a Fleet of Surfcraft For Skyward Journeys QUIVERS" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:08:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:08:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/brendon-gibbens-has-a-fleet-of-surfcraft-for-skyward-journeys-quivers</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/brendon-gibbens-has-a-fleet-of-surfcraft-for-skyward-journeys-quivers.html">&lt;p&gt;Whether he admits it or not, Brendon Gibbens enjoys being out of the water more than actually in it. We’re talking high-and-dry, above-the-lip surfing here, folks. So his choice in surfboards must enable a jet-like propulsion before the inevitable blast-off, be it on the majestic walls of J-Bay or in SoCal’s mushy beachbreaks. A five-year relationship with shaper Blake Peters of the Newport Beach-based Panda Surfboards has resulted in countless intergalactic air ships with a mere two duds (the surfer-shaper duo settled on blaming the blanks acquired from an unfamiliar source).  &lt;br /&gt;While Peters’ blades make up most of Gibbens’ California quiver, he’s taken Panda’s well-rounded “The Norts” model back to the motherland and scored heaps of quality waves around Cape Town and beyond. Peters also procured a funky-looking-but-functional quad/twinny hybrid, which Gibbens surfed miraculously well out at Cloudbreak.  &lt;br /&gt;“I never learned all the technical aspects of a board, like the concaves and whatever,” Gibbens says. “I’ve just always relied on that initial first wave on a new board. It’s how you know if a board is going to be good or not. It’s quite rare for me to get a board and ride it and then find it’s a lot better than I initially thought it was.”  &lt;br /&gt;But that doesn’t mean his best sessions are necessarily his first sessions when it comes to a fresh stick.  &lt;br /&gt;“My shaper in South Africa — DVG Shapes, Dave van Ginkel is his name — he has this analogy of comparing a surfboard to a favorite pair of shoes,” Gibbens says. “If you get a new pair of shoes, they’re almost too new and don’t feel good. You need to break them in. And I find that’s quite true about boards. A new board is beautiful…clean, but I really like it when you surf it a few times and give it a few pressure dents — really just lay your footprint into it.”  &lt;br /&gt;Perhaps this is why, in the newest episode of &quot;Quivers&quot; above, he’s raving about a used Channel Islands shape he nabbed from Dane Reynolds on a trip to Portugal. But no matter the shaper or the time peg of the board’s lifespan, Gibbens has an uncanny sense for the crafts that propel him inside, outside, upside down and all around when he’s riding waves.  &lt;br /&gt;To get a closer look at Bendon’s four-board arsenal, press play in our newest episode of “Quivers” above.  &lt;br /&gt;Featured boards in order of appearance:  &lt;br /&gt;“The Norts” by Panda Surfboards  &lt;br /&gt;6’0” x 19” x 2 3/8” 28.8L  &lt;br /&gt;“The Sweetleaf” by Panda Surfboards  &lt;br /&gt;5’10” x 19 1/4” x 2 3/8” 28.5L  &lt;br /&gt;“Dane Reynolds Lender” by Channel Islands Surfboards  &lt;br /&gt;Dimensions unknown  &lt;br /&gt;“The Shrizz” by Panda Surfboards  &lt;br /&gt;5’8” x 19 3/8” x 2 1/2” 30.22L&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Whether he admits it or not, Brendon Gibbens enjoys being out of the water more than actually in it. We’re talking high-and-dry, above-the-lip surfing here, folks. So his choice in surfboards must enable a jet-like propulsion before the inevitable blast-off, be it on the majestic walls of J-Bay or in SoCal’s mushy beachbreaks. A five-year relationship with shaper Blake Peters of the Newport Beach-based Panda Surfboards has resulted in countless intergalactic air ships with a mere two duds (the surfer-shaper duo settled on blaming the blanks acquired from an unfamiliar source). While Peters’ blades make up most of Gibbens’ California quiver, he’s taken Panda’s well-rounded “The Norts” model back to the motherland and scored heaps of quality waves around Cape Town and beyond. Peters also procured a funky-looking-but-functional quad/twinny hybrid, which Gibbens surfed miraculously well out at Cloudbreak. “I never learned all the technical aspects of a board, like the concaves and whatever,” Gibbens says. “I’ve just always relied on that initial first wave on a new board. It’s how you know if a board is going to be good or not. It’s quite rare for me to get a board and ride it and then find it’s a lot better than I initially thought it was.” But that doesn’t mean his best sessions are necessarily his first sessions when it comes to a fresh stick. “My shaper in South Africa — DVG Shapes, Dave van Ginkel is his name — he has this analogy of comparing a surfboard to a favorite pair of shoes,” Gibbens says. “If you get a new pair of shoes, they’re almost too new and don’t feel good. You need to break them in. And I find that’s quite true about boards. A new board is beautiful…clean, but I really like it when you surf it a few times and give it a few pressure dents — really just lay your footprint into it.” Perhaps this is why, in the newest episode of &quot;Quivers&quot; above, he’s raving about a used Channel Islands shape he nabbed from Dane Reynolds on a trip to Portugal. But no matter the shaper or the time peg of the board’s lifespan, Gibbens has an uncanny sense for the crafts that propel him inside, outside, upside down and all around when he’s riding waves. To get a closer look at Bendon’s four-board arsenal, press play in our newest episode of “Quivers” above. Featured boards in order of appearance: “The Norts” by Panda Surfboards 6’0” x 19” x 2 3/8” 28.8L “The Sweetleaf” by Panda Surfboards 5’10” x 19 1/4” x 2 3/8” 28.5L “Dane Reynolds Lender” by Channel Islands Surfboards Dimensions unknown “The Shrizz” by Panda Surfboards 5’8” x 19 3/8” x 2 1/2” 30.22L</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQEgn1VHwBdCiWaGg/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQEgn1VHwBdCiWaGg/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Monster Hunters (镇魂歌, 2020) chinese fantasy trailer</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/monster-hunters-2020-chinese-fantasy-trailer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Monster Hunters (镇魂歌, 2020) chinese fantasy trailer" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:07:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:07:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/monster-hunters-2020-chinese-fantasy-trailer</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/monster-hunters-2020-chinese-fantasy-trailer.html">&lt;p&gt;Five hundred years ago, Grandmaster Tianxuan sealed the King of All Demons, in exchange for a prosperous and peaceful world. However, the good times were short-lived. Demons lurked in the peaceful town of Qui Yuan, and cholera resurfaced. Monster Hunters Monster Hunters&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="shortfilms" />
  <summary type="html">Five hundred years ago, Grandmaster Tianxuan sealed the King of All Demons, in exchange for a prosperous and peaceful world. However, the good times were short-lived. Demons lurked in the peaceful town of Qui Yuan, and cholera resurfaced. Monster Hunters Monster Hunters</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPwTE1VGPZqjcPpHk/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPwTE1VGPZqjcPpHk/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Story 6: Doit-on reporter la rentrée ? - 19 08</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/story-6-doit-on-reporter-la-rentr-e-19-08.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Story 6: Doit-on reporter la rentrée ? - 19 08" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:07:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:07:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/story-6-doit-on-reporter-la-rentr-e-19-08</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/story-6-doit-on-reporter-la-rentr-e-19-08.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doit-on décaler la rentrée scolaire, le temps que le ministère de l’Education nationale affine le protocole ? Les différentes entités du corps enseignant attendent en effet des ordres clairs et précis. Dans un entretien à Paris Match, le président Emmanuel Macron a affirmé que &quot;les Français ont une anxiété légitime, liée au virus, que l’on doit accepter&quot;. Il a aussi souligné &quot;qu’on ne peut pas mettre le pays à l’arrêt, parce que les dommages collatéraux d’un confinement sont considérables&quot;. On en parle avec: Guislaine David, co-secrétaire générale du syndicat d’enseignants SNUIPP-FSU. Véronique Fèvre, journaliste éducation à BFMTV. Le Pr Élise Launay, pédiatre et infectiologue au CHU de Nantes (Loire-Atlantique). Le Pr Jean-Michel Constantin, chef du service anesthésie-réanimation à l’Hôpital de la Pitié-Salpêtrière à Paris. Et Cédric Faiche, correspondant de BFMTV à New York (États-Unis). - BFM Story, du mercredi 19 août 2020, présenté par Alain Marschall, sur BFMTV.   &lt;br /&gt;À partir de 17h, Olivier Truchot, remplacé par Alain Marschall, prend les rênes de l’antenne pour faire place à l’analyse et aux débats autour des événements marquants de la journée. Chaque soir, &quot;BFM STORY&quot; reçoit des invités de tous horizons qui font l’actualité et qui interviennent à l’antenne pour l’expliquer.   &lt;br /&gt;BFMTV, 1ère chaîne d’information en continu de France, vous propose toute l’info en temps réel avec 18h d’antenne live par jour et plus de 1000 duplex par mois. Retrouvez BFMTV sur le canal 15 de la TNT et sur BFMTV.com.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Doit-on décaler la rentrée scolaire, le temps que le ministère de l’Education nationale affine le protocole ? Les différentes entités du corps enseignant attendent en effet des ordres clairs et précis. Dans un entretien à Paris Match, le président Emmanuel Macron a affirmé que &quot;les Français ont une anxiété légitime, liée au virus, que l’on doit accepter&quot;. Il a aussi souligné &quot;qu’on ne peut pas mettre le pays à l’arrêt, parce que les dommages collatéraux d’un confinement sont considérables&quot;. On en parle avec: Guislaine David, co-secrétaire générale du syndicat d’enseignants SNUIPP-FSU. Véronique Fèvre, journaliste éducation à BFMTV. Le Pr Élise Launay, pédiatre et infectiologue au CHU de Nantes (Loire-Atlantique). Le Pr Jean-Michel Constantin, chef du service anesthésie-réanimation à l’Hôpital de la Pitié-Salpêtrière à Paris. Et Cédric Faiche, correspondant de BFMTV à New York (États-Unis). - BFM Story, du mercredi 19 août 2020, présenté par Alain Marschall, sur BFMTV. À partir de 17h, Olivier Truchot, remplacé par Alain Marschall, prend les rênes de l’antenne pour faire place à l’analyse et aux débats autour des événements marquants de la journée. Chaque soir, &quot;BFM STORY&quot; reçoit des invités de tous horizons qui font l’actualité et qui interviennent à l’antenne pour l’expliquer. BFMTV, 1ère chaîne d’information en continu de France, vous propose toute l’info en temps réel avec 18h d’antenne live par jour et plus de 1000 duplex par mois. Retrouvez BFMTV sur le canal 15 de la TNT et sur BFMTV.com.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPbMF1VFS3YOh4g_2/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPbMF1VFS3YOh4g_2/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Indian Railway: अब IRCTC में OFS के जरिए अपना हिस्सा बेचेगी Modi सरकार ! वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/indian-railway-irctc-ofs-modi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Indian Railway: अब IRCTC में OFS के जरिए अपना हिस्सा बेचेगी Modi सरकार ! वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:05:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:05:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/indian-railway-irctc-ofs-modi</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/indian-railway-irctc-ofs-modi.html">&lt;p&gt;The government is looking to cut its stake in the Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation (IRCTC) via offer for sale, CNBC-Awaaz reported. The Department of Disinvestment has invited bids for the appointment of merchant bankers and selling brokers.    &lt;br /&gt;मोदी सरकार IRCTC में अपनी हिस्सेदारी बेचने जा रही है. बिजनस न्यूज चैनल CNBC आवाज ने सूत्रों के हवाले से बताया है कि IRCTC में OFS के जरिए हिस्सा बेचा जाएगा. इसके लिए  विनिवेश विभाग ने मर्चेंट बैंकर्स की नियुक्ति के लिए बोलियां मंगाई है. इसको लेकर प्री-बिड मीटिंग 3 सितंबर को होगी. सरकार की IRCTC में 80 फीसदी से ज्यादा हिस्सेदारी है.    &lt;br /&gt;#IndianRailway #IRCTC #ModiGovernment #OneindiaHindi&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The government is looking to cut its stake in the Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation (IRCTC) via offer for sale, CNBC-Awaaz reported. The Department of Disinvestment has invited bids for the appointment of merchant bankers and selling brokers. मोदी सरकार IRCTC में अपनी हिस्सेदारी बेचने जा रही है. बिजनस न्यूज चैनल CNBC आवाज ने सूत्रों के हवाले से बताया है कि IRCTC में OFS के जरिए हिस्सा बेचा जाएगा. इसके लिए विनिवेश विभाग ने मर्चेंट बैंकर्स की नियुक्ति के लिए बोलियां मंगाई है. इसको लेकर प्री-बिड मीटिंग 3 सितंबर को होगी. सरकार की IRCTC में 80 फीसदी से ज्यादा हिस्सेदारी है. #IndianRailway #IRCTC #ModiGovernment #OneindiaHindi</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPZjP1VIBSFnp6TVJ/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPZjP1VIBSFnp6TVJ/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Delight as GCSE results 2020 are unveiled in Sheffield</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/delight-as-gcse-results-2020-are-unveiled-in-sheffield.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Delight as GCSE results 2020 are unveiled in Sheffield" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:04:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:04:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/delight-as-gcse-results-2020-are-unveiled-in-sheffield</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/delight-as-gcse-results-2020-are-unveiled-in-sheffield.html">&lt;p&gt;Students across Sheffield got their GCSE results today, with grades now being based on those given to them by their teachers.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="school" />
  <summary type="html">Students across Sheffield got their GCSE results today, with grades now being based on those given to them by their teachers.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPgVI1VFfoAB0CwKf/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPgVI1VFfoAB0CwKf/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">BMW 3 Series GT ‘Shadow Edition’ India Launch</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/bmw-3-series-gt-shadow-edition-india-launch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="BMW 3 Series GT ‘Shadow Edition’ India Launch" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:02:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:02:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/bmw-3-series-gt-shadow-edition-india-launch</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/bmw-3-series-gt-shadow-edition-india-launch.html">&lt;p&gt;BMW has launched a limited version of their 3 Series GT in the Indian market, called the ‘Shadow Edition’. The new 3 Series Gran Turismo ‘Shadow Edition’ is based on the model’s 330i M Sport variant and is priced at Rs 42.50 lakh, ex-showroom (India).  &lt;br /&gt;The new ‘Shadow Edition’ comes with a number of blacked-out elements, giving it a much sporty and aggressive look. The limited edition model, however, continues to be powered by the same 248bhp producing 2.0-litre petrol engine, mated to an eight-speed automatic transmission. Watch the video to know more details of the new 3 Series GT Shadow Edition.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="auto" />
  <summary type="html">BMW has launched a limited version of their 3 Series GT in the Indian market, called the ‘Shadow Edition’. The new 3 Series Gran Turismo ‘Shadow Edition’ is based on the model’s 330i M Sport variant and is priced at Rs 42.50 lakh, ex-showroom (India). The new ‘Shadow Edition’ comes with a number of blacked-out elements, giving it a much sporty and aggressive look. The limited edition model, however, continues to be powered by the same 248bhp producing 2.0-litre petrol engine, mated to an eight-speed automatic transmission. Watch the video to know more details of the new 3 Series GT Shadow Edition.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPdu61VHpBcKa5rV7/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPdu61VHpBcKa5rV7/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Two Men Indicted in Killing of Run-DMC’s Jam Master Jay RS News 8 18 20</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/two-men-indicted-in-killing-of-run-dmc-s-jam-master-jay-rs-news-8-18-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Two Men Indicted in Killing of Run-DMC’s Jam Master Jay RS News 8 18 20" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:01:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:01:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/two-men-indicted-in-killing-of-run-dmc-s-jam-master-jay-rs-news-8-18-2</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/two-men-indicted-in-killing-of-run-dmc-s-jam-master-jay-rs-news-8-18-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Federal prosecutors indicted two men in connection with the 2002 killing of Run-DMC’s Jam Master Jay.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="music" />
  <summary type="html">Federal prosecutors indicted two men in connection with the 2002 killing of Run-DMC’s Jam Master Jay.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPRT51VFTLw64gR19/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPRT51VFTLw64gR19/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">The Best Jose Rizal Quotes</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/the-best-jose-rizal-quotes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Best Jose Rizal Quotes" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:01:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:01:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/the-best-jose-rizal-quotes</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/the-best-jose-rizal-quotes.html">&lt;p&gt;Look back at the national hero’s most memorable quotes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Best Jose Rizal Quotes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;The Best Jose Rizal Quotes&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;The Best Jose Rizal Quotes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">Look back at the national hero’s most memorable quotes.The Best Jose Rizal Quotes The Best Jose Rizal Quotes The Best Jose Rizal Quotes</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQS881VHwltlr8FsS/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQS881VHwltlr8FsS/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Rahul tells government to listen to #students ke ‘Mann ki Baat’</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/rahul-tells-government-to-listen-to-students-ke-mann-ki-baat.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rahul tells government to listen to #students ke ‘Mann ki Baat’" />
  <published>2020-08-28T17:00:19+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T17:00:19+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/rahul-tells-government-to-listen-to-students-ke-mann-ki-baat</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/rahul-tells-government-to-listen-to-students-ke-mann-ki-baat.html">&lt;p&gt;Launching a sarcastic spin on Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s monthly address to the nation, Congress leader Rahul Gandhi urged the Central government to hear &quot;students ke mann ki baat&quot;.Rahul Gandhi demanded the government to postpone the JEE and the NEET - common entrance exams for admission to IITs and medical courses - in view of the coronavirus pandemic.  &lt;br /&gt;#Mannkibaat #RahulGandhi #CentralGovernment #JEE #NEET #Coronavirus #COVID19 #Pandemic&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Launching a sarcastic spin on Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s monthly address to the nation, Congress leader Rahul Gandhi urged the Central government to hear &quot;students ke mann ki baat&quot;.Rahul Gandhi demanded the government to postpone the JEE and the NEET - common entrance exams for admission to IITs and medical courses - in view of the coronavirus pandemic. #Mannkibaat #RahulGandhi #CentralGovernment #JEE #NEET #Coronavirus #COVID19 #Pandemic</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPzdk1VGf2YTdKHID/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPzdk1VGf2YTdKHID/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">États-Unis : Kellyanne Conway, proche conseillère de Donald Trump, démissionne</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/tats-unis-kellyanne-conway-proche-conseill-re-de-donald-trump-d-missio.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="États-Unis : Kellyanne Conway, proche conseillère de Donald Trump, démissionne" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:58:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:58:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/tats-unis-kellyanne-conway-proche-conseill-re-de-donald-trump-d-missio</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/tats-unis-kellyanne-conway-proche-conseill-re-de-donald-trump-d-missio.html">&lt;p&gt;Coup de tonnerre sur la Maison-Blanche. Kellyanne Conway, une proche conseillère du président Donald Trump, a annoncé dimanche 23 août 2020 qu’elle démissionnait pour se consacrer à sa famille. Elle a indiqué que leurs quatre enfants allaient commencer leur année académique à distance. « Comme des millions de parents à travers le pays le savent, les enfants qui font l’école à la maison requièrent un niveau d’attention et de vigilance qui est aussi inhabituel que cette période que nous vivons  », a-t-elle encore fait valoir. Dans un communiqué, Kellyanne Conway a précisé qu’elle quitterait la Maison-Blanche « à la fin du mois  ».  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Coup de tonnerre sur la Maison-Blanche. Kellyanne Conway, une proche conseillère du président Donald Trump, a annoncé dimanche 23 août 2020 qu’elle démissionnait pour se consacrer à sa famille. Elle a indiqué que leurs quatre enfants allaient commencer leur année académique à distance. « Comme des millions de parents à travers le pays le savent, les enfants qui font l’école à la maison requièrent un niveau d’attention et de vigilance qui est aussi inhabituel que cette période que nous vivons  », a-t-elle encore fait valoir. Dans un communiqué, Kellyanne Conway a précisé qu’elle quitterait la Maison-Blanche « à la fin du mois  ».</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ3eB1VGxyQLr5WSi/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ3eB1VGxyQLr5WSi/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Santan Saptami 2020: संतान सप्तमी पूजा मंत्र संतान गोपाल मंत्र Santan Saptami Mantra Boldsky</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/santan-saptami-2020-santan-saptami-mantra-boldsky.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Santan Saptami 2020: संतान सप्तमी पूजा मंत्र संतान गोपाल मंत्र Santan Saptami Mantra Boldsky" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:55:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:55:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/santan-saptami-2020-santan-saptami-mantra-boldsky</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/santan-saptami-2020-santan-saptami-mantra-boldsky.html">&lt;p&gt;Santan Saptami 2020 Puja: According to Hindi Panchang, Saptami Tithi of Shukla Paksha of Bhadrapada month is observed as fasting of Saptan Saptami. This year, Saptami Saptami is on 24th - 25th August. On this day, Lord Shiva and Goddess Gauri are worshiped by the law. He is pleased and blesses the devotees to have children, protect it and progress and skill. Know Santan Saptami Mantra or Santan Gopal Mantra.  &lt;br /&gt;Santan Saptami 2020 Puja: हिंदी पंचांग के अनुसार, भाद्रपद मास के शुक्ल पक्ष की सप्तमी ति​थि को संतान सप्तमी का व्रत किया जाता है। इस वर्ष संतान सप्तमी आज 24-25 अगस्त को है। आज के दिन भगवान शिव और माता गौरी की विधि विधान से पूजा की जाती है। वे प्रसन्न होकर भक्तों को संतान प्राप्ति, उसकी रक्षा और उन्नति व कुशलता का आशीर्वाद देते हैं। वीडियो में जानते हैं कि संतान सप्तमी पूजा मंत्र या संतान गोपाल मंत्र ।  &lt;br /&gt;#SantanSaptami2020 #SantanSaptamiMantra #SantanGopalMantra&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">Santan Saptami 2020 Puja: According to Hindi Panchang, Saptami Tithi of Shukla Paksha of Bhadrapada month is observed as fasting of Saptan Saptami. This year, Saptami Saptami is on 24th - 25th August. On this day, Lord Shiva and Goddess Gauri are worshiped by the law. He is pleased and blesses the devotees to have children, protect it and progress and skill. Know Santan Saptami Mantra or Santan Gopal Mantra. Santan Saptami 2020 Puja: हिंदी पंचांग के अनुसार, भाद्रपद मास के शुक्ल पक्ष की सप्तमी ति​थि को संतान सप्तमी का व्रत किया जाता है। इस वर्ष संतान सप्तमी आज 24-25 अगस्त को है। आज के दिन भगवान शिव और माता गौरी की विधि विधान से पूजा की जाती है। वे प्रसन्न होकर भक्तों को संतान प्राप्ति, उसकी रक्षा और उन्नति व कुशलता का आशीर्वाद देते हैं। वीडियो में जानते हैं कि संतान सप्तमी पूजा मंत्र या संतान गोपाल मंत्र । #SantanSaptami2020 #SantanSaptamiMantra #SantanGopalMantra</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4rQ1VHv6auyaMbW/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4rQ1VHv6auyaMbW/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Drone footage shows how old Sunderland fire station site has been cleared to make way for housing</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/drone-footage-shows-how-old-sunderland-fire-station-site-has-been-clea.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Drone footage shows how old Sunderland fire station site has been cleared to make way for housing" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:55:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:55:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/drone-footage-shows-how-old-sunderland-fire-station-site-has-been-clea</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/drone-footage-shows-how-old-sunderland-fire-station-site-has-been-clea.html">&lt;p&gt;A landmark fire station which served the Sunderland community from its launch during the Second World War is no more after a demolition crew moved in to clear the Fulwell site.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">A landmark fire station which served the Sunderland community from its launch during the Second World War is no more after a demolition crew moved in to clear the Fulwell site.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPYxN1VFxruEaQC-5/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPYxN1VFxruEaQC-5/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">44,1°C à Paris : voici à quoi pourrait ressembler la canicule en France en 2050</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/44-1-c-paris-voici-quoi-pourrait-ressembler-la-canicule-en-france-en-2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="44,1°C à Paris : voici à quoi pourrait ressembler la canicule en France en 2050" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:54:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:54:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/44-1-c-paris-voici-quoi-pourrait-ressembler-la-canicule-en-france-en-2</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/44-1-c-paris-voici-quoi-pourrait-ressembler-la-canicule-en-france-en-2.html">&lt;p&gt;Météo-France a diffusé une carte montrant à quoi pourraient ressembler les températures estivales dans 30 ans.  &lt;br /&gt;Les résultats des calculs sont des plus inquiétants…  &lt;br /&gt;Les températures affichées sont préoccupantes : 32,7 °C à Brest, 42,7 à Bordeaux, ou encore 44,1 °C à Paris.  &lt;br /&gt;Cette carte présente  les températures possibles d’une seule journée type en France, lors de la canicule en 2050.   &lt;br /&gt;Les températures devraient être de 1,2 à 1,5°C plus élevées que celles que la France connaît avec la canicule.  &lt;br /&gt;Météo-France a utilisé les données de la canicule de 2019, l’une des plus intense en France, avec un record de 46°C.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Météo-France a diffusé une carte montrant à quoi pourraient ressembler les températures estivales dans 30 ans. Les résultats des calculs sont des plus inquiétants… Les températures affichées sont préoccupantes : 32,7 °C à Brest, 42,7 à Bordeaux, ou encore 44,1 °C à Paris. Cette carte présente les températures possibles d’une seule journée type en France, lors de la canicule en 2050.  Les températures devraient être de 1,2 à 1,5°C plus élevées que celles que la France connaît avec la canicule. Météo-France a utilisé les données de la canicule de 2019, l’une des plus intense en France, avec un record de 46°C.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPRH31VHyoIqoYqyJ/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPRH31VHyoIqoYqyJ/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Rohit Sharma, Vinesh Phogat, Manika Batra, Mariyappan nominated for Khel Ratna 2020 Oneindia Sports</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/rohit-sharma-vinesh-phogat-manika-batra-mariyappan-nominated-for-khel.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rohit Sharma, Vinesh Phogat, Manika Batra, Mariyappan nominated for Khel Ratna 2020 Oneindia Sports" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:49:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:49:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/rohit-sharma-vinesh-phogat-manika-batra-mariyappan-nominated-for-khel</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/rohit-sharma-vinesh-phogat-manika-batra-mariyappan-nominated-for-khel.html">&lt;p&gt;Cricketer Rohit Sharma, wrestler Vinesh Phogat, table tennis player Manika Batra and Paralympic gold-winning high jumper Mariyappan Thangavelu were on Tuesday picked for this year’s Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna award by the sports ministry’s selection committee. This is the second time since 2016 that four athletes have been finalised for the country’s highest sporting honour. The committee, which includes of Virender Sehwag and former hockey captain Sardar Singh, met at the Sports Authority of India headquarters in Delhi.    &lt;br /&gt;आईपीएल से पहले रोहित शर्मा के फैंस के लिए खुशखबरी है. रोहित शर्मा को राजीव गांधी खेल रत्न अवॉर्ड के लिए नॉमिनेट किया गया है. नेशनल स्पोर्ट्स अवॉर्ड के लिए बनाई गई चयन समिति ने हिटमैन रोहित शर्मा के नाम की सिफारिश खेल सम्मान के लिए किया है. अब अगर रोहित शर्मा को यखेल रत्न से नवाजा जाता है. तो वो ये सम्मान पाने वाले देश के चौथे क्रिकेटर बन जाएंगे. आपको बता दें, खेल रत्न भारत के किसी नागरिक को दिया जाने वाला सर्वोच्च खेल सम्मान है. खिलाड़ियों के उसके सर्वश्रेष्ठ प्रदर्शन के लिए ये अवॉर्ड से नवाजा जाता है.    &lt;br /&gt;#RohitSharma   #VineshPhogat    #ManikaBatra&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Cricketer Rohit Sharma, wrestler Vinesh Phogat, table tennis player Manika Batra and Paralympic gold-winning high jumper Mariyappan Thangavelu were on Tuesday picked for this year’s Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna award by the sports ministry’s selection committee. This is the second time since 2016 that four athletes have been finalised for the country’s highest sporting honour. The committee, which includes of Virender Sehwag and former hockey captain Sardar Singh, met at the Sports Authority of India headquarters in Delhi. आईपीएल से पहले रोहित शर्मा के फैंस के लिए खुशखबरी है. रोहित शर्मा को राजीव गांधी खेल रत्न अवॉर्ड के लिए नॉमिनेट किया गया है. नेशनल स्पोर्ट्स अवॉर्ड के लिए बनाई गई चयन समिति ने हिटमैन रोहित शर्मा के नाम की सिफारिश खेल सम्मान के लिए किया है. अब अगर रोहित शर्मा को यखेल रत्न से नवाजा जाता है. तो वो ये सम्मान पाने वाले देश के चौथे क्रिकेटर बन जाएंगे. आपको बता दें, खेल रत्न भारत के किसी नागरिक को दिया जाने वाला सर्वोच्च खेल सम्मान है. खिलाड़ियों के उसके सर्वश्रेष्ठ प्रदर्शन के लिए ये अवॉर्ड से नवाजा जाता है. #RohitSharma #VineshPhogat #ManikaBatra</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPSil1VF1PgKNqz8d/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPSil1VF1PgKNqz8d/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Indonesia’s Mount Sinabung shoots ash 1,000 feet into the air</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/indonesia-s-mount-sinabung-shoots-ash-1-000-feet-into-the-air.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Indonesia’s Mount Sinabung shoots ash 1,000 feet into the air" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:47:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:47:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/indonesia-s-mount-sinabung-shoots-ash-1-000-feet-into-the-air</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/indonesia-s-mount-sinabung-shoots-ash-1-000-feet-into-the-air.html">&lt;p&gt;Authorities in Indonesia are closely monitoring Mount Sinabung on Sumatra after the volcano shot smoke and ash more than 1,000 metres into the air this morning (August 23rd).  &lt;br /&gt;Villagers were advised to stay 5 kilometres (3.1 miles) from the crater and should be aware of the danger of lava, Indonesia’s Volcanology and Geological Hazard Mitigation Center said.  &lt;br /&gt;Lava and other volcanic material spewed from Mount Sinabung in May 2016 killing seven people.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Authorities in Indonesia are closely monitoring Mount Sinabung on Sumatra after the volcano shot smoke and ash more than 1,000 metres into the air this morning (August 23rd). Villagers were advised to stay 5 kilometres (3.1 miles) from the crater and should be aware of the danger of lava, Indonesia’s Volcanology and Geological Hazard Mitigation Center said. Lava and other volcanic material spewed from Mount Sinabung in May 2016 killing seven people.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPy6Y1VGYyof6di2W/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPy6Y1VGYyof6di2W/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Wonder Woman 1984 - Bande Annonce#2 (VOST) avec Gal Gadot, Chris Pine</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/wonder-woman-1984-bande-annonce-2-vost-avec-gal-gadot-chris-pine.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wonder Woman 1984 - Bande Annonce#2 (VOST) avec Gal Gadot, Chris Pine" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:46:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:46:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/wonder-woman-1984-bande-annonce-2-vost-avec-gal-gadot-chris-pine</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/wonder-woman-1984-bande-annonce-2-vost-avec-gal-gadot-chris-pine.html">&lt;p&gt;Une nouvelle ère commence avec Wonder Woman. Wonder Woman 1984, bientôt au cinéma. Après la Première guerre mondiale, direction les années 80 ! Cette fois, Wonder Woman doit affronter deux nouveaux ennemis, particulièrement redoutables : Max Lord et Cheetah Suite de WONDER WOMAN, qui avait généré 822 millions de dollars de recettes mondiales en 2017, WONDER WOMAN 1984 est de nouveau signé Patty Jenkins et interprété par Gal Gadot dans le rôle-titre. Le film réunit Chris Pine sous les traits de Steve Trevor, Kristen Wiig dans le rôle de Cheetah, Pedro Pascal dans celui de Max Lord, Robin Wright dans celui d’Antiope et Connie Nielsen dans celui d’Hippolyta.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="shortfilms" />
  <summary type="html">Une nouvelle ère commence avec Wonder Woman. Wonder Woman 1984, bientôt au cinéma. Après la Première guerre mondiale, direction les années 80 ! Cette fois, Wonder Woman doit affronter deux nouveaux ennemis, particulièrement redoutables : Max Lord et Cheetah Suite de WONDER WOMAN, qui avait généré 822 millions de dollars de recettes mondiales en 2017, WONDER WOMAN 1984 est de nouveau signé Patty Jenkins et interprété par Gal Gadot dans le rôle-titre. Le film réunit Chris Pine sous les traits de Steve Trevor, Kristen Wiig dans le rôle de Cheetah, Pedro Pascal dans celui de Max Lord, Robin Wright dans celui d’Antiope et Connie Nielsen dans celui d’Hippolyta.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPyLn1VGa1pC520J5/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPyLn1VGa1pC520J5/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Hrithik Roshan And Ex-Wife Sussanne Bid Goodbye To Lord Ganesha</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/hrithik-roshan-and-ex-wife-sussanne-bid-goodbye-to-lord-ganesha.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hrithik Roshan And Ex-Wife Sussanne Bid Goodbye To Lord Ganesha" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:44:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:44:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/hrithik-roshan-and-ex-wife-sussanne-bid-goodbye-to-lord-ganesha</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/hrithik-roshan-and-ex-wife-sussanne-bid-goodbye-to-lord-ganesha.html">&lt;p&gt;Hrithik Roshan, along with his ex-wife Sussanne and other family members bid goodbye to Lord Ganesha at home. #HrithikRoshan #GanpatiVisarjan #SussanneKhan  &lt;br /&gt;Log On To Our Official Website :   &lt;br /&gt;For More Such News &amp;amp; Gossips Subscribe now! :   &lt;br /&gt;Lehren On Podcast:   &lt;br /&gt;Download The ‘Lehren App’:   &lt;br /&gt;Facebook :   &lt;br /&gt;Twitter:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="people" />
  <summary type="html">Hrithik Roshan, along with his ex-wife Sussanne and other family members bid goodbye to Lord Ganesha at home. #HrithikRoshan #GanpatiVisarjan #SussanneKhan Log On To Our Official Website : For More Such News &amp;amp; Gossips Subscribe now! : Lehren On Podcast: Download The ‘Lehren App’: Facebook : Twitter:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ6C01VHD0bwNLi8A/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ6C01VHD0bwNLi8A/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Dhoniக்கு Farewell match அமைக்க BCCI திட்டம் Oneindia Tamil</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/dhoni-farewell-match-bcci-oneindia-tamil.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dhoniக்கு Farewell match அமைக்க BCCI திட்டம் Oneindia Tamil" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:37:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:37:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/dhoni-farewell-match-bcci-oneindia-tamil</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/dhoni-farewell-match-bcci-oneindia-tamil.html">&lt;p&gt;#dhoni  &lt;br /&gt;#dhoniretires  &lt;br /&gt;Dhoni’s Farewell match planned by BCCI, says sources  &lt;br /&gt;தோனிக்கு வழியனுப்பும் போட்டியை அமைக்க பிசிசிஐ முயற்சி செய்து வருவதாக தகவல்கள் வருகிறது   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">#dhoni #dhoniretires Dhoni’s Farewell match planned by BCCI, says sources தோனிக்கு வழியனுப்பும் போட்டியை அமைக்க பிசிசிஐ முயற்சி செய்து வருவதாக தகவல்கள் வருகிறது</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPYxr1VFI_waIaR9L/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPYxr1VFI_waIaR9L/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out! Episode 7 English sub Uzaki-chan wa Asobitai! Episode 7</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/uzaki-chan-wants-to-hang-out-episode-7-english-sub-uzaki-chan-wa-asobi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out! Episode 7 English sub Uzaki-chan wa Asobitai! Episode 7" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:36:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:36:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/uzaki-chan-wants-to-hang-out-episode-7-english-sub-uzaki-chan-wa-asobi</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/uzaki-chan-wants-to-hang-out-episode-7-english-sub-uzaki-chan-wa-asobi.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out! Episode 7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;English sub&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Uzaki-chan wa Asobitai! Episode 7  &lt;br /&gt;Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out! Episode 7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;English sub&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out episode 7  &lt;br /&gt;Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out,  &lt;br /&gt;Uzaki-chan wa Asobitai!,  &lt;br /&gt;Uzaki-chan Wants to Play!,  &lt;br /&gt;宇崎ちゃんは遊びたい！  &lt;br /&gt;Thanks for watching!  &lt;br /&gt;Follow for more episodes!  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="fun" />
  <summary type="html">Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out! Episode 7 English sub Uzaki-chan wa Asobitai! Episode 7 Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out! Episode 7 English sub Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out episode 7 Uzaki-chan Wants to Hang Out, Uzaki-chan wa Asobitai!, Uzaki-chan Wants to Play!, 宇崎ちゃんは遊びたい！ Thanks for watching! Follow for more episodes!</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPprS1VGVkJgHnzp7/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPprS1VGVkJgHnzp7/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Menkes Terawan Serahkan Bantuan Mobil Laboratorium PCR</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/menkes-terawan-serahkan-bantuan-mobil-laboratorium-pcr.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Menkes Terawan Serahkan Bantuan Mobil Laboratorium PCR" />
  <published>2020-08-28T16:33:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T16:33:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/menkes-terawan-serahkan-bantuan-mobil-laboratorium-pcr</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/menkes-terawan-serahkan-bantuan-mobil-laboratorium-pcr.html">&lt;p&gt;MANADO, KOMPAS.TV -  Menteri Kesehatan Ri Dokter Terawan Agus Putranto, menyerahkan bantuan sebuah mobil laboratorium Polymerase Chain Reaction atau Pcr.  Mobil Pcr ini diterima gubernur sulut olly dondokambey.   &lt;br /&gt;Penyerahan mobil Polymerase Chain Reaction atau Pcr Covid-19 dilakukan secara simbolis di halaman vvip Bandara Samratulangi saat Menkes Terawan tiba di Manado pada Selasa pagi, 25 Agustus 2020.   &lt;br /&gt;Mobil Pcr yang diterima Gubernur Olly Dondokambey ini, berstandar Who senilai 4,14 miliar rupiah , merupakan bantuan Pt Msm dan Pt. Ttn anak perusahaan Pt.Archi yang akan digunakan untuk mendeteksi Covid-19 di tengah masyarakat di 15 kabupaten kota di Sulawesi Utara secara mobile.   &lt;br /&gt;&quot;saya atas nama rakyat sulawesi utara tentu merasa bersyukur atas bantuan mobil laboratorium pcr ini. bantuan ini sangat berarti bagi kami sebagai pemerintah daerah ditengah upaya menekan penyebaran virus korona, &quot; ujar  Olly Dondokambey Gubernur Sulawesi Utara.   &lt;br /&gt;Nantinya  mobil Pcr Dapat mengerjakan  96 sampel dalam sekali proses dan memiliki bio safety cabinet untuk pengerjaan sampel, serta fasilitas ruangan bertekanan negatif.   &lt;br /&gt;#kompastvmanado #menkesterawan #bantuan #mobillabpcr   &lt;br /&gt;ALDY PASCOAL / KOMPAS TV MANADO SULAWESI UTARA   &lt;br /&gt;Saksikan Siaran Kompastv :   &lt;br /&gt;Chanel 48 UHF   &lt;br /&gt;Fb : Kompastv Manado   &lt;br /&gt;Yt : Kompastv Manado   &lt;br /&gt;Alamat Studio Kompastv Manado   &lt;br /&gt;Jl.Anugerah No.08 Kelurahan Winangun   &lt;br /&gt;Kecamatan Malalayang, Kota Manado   &lt;br /&gt;Sulawesi Utara   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">MANADO, KOMPAS.TV - Menteri Kesehatan Ri Dokter Terawan Agus Putranto, menyerahkan bantuan sebuah mobil laboratorium Polymerase Chain Reaction atau Pcr. Mobil Pcr ini diterima gubernur sulut olly dondokambey. Penyerahan mobil Polymerase Chain Reaction atau Pcr Covid-19 dilakukan secara simbolis di halaman vvip Bandara Samratulangi saat Menkes Terawan tiba di Manado pada Selasa pagi, 25 Agustus 2020. Mobil Pcr yang diterima Gubernur Olly Dondokambey ini, berstandar Who senilai 4,14 miliar rupiah , merupakan bantuan Pt Msm dan Pt. Ttn anak perusahaan Pt.Archi yang akan digunakan untuk mendeteksi Covid-19 di tengah masyarakat di 15 kabupaten kota di Sulawesi Utara secara mobile. &quot;saya atas nama rakyat sulawesi utara tentu merasa bersyukur atas bantuan mobil laboratorium pcr ini. bantuan ini sangat berarti bagi kami sebagai pemerintah daerah ditengah upaya menekan penyebaran virus korona, &quot; ujar Olly Dondokambey Gubernur Sulawesi Utara. Nantinya mobil Pcr Dapat mengerjakan 96 sampel dalam sekali proses dan memiliki bio safety cabinet untuk pengerjaan sampel, serta fasilitas ruangan bertekanan negatif. #kompastvmanado #menkesterawan #bantuan #mobillabpcr ALDY PASCOAL / KOMPAS TV MANADO SULAWESI UTARA Saksikan Siaran Kompastv : Chanel 48 UHF Fb : Kompastv Manado Yt : Kompastv Manado Alamat Studio Kompastv Manado Jl.Anugerah No.08 Kelurahan Winangun Kecamatan Malalayang, Kota Manado Sulawesi Utara</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQSDw1VHwCBhDxZ5D/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQSDw1VHwCBhDxZ5D/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 </feed>