<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
<updated>2020-08-30T03:24:02+03:00</updated>
<id>https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml</id>
<title type="html">Adowsom</title>
<subtitle>Duct Tape is like the force. There's a dark side and a light side, and it holds the universe together.</subtitle>
<author>
 <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
 <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
 <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
</author>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Jateng Valley Diklaim Jadi Tempat Wisata Terbesar Se-Asia Tenggara</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/jateng-valley-diklaim-jadi-tempat-wisata-terbesar-se-asia-tenggara.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jateng Valley Diklaim Jadi Tempat Wisata Terbesar Se-Asia Tenggara" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:19:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:19:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/jateng-valley-diklaim-jadi-tempat-wisata-terbesar-se-asia-tenggara</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/jateng-valley-diklaim-jadi-tempat-wisata-terbesar-se-asia-tenggara.html">&lt;p&gt;SEMARANG, KOMPAS.TV - Ground Breaking pembangunan obyek wisata Jateng Valley di hutan Penggaron, Kabupaten Semarang,  telah dilakukan oleh Gubernur Jawa Tengah, Ganjar Pranowo. Ground Breaking dilakukan bertepatan dengan HUT Jateng ke 70 tahun pada tanggal 15 Agustus 2020 lalu.   &lt;br /&gt;Nantinya, Jateng Valley ini diklaim sebagai tempat wisata terbesar se-Asia Tenggara.   &lt;br /&gt;Pembangunan objek wisata Jateng Valley ini sebenarnya sudah dirintis sejak 2010. Objek wisata yang sebelumnya akan diberi nama Jateng Park ini menempati areal yang luasnya mencapai 370 hektar.   &lt;br /&gt;Menurut pihak PT. Taman Wisata Jateng, yang merupakan pengembang objek wisata Jateng Valley, awalnya pembangunan Jateng Valley ini akan menghabiskan anggaran 2 triliun rupiah, namun jumlah anggaran ini diperkirakan akan membengkak hingga berkali lipat.   &lt;br /&gt;Nantinya obyek wisata Jateng Valley akan dilengkapi dengan fasilitas seperti resort, hotel, taman bermain, taman edukasi, mice, outbond, science centre, serta destinasi pendukung lainnya. Konsep wisata ini tak hanya menawarkan hiburan, namun juga edukasi.   &lt;br /&gt;Ganjar berharap, pembangunan Jateng Valley akan memberi dampak yang besar bagi masyarakat Jawa Tengah. Dengan adanya destinasi wisata baru, maka wisatawan akan banyak berdatangan dan ekonomi akan menggeliat. Selian itu, Ganjar Pranowo juga berpesan agar keasrian lingkungan hutan Penggaron tetap terjaga.   &lt;br /&gt;#JatengValley #AsiaTenggara #GanjarPranowo   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">SEMARANG, KOMPAS.TV - Ground Breaking pembangunan obyek wisata Jateng Valley di hutan Penggaron, Kabupaten Semarang, telah dilakukan oleh Gubernur Jawa Tengah, Ganjar Pranowo. Ground Breaking dilakukan bertepatan dengan HUT Jateng ke 70 tahun pada tanggal 15 Agustus 2020 lalu. Nantinya, Jateng Valley ini diklaim sebagai tempat wisata terbesar se-Asia Tenggara. Pembangunan objek wisata Jateng Valley ini sebenarnya sudah dirintis sejak 2010. Objek wisata yang sebelumnya akan diberi nama Jateng Park ini menempati areal yang luasnya mencapai 370 hektar. Menurut pihak PT. Taman Wisata Jateng, yang merupakan pengembang objek wisata Jateng Valley, awalnya pembangunan Jateng Valley ini akan menghabiskan anggaran 2 triliun rupiah, namun jumlah anggaran ini diperkirakan akan membengkak hingga berkali lipat. Nantinya obyek wisata Jateng Valley akan dilengkapi dengan fasilitas seperti resort, hotel, taman bermain, taman edukasi, mice, outbond, science centre, serta destinasi pendukung lainnya. Konsep wisata ini tak hanya menawarkan hiburan, namun juga edukasi. Ganjar berharap, pembangunan Jateng Valley akan memberi dampak yang besar bagi masyarakat Jawa Tengah. Dengan adanya destinasi wisata baru, maka wisatawan akan banyak berdatangan dan ekonomi akan menggeliat. Selian itu, Ganjar Pranowo juga berpesan agar keasrian lingkungan hutan Penggaron tetap terjaga. #JatengValley #AsiaTenggara #GanjarPranowo</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQHoj1VHVhbFO3Gxy/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQHoj1VHVhbFO3Gxy/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Tour de France 2020 : la Grande Boucle commence demain</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/tour-de-france-2020-la-grande-boucle-commence-demain.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tour de France 2020 : la Grande Boucle commence demain" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:15:10+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:15:10+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/tour-de-france-2020-la-grande-boucle-commence-demain</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/tour-de-france-2020-la-grande-boucle-commence-demain.html">&lt;p&gt;Le Tour de France doit démarrer samedi 29 août pour trois semaines de courses.  &lt;br /&gt;Retrouver toutes les infos sur la vidéo sur :&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Le Tour de France doit démarrer samedi 29 août pour trois semaines de courses. Retrouver toutes les infos sur la vidéo sur :</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQZGE1VIDIBvloYWx/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQZGE1VIDIBvloYWx/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Équipe de France : La liste de Didier Deschamps pour affronter la Suède et la Croatie</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/quipe-de-france-la-liste-de-didier-deschamps-pour-affronter-la-su-de-e.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Équipe de France : La liste de Didier Deschamps pour affronter la Suède et la Croatie" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:13:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:13:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/quipe-de-france-la-liste-de-didier-deschamps-pour-affronter-la-su-de-e</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/quipe-de-france-la-liste-de-didier-deschamps-pour-affronter-la-su-de-e.html">&lt;p&gt;Le sélectionneur des Bleus, Didier Deschamps, a dévoilé la liste des joueurs retenus pour disputer les matchs de Ligue des nations  &lt;br /&gt;contre la Suède (5 septembre 2020) et la Croatie (8 septembre 2020), qui se dérouleront à huis clos.  &lt;br /&gt;Sans plus attendre, découvrez la liste tant attendue :   &lt;br /&gt;Gardiens :   &lt;br /&gt;Hugo Lloris (Tottenham),   &lt;br /&gt;Mike Maignan (Lille),   &lt;br /&gt;Steve Mandanda (Marseille).  &lt;br /&gt;Défenseurs :  &lt;br /&gt;Lucas Digne (Everton),   &lt;br /&gt;Léo Dubois (Lyon),   &lt;br /&gt;Lucas Hernandez (Bayern),   &lt;br /&gt;Presnel Kimpembé (PSG),   &lt;br /&gt;Clément Lenglet (FC Barcelone),   &lt;br /&gt;Ferland Mendy (Real Madrid),   &lt;br /&gt;Dayot Upamecano (RB Leipzig),  &lt;br /&gt;Raphaël Varane (Real Madrid).  &lt;br /&gt;Milieux :   &lt;br /&gt;Eduardo Camavinga (Rennes),   &lt;br /&gt;N’Golo Kanté (Chelsea),   &lt;br /&gt;Steven Nzonzi (Rennes),   &lt;br /&gt;Adrien Rabiot (Juventus),   &lt;br /&gt;Moussa Sissoko (Tottenham).  &lt;br /&gt;Attaquants :   &lt;br /&gt;Houssem Aouar (Lyon),   &lt;br /&gt;Wissam Ben Yedder (Monaco),   &lt;br /&gt;Olivier Giroud (Chelsea),   &lt;br /&gt;Antoine Griezmann (FC Barcelone),   &lt;br /&gt;Jonathan Ikoné (Lille),   &lt;br /&gt;Anthony Martial (Manchester United),   &lt;br /&gt;Kylian Mbappé (PSG).  &lt;br /&gt;3 joueurs ont donc été appelés pour leur première sélection :  Upamecano, Aouar et Camavinga.   &lt;br /&gt;Vous noterez l’absence de Blaise Matuidi et de Paul Pogba.   &lt;br /&gt;Concernant ce dernier, Deschamps s’est exprimé :   &lt;br /&gt;Malheureusement il a effectué hier (mercredi) un test qui s’est révélé positif ce matin, je l’ai remplacé par Camavinga.  &lt;br /&gt;Le retour d’Adrien Rabiot, après plus de 2 ans d’absence avec les Bleus est LA grande surprise.   &lt;br /&gt;Il avait refusé d’être réserviste avec l’Équipe de France pour le Mondial 2018.  &lt;br /&gt;Les 23 joueurs se rendront lundi au centre d’entraînement de Clairefontaine.   &lt;br /&gt;En raison de la crise sanitaire (à l’origine du report de l’Euro 2020), les Bleus n’avaient plus joué depuis près de 10 mois.  &lt;br /&gt;Leur dernière rencontre internationale remonte au 17 novembre 2019 (victoire 2-0 face à l’Albanie).&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Le sélectionneur des Bleus, Didier Deschamps, a dévoilé la liste des joueurs retenus pour disputer les matchs de Ligue des nations contre la Suède (5 septembre 2020) et la Croatie (8 septembre 2020), qui se dérouleront à huis clos. Sans plus attendre, découvrez la liste tant attendue : Gardiens : Hugo Lloris (Tottenham), Mike Maignan (Lille), Steve Mandanda (Marseille). Défenseurs : Lucas Digne (Everton), Léo Dubois (Lyon), Lucas Hernandez (Bayern), Presnel Kimpembé (PSG), Clément Lenglet (FC Barcelone), Ferland Mendy (Real Madrid), Dayot Upamecano (RB Leipzig), Raphaël Varane (Real Madrid). Milieux :  Eduardo Camavinga (Rennes), N’Golo Kanté (Chelsea), Steven Nzonzi (Rennes), Adrien Rabiot (Juventus), Moussa Sissoko (Tottenham). Attaquants :  Houssem Aouar (Lyon), Wissam Ben Yedder (Monaco), Olivier Giroud (Chelsea), Antoine Griezmann (FC Barcelone), Jonathan Ikoné (Lille), Anthony Martial (Manchester United), Kylian Mbappé (PSG). 3 joueurs ont donc été appelés pour leur première sélection : Upamecano, Aouar et Camavinga. Vous noterez l’absence de Blaise Matuidi et de Paul Pogba. Concernant ce dernier, Deschamps s’est exprimé : Malheureusement il a effectué hier (mercredi) un test qui s’est révélé positif ce matin, je l’ai remplacé par Camavinga. Le retour d’Adrien Rabiot, après plus de 2 ans d’absence avec les Bleus est LA grande surprise. Il avait refusé d’être réserviste avec l’Équipe de France pour le Mondial 2018. Les 23 joueurs se rendront lundi au centre d’entraînement de Clairefontaine. En raison de la crise sanitaire (à l’origine du report de l’Euro 2020), les Bleus n’avaient plus joué depuis près de 10 mois. Leur dernière rencontre internationale remonte au 17 novembre 2019 (victoire 2-0 face à l’Albanie).</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQTfx1VIJbpfHJ54b/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQTfx1VIJbpfHJ54b/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Did Saumya Tandon Quit Bhabhiji Ghar Par Hain For Bigg Boss 14?</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/did-saumya-tandon-quit-bhabhiji-ghar-par-hain-for-bigg-boss-14.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Did Saumya Tandon Quit Bhabhiji Ghar Par Hain For Bigg Boss 14?" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:12:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:12:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/did-saumya-tandon-quit-bhabhiji-ghar-par-hain-for-bigg-boss-14</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/did-saumya-tandon-quit-bhabhiji-ghar-par-hain-for-bigg-boss-14.html">&lt;p&gt;Recently Saumya Tandon from Bhabhiji Ghar Par Hain was in the news as it was reported that she left the show due to the global pandemic and will be replaced by Kanta Laga fame Shefali Jariwala. However, Shefali later denied the rumours but in the latest developments, Saumya has indeed quit the show. Reportedly, in an interview, Saumya confirmed her exit for Bhabhiji Ghar Par Hain as she wants to do much bigger projects where there is scope for growth as an artiste. However, there were some reports about her joining Bigg Boss 14 but she denied such rumours and said, &quot;I am not quitting because of Bigg Boss or coronavirus or pay cut or any other reason, these are all rumours and speculations. I just want to explore other challenging projects in future.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="people" />
  <summary type="html">Recently Saumya Tandon from Bhabhiji Ghar Par Hain was in the news as it was reported that she left the show due to the global pandemic and will be replaced by Kanta Laga fame Shefali Jariwala. However, Shefali later denied the rumours but in the latest developments, Saumya has indeed quit the show. Reportedly, in an interview, Saumya confirmed her exit for Bhabhiji Ghar Par Hain as she wants to do much bigger projects where there is scope for growth as an artiste. However, there were some reports about her joining Bigg Boss 14 but she denied such rumours and said, &quot;I am not quitting because of Bigg Boss or coronavirus or pay cut or any other reason, these are all rumours and speculations. I just want to explore other challenging projects in future.&quot;</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPmNv1VFunJ_jEo6i/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPmNv1VFunJ_jEo6i/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Des WC publiques transparentes installées au Japon pour une raison incroyable</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/des-wc-publiques-transparentes-installe-es-au-japon-pour-une-raison-in.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Des WC publiques transparentes installées au Japon pour une raison incroyable" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:11:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:11:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/des-wc-publiques-transparentes-installe-es-au-japon-pour-une-raison-in</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/des-wc-publiques-transparentes-installe-es-au-japon-pour-une-raison-in.html">&lt;p&gt;Ces toilettes publiques japonaises sont transparentes. Et la raison est assez logique… On vous explique tout.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="fun" />
  <summary type="html">Ces toilettes publiques japonaises sont transparentes. Et la raison est assez logique… On vous explique tout.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBDL1VHG5iCymqTI/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBDL1VHG5iCymqTI/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">UCAD : voici la décision du recteur sur l’ouverture des cours</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/ucad-voici-la-d-cision-du-recteur-sur-l-ouverture-des-cours.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="UCAD : voici la décision du recteur sur l’ouverture des cours" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:10:08+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:10:08+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/ucad-voici-la-d-cision-du-recteur-sur-l-ouverture-des-cours</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/ucad-voici-la-d-cision-du-recteur-sur-l-ouverture-des-cours.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;UCAD : voici la décision du recteur sur l’ouverture des cours&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;UCAD : voici la décision du recteur sur l’ouverture des cours&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;UCAD : voici la décision du recteur sur l'ouverture des cours&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">UCAD : voici la décision du recteur sur l’ouverture des cours UCAD : voici la décision du recteur sur l’ouverture des cours UCAD : voici la décision du recteur sur l'ouverture des cours</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQbjJ1VIKJmv0mah-/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQbjJ1VIKJmv0mah-/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Royaume-Uni : des salariés payés pour rester à la maison et enrayer l’épidémie</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/royaume-uni-des-salari-s-pay-s-pour-rester-la-maison-et-enrayer-l-pid.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Royaume-Uni : des salariés payés pour rester à la maison et enrayer l’épidémie" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:08:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:08:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/royaume-uni-des-salari-s-pay-s-pour-rester-la-maison-et-enrayer-l-pid</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/royaume-uni-des-salari-s-pay-s-pour-rester-la-maison-et-enrayer-l-pid.html">&lt;p&gt;Chacun des voisins européens a sa propre méthode pour inciter à casser la chaîne de transmission et inciter à se mettre en quarantaine. Les Britanniques misent sur les incitations financières.  &lt;br /&gt;Retrouver toutes les infos sur la vidéo sur :&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Chacun des voisins européens a sa propre méthode pour inciter à casser la chaîne de transmission et inciter à se mettre en quarantaine. Les Britanniques misent sur les incitations financières. Retrouver toutes les infos sur la vidéo sur :</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQZ0x1VICR8uyCycr/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQZ0x1VICR8uyCycr/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Emmanuel Macron : ce souvenir traumatisant à l’origine d’une mauvaise habitude lors de ses</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/emmanuel-macron-ce-souvenir-traumatisant-l-origine-d-une-mauvaise-habi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Emmanuel Macron : ce souvenir traumatisant à l’origine d’une mauvaise habitude lors de ses" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:07:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:07:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/emmanuel-macron-ce-souvenir-traumatisant-l-origine-d-une-mauvaise-habi</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/emmanuel-macron-ce-souvenir-traumatisant-l-origine-d-une-mauvaise-habi.html">&lt;p&gt;Emmanuel Macron : ce souvenir traumatisant à l’origine d’une mauvaise habitude lors de ses voyages.  &lt;br /&gt;Emmanuel Macron a eu une habitude bien   &lt;br /&gt;à lui lorsqu’il prend l’avion. .  &lt;br /&gt;En effet, le président ne boucle jamais sa ceinture   &lt;br /&gt;de sécurité lorsqu’il emprunte ce mode de déplacement. .  &lt;br /&gt;Pourtant, les consignes sont claires à ce sujet : c’est obligatoire.  &lt;br /&gt;Il a pris cette habitude depuis le dimanche 5 mai 2002. .  &lt;br /&gt;À cette date, Emmanuel Macron se trouve   &lt;br /&gt;au Nigeria, où il y effectue un stage   &lt;br /&gt;à l’Ambassade de France, pour l’ENA.  &lt;br /&gt;Seulement, un crash aérien a fait de nombreuses victimes. .  &lt;br /&gt;Le vol 4226 de la compagnie EAS a pris feu,   &lt;br /&gt;juste après le décollage, sur des immeubles et   &lt;br /&gt;une école de quartier ouvrier située au nord pays. .  &lt;br /&gt;Alors que des Français font partis des 150 victimes, il est dépêché sur place. .  &lt;br /&gt;Mais à la morgue, il a été bouleversé devant   &lt;br /&gt;les corps calcinés ou démembrés.  &lt;br /&gt;D’autres ont même été coupés en deux à cause de   &lt;br /&gt;la ceinture de sécurité qui devait pourtant les protéger. .  &lt;br /&gt;Choqué par les scènes qu’il a vu, il a pris la décision   &lt;br /&gt;de ne plus jamais attacher cette ceinture dans les avions&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Emmanuel Macron : ce souvenir traumatisant à l’origine d’une mauvaise habitude lors de ses voyages. Emmanuel Macron a eu une habitude bien à lui lorsqu’il prend l’avion. . En effet, le président ne boucle jamais sa ceinture de sécurité lorsqu’il emprunte ce mode de déplacement. . Pourtant, les consignes sont claires à ce sujet : c’est obligatoire. Il a pris cette habitude depuis le dimanche 5 mai 2002. . À cette date, Emmanuel Macron se trouve au Nigeria, où il y effectue un stage à l’Ambassade de France, pour l’ENA. Seulement, un crash aérien a fait de nombreuses victimes. . Le vol 4226 de la compagnie EAS a pris feu, juste après le décollage, sur des immeubles et une école de quartier ouvrier située au nord pays. . Alors que des Français font partis des 150 victimes, il est dépêché sur place. . Mais à la morgue, il a été bouleversé devant les corps calcinés ou démembrés. D’autres ont même été coupés en deux à cause de la ceinture de sécurité qui devait pourtant les protéger. . Choqué par les scènes qu’il a vu, il a pris la décision de ne plus jamais attacher cette ceinture dans les avions</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ2-O1VGvnnVEAFi5/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ2-O1VGvnnVEAFi5/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Bartomeu, dispuesto a dejar la presidencia del Barcelona para que Messi siga en el club</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/bartomeu-dispuesto-a-dejar-la-presidencia-del-barcelona-para-que-messi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bartomeu, dispuesto a dejar la presidencia del Barcelona para que Messi siga en el club" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:03:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:03:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/bartomeu-dispuesto-a-dejar-la-presidencia-del-barcelona-para-que-messi</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/bartomeu-dispuesto-a-dejar-la-presidencia-del-barcelona-para-que-messi.html">&lt;p&gt;El actual presidente blaugrana tendría pensando renunciar para que La Pulga no salga de la institución&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">El actual presidente blaugrana tendría pensando renunciar para que La Pulga no salga de la institución</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQUyg1VIEMS9DmiQv/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQUyg1VIEMS9DmiQv/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Alpes : le col du Galibier réservé aux cyclistes le temps d’une matinée</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/alpes-le-col-du-galibier-r-serv-aux-cyclistes-le-temps-d-une-matin-e.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Alpes : le col du Galibier réservé aux cyclistes le temps d’une matinée" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:03:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:03:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/alpes-le-col-du-galibier-r-serv-aux-cyclistes-le-temps-d-une-matin-e</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/alpes-le-col-du-galibier-r-serv-aux-cyclistes-le-temps-d-une-matin-e.html">&lt;p&gt;Les adeptes du Tour de France le connaissent bien. Le col du Galibier relie la Savoie et les Hautes-Alpes. Exceptionnellement, ce col mythique était uniquement réservé aux cyclistes jeudi 20 août.    &lt;br /&gt;Retrouver toutes les infos sur la vidéo sur :&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Les adeptes du Tour de France le connaissent bien. Le col du Galibier relie la Savoie et les Hautes-Alpes. Exceptionnellement, ce col mythique était uniquement réservé aux cyclistes jeudi 20 août.   Retrouver toutes les infos sur la vidéo sur :</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPp5V1VF_iZw1uDOw/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPp5V1VF_iZw1uDOw/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Not compulsory to record temperature readings</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/not-compulsory-to-record-temperature-readings.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Not compulsory to record temperature readings" />
  <published>2020-08-30T03:02:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T03:02:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/not-compulsory-to-record-temperature-readings</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/not-compulsory-to-record-temperature-readings.html">&lt;p&gt;Business owners have to check the body temperature of patrons but are not required to record the readings, instead only the names and phone numbers should be recorded in the book if the customer does not use the MySejahtera application.  &lt;br /&gt;Senior Minister Datuk Seri Ismail Sabri Yaakob said business premises that have been penalised by the authorities for not recording the body temperature readings can contact the particular authority that took action against them.  &lt;br /&gt;WATCH MORE:   &lt;br /&gt;SUBSCRIBE:   &lt;br /&gt;LIKE:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Business owners have to check the body temperature of patrons but are not required to record the readings, instead only the names and phone numbers should be recorded in the book if the customer does not use the MySejahtera application. Senior Minister Datuk Seri Ismail Sabri Yaakob said business premises that have been penalised by the authorities for not recording the body temperature readings can contact the particular authority that took action against them. WATCH MORE: SUBSCRIBE: LIKE:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQRwz1VHwvDBzARFY/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQRwz1VHwvDBzARFY/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Trump 2020 Senior Advisor says RNC, campaign will be ‘high energy’</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/trump-2020-senior-advisor-says-rnc-campaign-will-be-high-energy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trump 2020 Senior Advisor says RNC, campaign will be ‘high energy’" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:57:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:57:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/trump-2020-senior-advisor-says-rnc-campaign-will-be-high-energy</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/trump-2020-senior-advisor-says-rnc-campaign-will-be-high-energy.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trump 2020 Senior Advisor says RNC, campaign will be ‘high energy’&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Trump 2020 Senior Advisor says RNC, campaign will be ‘high energy’&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Trump 2020 Senior Advisor says RNC, campaign will be 'high energy'&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">Trump 2020 Senior Advisor says RNC, campaign will be ‘high energy’ Trump 2020 Senior Advisor says RNC, campaign will be ‘high energy’ Trump 2020 Senior Advisor says RNC, campaign will be 'high energy'</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPymk1VIWXbFCzFoh/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPymk1VIWXbFCzFoh/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">FOOTBALL : International : Bleus - Deschamps : ‘Aouar a plus de continuité dans ses performances’</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/football-international-bleus-deschamps-aouar-a-plus-de-continuit-dans.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="FOOTBALL : International : Bleus - Deschamps : ‘Aouar a plus de continuité dans ses performances’" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:56:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:56:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/football-international-bleus-deschamps-aouar-a-plus-de-continuit-dans</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/football-international-bleus-deschamps-aouar-a-plus-de-continuit-dans.html">&lt;p&gt;Didier Deschamps a décidé d’appeler pour la première fois avec les A Houssem Aouar. Le sélectionneur loue son évolution, sa technique et sa polyvalence offensive.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Didier Deschamps a décidé d’appeler pour la première fois avec les A Houssem Aouar. Le sélectionneur loue son évolution, sa technique et sa polyvalence offensive.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQTC21VIB1alHEIkL/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQTC21VIB1alHEIkL/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">L’Heure des Pros du 25 08 2020</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/l-heure-des-pros-du-25-08-2020.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="L’Heure des Pros du 25 08 2020" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:54:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:54:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/l-heure-des-pros-du-25-08-2020</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/l-heure-des-pros-du-25-08-2020.html">&lt;p&gt;Les invités de #HDPros débattent des grands thèmes de l’actualité.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;L’Heure des Pros du 25 08 2020&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;L’Heure des Pros du 25 08 2020&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;L'Heure des Pros du 25 08 2020&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Les invités de #HDPros débattent des grands thèmes de l’actualité.L’Heure des Pros du 25 08 2020 L’Heure des Pros du 25 08 2020 L'Heure des Pros du 25 08 2020</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBKE1VHK2ZrlNhvP/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBKE1VHK2ZrlNhvP/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">WTT Rewind: Jessica Pegula vs. Jen Brady</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/wtt-rewind-jessica-pegula-vs-jen-brady.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WTT Rewind: Jessica Pegula vs. Jen Brady" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:53:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:53:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/wtt-rewind-jessica-pegula-vs-jen-brady</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/wtt-rewind-jessica-pegula-vs-jen-brady.html">&lt;p&gt;Get tuned up for Western &amp;amp; Southern Open as Jessica Pegula takes on Jen Brady in a women’s singles match.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Get tuned up for Western &amp;amp; Southern Open as Jessica Pegula takes on Jen Brady in a women’s singles match.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPzd51VGv9w5JYYQf/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPzd51VGv9w5JYYQf/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">How Can I Increase My Chances of Getting a Job If I’ve Been Unemployed for Years?</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/how-can-i-increase-my-chances-of-getting-a-job-if-i-ve-been-unemployed.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Can I Increase My Chances of Getting a Job If I’ve Been Unemployed for Years?" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:49:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:49:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/how-can-i-increase-my-chances-of-getting-a-job-if-i-ve-been-unemployed</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/how-can-i-increase-my-chances-of-getting-a-job-if-i-ve-been-unemployed.html">&lt;p&gt;Career expert and managing director of Lee Hecht Harrison Philippines Jo Ann Rosary Asetre talks about how you can increase your chances of getting a job if you’ve been unemployed for a long time.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">Career expert and managing director of Lee Hecht Harrison Philippines Jo Ann Rosary Asetre talks about how you can increase your chances of getting a job if you’ve been unemployed for a long time.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQf_01VIX7Y1XAYCq/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQf_01VIX7Y1XAYCq/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Dirilis Ertugrul Episode 19 Season 3 (English Subtitles)</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/dirilis-ertugrul-episode-19-season-3-english-subtitles.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dirilis Ertugrul Episode 19 Season 3 (English Subtitles)" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:48:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:48:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/dirilis-ertugrul-episode-19-season-3-english-subtitles</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/dirilis-ertugrul-episode-19-season-3-english-subtitles.html">&lt;p&gt;Dirilis Ertugrul Episode 19  Season 3 (English Subtitles)  &lt;br /&gt;On this channel, We Will Upload all Episodes and All Seasons of Resurrection Ertugrul With English Subtitles  &lt;br /&gt;‘Ertugrul Ghazi’ is an epic story rooted in the historical events of Anatolia (modern-day Turkey). It is the tale of a daring character with enthralling love and a sense of justice that was strong enough to change the fate of the World. The nomadic Kayi tribe of the Oghuz Turks are on a quest to find a place they can finally call home. Ertugrul leads his people through perseverance against hardship while striving for justice and maintaining the traditions of the land. By battling his enemies with strength and bravery, Ertugrul consequently plants the seed that would lead to the founding of the Ottoman Empire, which spread across three continents and ruled for six centuries.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">Dirilis Ertugrul Episode 19 Season 3 (English Subtitles) On this channel, We Will Upload all Episodes and All Seasons of Resurrection Ertugrul With English Subtitles ‘Ertugrul Ghazi’ is an epic story rooted in the historical events of Anatolia (modern-day Turkey). It is the tale of a daring character with enthralling love and a sense of justice that was strong enough to change the fate of the World. The nomadic Kayi tribe of the Oghuz Turks are on a quest to find a place they can finally call home. Ertugrul leads his people through perseverance against hardship while striving for justice and maintaining the traditions of the land. By battling his enemies with strength and bravery, Ertugrul consequently plants the seed that would lead to the founding of the Ottoman Empire, which spread across three continents and ruled for six centuries.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPgNW1VINVz-fhoXg/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPgNW1VINVz-fhoXg/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">3 Easy Makeup Looks Using Cheek Tint Preview Edit PREVIEW</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/3-easy-makeup-looks-using-cheek-tint-preview-edit-preview.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="3 Easy Makeup Looks Using Cheek Tint Preview Edit PREVIEW" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:43:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:43:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/3-easy-makeup-looks-using-cheek-tint-preview-edit-preview</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/3-easy-makeup-looks-using-cheek-tint-preview-edit-preview.html">&lt;p&gt;Cheek tint is the one makeup product that every Pinay seems to have in their makeup kit. The product is undeniably easy to use and gives you the needed pop of color to instantly brighten up your face. Having said that, your favorite cheek tint can actually be used in more ways than one. In this Preview Edit video, I try to create three very easy makeup looks you can do with cheek tint–and at the same time review Ever Bilena’s newly formulated Blush Rush roller tint and a few more drugstore finds that just arrived in stores.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">Cheek tint is the one makeup product that every Pinay seems to have in their makeup kit. The product is undeniably easy to use and gives you the needed pop of color to instantly brighten up your face. Having said that, your favorite cheek tint can actually be used in more ways than one. In this Preview Edit video, I try to create three very easy makeup looks you can do with cheek tint–and at the same time review Ever Bilena’s newly formulated Blush Rush roller tint and a few more drugstore finds that just arrived in stores.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQgLx1VIZ5kpP3kki/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQgLx1VIZ5kpP3kki/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">España recluta voluntarios para probar vacuna contra la covid-19</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/espa-a-recluta-voluntarios-para-probar-vacuna-contra-la-covid-19.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="España recluta voluntarios para probar vacuna contra la covid-19" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:41:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:41:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/espa-a-recluta-voluntarios-para-probar-vacuna-contra-la-covid-19</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/espa-a-recluta-voluntarios-para-probar-vacuna-contra-la-covid-19.html">&lt;p&gt;Madrid, 29 ago (EFE).- España autorizó este viernes el primer ensayo clínico en humanos para una vacuna anticovid, en el que participarán 190 voluntarios, mientras el avance de la pandemia sigue alcanzando récord de contagios, con 3.829 nuevos casos en las últimas 24 horas, y los fallecidos superan ya los 29.000.  &lt;br /&gt;El Ministerio español de Sanidad registró ayer otros 9.779 positivos, el mayor incremento de esta segunda ola de coronavirus, y suma 33.850 casos en esta semana, 439.286 desde el inicio de la enfermedad.  &lt;br /&gt;La presión asistencial subió un punto porcentual en todo el territorio, pasando del 5 al 6 por ciento, después de haberse producido 188 nuevos ingresos, y las camas ocupadas por pacientes con covid-19 son 6.224, de las que 751 son de UCI, de acuerdo al balance oficial.  &lt;br /&gt;Madrid sigue acaparando la mayor parte de los nuevos contagios, un 30 por ciento de los notificados en las últimas 24 horas, y la presión hospitalaria en la capital española aumenta un punto, hasta el 14 por ciento.  &lt;br /&gt;En toda la región, las restricciones al ocio nocturno y a fumar en la calle serán de aplicación inmediata después de que el Tribunal Superior de Justicia ratificara hoy la orden del gobierno autonómico que había sido suspendida por un magistrado hace una semana, al considerar que no requieren autorización judicial.  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;INCLUYE DECLARACIONES DEL DIRECTOR DEL INSTITUTO DE INVESTIGACIÓN DEL HOSPITAL UNIVERSITARIO MARQUÉS DE VALDECILLA EN SANTANDER, GALO PERALTA  &lt;br /&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;EDICIÓN Y LOCUCIÓN: ROSA IRENE MONSIVÁIS&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Madrid, 29 ago (EFE).- España autorizó este viernes el primer ensayo clínico en humanos para una vacuna anticovid, en el que participarán 190 voluntarios, mientras el avance de la pandemia sigue alcanzando récord de contagios, con 3.829 nuevos casos en las últimas 24 horas, y los fallecidos superan ya los 29.000. El Ministerio español de Sanidad registró ayer otros 9.779 positivos, el mayor incremento de esta segunda ola de coronavirus, y suma 33.850 casos en esta semana, 439.286 desde el inicio de la enfermedad. La presión asistencial subió un punto porcentual en todo el territorio, pasando del 5 al 6 por ciento, después de haberse producido 188 nuevos ingresos, y las camas ocupadas por pacientes con covid-19 son 6.224, de las que 751 son de UCI, de acuerdo al balance oficial. Madrid sigue acaparando la mayor parte de los nuevos contagios, un 30 por ciento de los notificados en las últimas 24 horas, y la presión hospitalaria en la capital española aumenta un punto, hasta el 14 por ciento. En toda la región, las restricciones al ocio nocturno y a fumar en la calle serán de aplicación inmediata después de que el Tribunal Superior de Justicia ratificara hoy la orden del gobierno autonómico que había sido suspendida por un magistrado hace una semana, al considerar que no requieren autorización judicial.   INCLUYE DECLARACIONES DEL DIRECTOR DEL INSTITUTO DE INVESTIGACIÓN DEL HOSPITAL UNIVERSITARIO MARQUÉS DE VALDECILLA EN SANTANDER, GALO PERALTA   EDICIÓN Y LOCUCIÓN: ROSA IRENE MONSIVÁIS</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQg-91VIdB1iMwcCW/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQg-91VIdB1iMwcCW/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Indian heroes- Goutam Narayan saves the Pygmy Hog in India</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/indian-heroes-goutam-narayan-saves-the-pygmy-hog-in-india.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Indian heroes- Goutam Narayan saves the Pygmy Hog in India" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:40:10+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:40:10+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/indian-heroes-goutam-narayan-saves-the-pygmy-hog-in-india</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/indian-heroes-goutam-narayan-saves-the-pygmy-hog-in-india.html">&lt;p&gt;Known for its small size, the Pygmy Hog is the smallest species of wild pig. Scientifically known as Porcula salvania and Nol Gahori or Takuri Borah in Assamese, it is found only in the grassland of Manas Tiger Reserve of Assam in India. In the past they were found in a narrow belt of grassland south of Himalayan foothills in Uttar Pradesh, Nepal, Bihar, North Bengal and Assam. With features like that of a Wild boar, but relatively much smaller than even a baby wild boar, the adult Pygmy Hog measures about 65 cm (25 inches) in length and 25 cm (10 inches) in height and weighs in at around 8 to 9 kgs or under 20 pounds. Males are little bigger than females and can be identified by their moustache. Newborn babies weigh only 150 - 200 grams. A vestigial tail and only three pairs of mammary glands distinguish it from the wild boar, which, despite being much larger, often gets confused with pygmy hogs. Pygmy Hogs survive in tall grasslands and feed on roots, tubers, wild-fruits, termites, earthworms and eggs found in the grasslands. With the extinction of tall, wet grasslands in the region, the Pygmy Hog is currently restricted to a single viable population in the wild in Manas Tiger Reserve and couple of reintroduced populations in Sonai Rupai Wildlife Sanctuary and Orang National Park, all in North-Western Assam. Pygmy Hog is also mentioned in the red list category of the IUCN and is categorized as ‘Critically Endangered,’ putting it among the most threatened of all mammals. Although accurate numbers are not known, it is estimated that there may be only a few hundred, probably less than 300, Pygmy Hogs left in the wild. It is impossible to see Pygmy Hogs in their wild natural habitat, as they are very shy animals. They are well adapted to move fast through tall dense grasses with their streamlined bodies. Pygmy Hogs are very sensitive animals and their survival is closely linked to the existence of the tall, wet grasslands of the region, which, besides being a highly threatened habitat itself, is also crucial for survival of a number of other endangered species. With the aim to saving the species and its habitat the Pygmy Hog Conservation Programme (PHCP), a broad-based research and conservation programme is a collaborative project of the Durrell Wildlife Conservation Trust, IUCN/SSC Wild Pig Specialist Group, the Forest Department – Govt. of Assam and the Ministry of Environment &amp;amp; Forests – Govt. of India that has been trying to conserve Pygmy Hogs and other such endangered species of the tall grasslands of the region through field research, captive breeding and re-introduction after adequate restoration of degraded former habitats. It is administered in Assam by EcoSystems-India. One of the main activities of PHCP is conservation breeding of pygmy hogs. PHCP maintains a captive population of about 50 hogs and has reintroduced 60 hogs over five years in Sonai Rupai Wildlife Sanctuary and Orang National Park. The only captive breeding center in Assa&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="travel" />
  <summary type="html">Known for its small size, the Pygmy Hog is the smallest species of wild pig. Scientifically known as Porcula salvania and Nol Gahori or Takuri Borah in Assamese, it is found only in the grassland of Manas Tiger Reserve of Assam in India. In the past they were found in a narrow belt of grassland south of Himalayan foothills in Uttar Pradesh, Nepal, Bihar, North Bengal and Assam. With features like that of a Wild boar, but relatively much smaller than even a baby wild boar, the adult Pygmy Hog measures about 65 cm (25 inches) in length and 25 cm (10 inches) in height and weighs in at around 8 to 9 kgs or under 20 pounds. Males are little bigger than females and can be identified by their moustache. Newborn babies weigh only 150 - 200 grams. A vestigial tail and only three pairs of mammary glands distinguish it from the wild boar, which, despite being much larger, often gets confused with pygmy hogs. Pygmy Hogs survive in tall grasslands and feed on roots, tubers, wild-fruits, termites, earthworms and eggs found in the grasslands. With the extinction of tall, wet grasslands in the region, the Pygmy Hog is currently restricted to a single viable population in the wild in Manas Tiger Reserve and couple of reintroduced populations in Sonai Rupai Wildlife Sanctuary and Orang National Park, all in North-Western Assam. Pygmy Hog is also mentioned in the red list category of the IUCN and is categorized as ‘Critically Endangered,’ putting it among the most threatened of all mammals. Although accurate numbers are not known, it is estimated that there may be only a few hundred, probably less than 300, Pygmy Hogs left in the wild. It is impossible to see Pygmy Hogs in their wild natural habitat, as they are very shy animals. They are well adapted to move fast through tall dense grasses with their streamlined bodies. Pygmy Hogs are very sensitive animals and their survival is closely linked to the existence of the tall, wet grasslands of the region, which, besides being a highly threatened habitat itself, is also crucial for survival of a number of other endangered species. With the aim to saving the species and its habitat the Pygmy Hog Conservation Programme (PHCP), a broad-based research and conservation programme is a collaborative project of the Durrell Wildlife Conservation Trust, IUCN/SSC Wild Pig Specialist Group, the Forest Department – Govt. of Assam and the Ministry of Environment &amp;amp; Forests – Govt. of India that has been trying to conserve Pygmy Hogs and other such endangered species of the tall grasslands of the region through field research, captive breeding and re-introduction after adequate restoration of degraded former habitats. It is administered in Assam by EcoSystems-India. One of the main activities of PHCP is conservation breeding of pygmy hogs. PHCP maintains a captive population of about 50 hogs and has reintroduced 60 hogs over five years in Sonai Rupai Wildlife Sanctuary and Orang National Park. The only captive breeding center in Assa</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBeU1VHstgSxkGR0/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBeU1VHstgSxkGR0/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award for Rohit Sharma and Mariappan Thangavelu ONEINDIA TAMIL</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/rajiv-gandhi-khel-ratna-award-for-rohit-sharma-and-mariappan-thangavel.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award for Rohit Sharma and Mariappan Thangavelu ONEINDIA TAMIL" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:39:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:39:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/rajiv-gandhi-khel-ratna-award-for-rohit-sharma-and-mariappan-thangavel</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/rajiv-gandhi-khel-ratna-award-for-rohit-sharma-and-mariappan-thangavel.html">&lt;p&gt;#rohitsharma  &lt;br /&gt;# MariappanThangavelu   &lt;br /&gt;Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award : This is the first time five candidates to get Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award. Indian cricket player Rohit Sharma, Tamilnadu’s para-athlete Mariappan Thangavelu, table tennis champion Manika Batra, wrestler Vinesh Phogat and hockey player Rani Rampal to get Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award.  &lt;br /&gt;2020ஆம் ஆண்டிற்கான ராஜீவ் காந்தி கேல் ரத்னா மற்றும் அர்ஜுனா விருதுப் பட்டியல் வெளியாகி உள்ளது. இந்த ஆண்டு ஐந்து பேருக்கு ராஜீவ் காந்தி கேல் ரத்னா விருது வழங்கப்பட உள்ளது.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">#rohitsharma # MariappanThangavelu Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award : This is the first time five candidates to get Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award. Indian cricket player Rohit Sharma, Tamilnadu’s para-athlete Mariappan Thangavelu, table tennis champion Manika Batra, wrestler Vinesh Phogat and hockey player Rani Rampal to get Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award. 2020ஆம் ஆண்டிற்கான ராஜீவ் காந்தி கேல் ரத்னா மற்றும் அர்ஜுனா விருதுப் பட்டியல் வெளியாகி உள்ளது. இந்த ஆண்டு ஐந்து பேருக்கு ராஜீவ் காந்தி கேல் ரத்னா விருது வழங்கப்பட உள்ளது.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPq3J1VG1O6PGuxTN/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPq3J1VG1O6PGuxTN/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">#TDF2020 - Étape 1 Stage 1 - Sourires Smiles</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/tdf2020-tape-1-stage-1-sourires-smiles.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="#TDF2020 - Étape 1 Stage 1 - Sourires Smiles" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:38:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:38:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/tdf2020-tape-1-stage-1-sourires-smiles</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/tdf2020-tape-1-stage-1-sourires-smiles.html">&lt;p&gt;Initialement prévu du 27 juin au 19 juillet, le Tour de France se déroulera sur le parcours prévu, sans changement, de Nice à Paris, du samedi 29 août au dimanche 20 septembre 2020. L’accent est mis sur une visite de l’ensemble des massifs montagneux du territoire : l’étalement, la variété et la raideur atypique des ascensions mettront à disposition des grimpeurs ambitieux des opportunités tout au long de l’épreuve, de l’arrivée d’Orcières-Merlette au chrono de la Planche-des-Belles-Filles, en passant par le Puy Mary, le Grand Colombier ou le col de la Loze en surplomb de Méribel.  &lt;br /&gt;The Tour de France 2020 defining characteristic is the inclusion of all the mountain ranges in France. The spread-out, varied and exceptionally steep climbs will give ambitious climbers one opportunity after another throughout the race, from the finish at Orcières-Merlette to the time trial on La Planche des Belles Filles, not to mention the Puy Mary, the Grand Colombier and the Col de la Loze, overhanging Méribel.  &lt;br /&gt;Plus d’informations sur / More information on:  &lt;br /&gt;Hashtag officiel / Official Hashtag: #TDF2020  &lt;br /&gt;© Amaury Sport Organisation - www.aso.fr&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Initialement prévu du 27 juin au 19 juillet, le Tour de France se déroulera sur le parcours prévu, sans changement, de Nice à Paris, du samedi 29 août au dimanche 20 septembre 2020. L’accent est mis sur une visite de l’ensemble des massifs montagneux du territoire : l’étalement, la variété et la raideur atypique des ascensions mettront à disposition des grimpeurs ambitieux des opportunités tout au long de l’épreuve, de l’arrivée d’Orcières-Merlette au chrono de la Planche-des-Belles-Filles, en passant par le Puy Mary, le Grand Colombier ou le col de la Loze en surplomb de Méribel. The Tour de France 2020 defining characteristic is the inclusion of all the mountain ranges in France. The spread-out, varied and exceptionally steep climbs will give ambitious climbers one opportunity after another throughout the race, from the finish at Orcières-Merlette to the time trial on La Planche des Belles Filles, not to mention the Puy Mary, the Grand Colombier and the Col de la Loze, overhanging Méribel. Plus d’informations sur / More information on: Hashtag officiel / Official Hashtag: #TDF2020 © Amaury Sport Organisation - www.aso.fr</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQiGo1VIfN2JdaweD/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQiGo1VIfN2JdaweD/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Fernandez : « Neymar est en train de faire un groupe» - Foot - C1 - PSG</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/fernandez-neymar-est-en-train-de-faire-un-groupe-foot-c1-psg.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fernandez : « Neymar est en train de faire un groupe» - Foot - C1 - PSG" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:37:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:37:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/fernandez-neymar-est-en-train-de-faire-un-groupe-foot-c1-psg</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/fernandez-neymar-est-en-train-de-faire-un-groupe-foot-c1-psg.html">&lt;p&gt;VIDÉO FOOT - L’ancien joueur et coach du paris-SG était invité ce samedi sur le plateau de l’équipe du soir sur la chaîne L’Équipe et il a évoqué l’actuel état d’esprit de Neymar, le «chef d’orchestre» de l’équipe parisienne.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">VIDÉO FOOT - L’ancien joueur et coach du paris-SG était invité ce samedi sur le plateau de l’équipe du soir sur la chaîne L’Équipe et il a évoqué l’actuel état d’esprit de Neymar, le «chef d’orchestre» de l’équipe parisienne.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPwTR1VGPP2JrCckP/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPwTR1VGPP2JrCckP/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">India May Get Oxford’s COVID-19 Vaccine In December‌ Oneindia Malayalam</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/india-may-get-oxford-s-covid-19-vaccine-in-december-oneindia-malayalam.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="India May Get Oxford’s COVID-19 Vaccine In December‌ Oneindia Malayalam" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:36:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:36:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/india-may-get-oxford-s-covid-19-vaccine-in-december-oneindia-malayalam</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/india-may-get-oxford-s-covid-19-vaccine-in-december-oneindia-malayalam.html">&lt;p&gt;India May Get Oxford’s COVID-19 Vaccine In December  &lt;br /&gt;കൊവിഡ് ഭീതിക്കിടെ ആശ്വാസവാര്‍ത്ത. ഓക്സ്ഫഡ് യൂണിവേഴ്സിറ്റിയുടെ നേതൃത്വത്തില്‍ വികസിപ്പിക്കുന്ന കോവിഡ് പ്രതിരോധ വാക്സീന്‍ ഇന്ത്യയില്‍ മനുഷ്യരില്‍ പരീക്ഷണം തുടങ്ങി.രണ്ടും മൂന്നും ഘട്ട പരീക്ഷണങ്ങള്‍ പുനെ സെറം ഇന്‍സ്റ്റിറ്റ്യൂട്ടില്‍ ആരംഭിച്ചു.1500 പേരിലാണ് മൂന്നാഘട്ട പരീക്ഷണം. വിജയിച്ചാല്‍ വാക്സീന്‍ ഡിസംബറില്‍ തന്നെയെന്ന് ഡയറക്ടര്‍ പുരുഷോത്തമന്‍ സി.നമ്ബ്യാര്‍ പറഞ്ഞു.രാജ്യത്ത് 250 രൂപയ്ക്കു വില്‍ക്കാനാകുമെന്നാണു കരുതുന്നത് എന്നും അദ്ദേഹം പറഞ്ഞു&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">India May Get Oxford’s COVID-19 Vaccine In December കൊവിഡ് ഭീതിക്കിടെ ആശ്വാസവാര്‍ത്ത. ഓക്സ്ഫഡ് യൂണിവേഴ്സിറ്റിയുടെ നേതൃത്വത്തില്‍ വികസിപ്പിക്കുന്ന കോവിഡ് പ്രതിരോധ വാക്സീന്‍ ഇന്ത്യയില്‍ മനുഷ്യരില്‍ പരീക്ഷണം തുടങ്ങി.രണ്ടും മൂന്നും ഘട്ട പരീക്ഷണങ്ങള്‍ പുനെ സെറം ഇന്‍സ്റ്റിറ്റ്യൂട്ടില്‍ ആരംഭിച്ചു.1500 പേരിലാണ് മൂന്നാഘട്ട പരീക്ഷണം. വിജയിച്ചാല്‍ വാക്സീന്‍ ഡിസംബറില്‍ തന്നെയെന്ന് ഡയറക്ടര്‍ പുരുഷോത്തമന്‍ സി.നമ്ബ്യാര്‍ പറഞ്ഞു.രാജ്യത്ത് 250 രൂപയ്ക്കു വില്‍ക്കാനാകുമെന്നാണു കരുതുന്നത് എന്നും അദ്ദേഹം പറഞ്ഞു</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPsna1VIGovHaiVFB/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPsna1VIGovHaiVFB/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">MS Dhoni’s Six Cancelled A Pak Cricketer’s ‘Date’ With An Indian Girl Oneindia Telugu</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/ms-dhoni-s-six-cancelled-a-pak-cricketer-s-date-with-an-indian-girl-on.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MS Dhoni’s Six Cancelled A Pak Cricketer’s ‘Date’ With An Indian Girl Oneindia Telugu" />
  <published>2020-08-30T02:36:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-30T02:36:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/ms-dhoni-s-six-cancelled-a-pak-cricketer-s-date-with-an-indian-girl-on</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/ms-dhoni-s-six-cancelled-a-pak-cricketer-s-date-with-an-indian-girl-on.html">&lt;p&gt;MS Dhoni’s six cost Pak cricketer a potential ‘date’ with an Indian girl  during India’s A tour of Kenya in 2004.   &lt;br /&gt;#MSDhoni   &lt;br /&gt;#MSDhoniSixer   &lt;br /&gt;#IndVsPak   &lt;br /&gt;#pakcricketer   &lt;br /&gt;#IPL2020   &lt;br /&gt;#ChennaiSuperKings   &lt;br /&gt;#Cricket   &lt;br /&gt;#TeamIndia   &lt;br /&gt;భారత మాజీ కెప్టెన్ మహేంద్ర సింగ్ ధోనీ అనుకోకుండా ఒక పాకిస్థాన్‌ క్రికెటర్‌ డేటింగ్‌ రద్దుకు కారణమయ్యాడని ఓ ప్రముఖ ఛానల్ తన కథనంలో పేర్కొంది. అది కూడా మహీ టీమిండియాకు ఎంపికవ్వకముందని, ఆ పాక్‌ క్రికెటర్‌ డేటింగ్‌కి వెళ్లాల్సింది కూడా ఓ భారత యువతితోనని రాసుకొచ్చింది.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">MS Dhoni’s six cost Pak cricketer a potential ‘date’ with an Indian girl during India’s A tour of Kenya in 2004. #MSDhoni #MSDhoniSixer #IndVsPak #pakcricketer #IPL2020 #ChennaiSuperKings #Cricket #TeamIndia భారత మాజీ కెప్టెన్ మహేంద్ర సింగ్ ధోనీ అనుకోకుండా ఒక పాకిస్థాన్‌ క్రికెటర్‌ డేటింగ్‌ రద్దుకు కారణమయ్యాడని ఓ ప్రముఖ ఛానల్ తన కథనంలో పేర్కొంది. అది కూడా మహీ టీమిండియాకు ఎంపికవ్వకముందని, ఆ పాక్‌ క్రికెటర్‌ డేటింగ్‌కి వెళ్లాల్సింది కూడా ఓ భారత యువతితోనని రాసుకొచ్చింది.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPzTs1VGdfFVbdWTv/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPzTs1VGdfFVbdWTv/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 </feed>