<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
<updated>2020-08-26T10:18:44+03:00</updated>
<id>https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml</id>
<title type="html">Adowsom</title>
<subtitle>Duct Tape is like the force. There's a dark side and a light side, and it holds the universe together.</subtitle>
<author>
 <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
 <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
 <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
</author>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Delhi Terrorist Encounter : संदिग्ध ISIS आतंकी गिरफ्तार, IED बरामद वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/delhi-terrorist-encounter-isis-ied.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Delhi Terrorist Encounter : संदिग्ध ISIS आतंकी गिरफ्तार, IED बरामद वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:13:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:13:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/delhi-terrorist-encounter-isis-ied</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/delhi-terrorist-encounter-isis-ied.html">&lt;p&gt;The Delhi Police has arrested a suspected terrorist in an encounter in Dhaulakuan last night amid warnings of terrorist attack once again in the capital Delhi. Weapons have been recovered along with the IED from the terrorist. The encounter took place near the ridge road connecting Dhaulakuan to Karol Bagh. After firing from both sides, the police has arrested the terrorist.  &lt;br /&gt;राजधानी दिल्ली में एक बार फिर आतंकी हमले के अलर्ट के बीच धौलाकुआं में बीती रात हुई मुठभेड़ में दिल्ली पुलिस ने एक संदिग्ध आतंकी को गिरफ्तार किया है. आतंकी के पास से आईईडी के साथ ही हथियार बरामद किए हैं. ये एनकाउंटर धौलाकुआं से करोल बाग को जोड़ने वाली रिज रोड के पास हुआ. दोनों तरफ से फायरिंग के बाद पुलिस ने आतंकी को गिरफ्तार किया है.    &lt;br /&gt;#DelhiTerroristEncounter #DelhiPolice #ISISTerrorist&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The Delhi Police has arrested a suspected terrorist in an encounter in Dhaulakuan last night amid warnings of terrorist attack once again in the capital Delhi. Weapons have been recovered along with the IED from the terrorist. The encounter took place near the ridge road connecting Dhaulakuan to Karol Bagh. After firing from both sides, the police has arrested the terrorist. राजधानी दिल्ली में एक बार फिर आतंकी हमले के अलर्ट के बीच धौलाकुआं में बीती रात हुई मुठभेड़ में दिल्ली पुलिस ने एक संदिग्ध आतंकी को गिरफ्तार किया है. आतंकी के पास से आईईडी के साथ ही हथियार बरामद किए हैं. ये एनकाउंटर धौलाकुआं से करोल बाग को जोड़ने वाली रिज रोड के पास हुआ. दोनों तरफ से फायरिंग के बाद पुलिस ने आतंकी को गिरफ्तार किया है. #DelhiTerroristEncounter #DelhiPolice #ISISTerrorist</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPsL41VGAXjpV8AHN/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPsL41VGAXjpV8AHN/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Silk Board Metro ನಿಲ್ದಾಣದ ಬಳಿ ಬಸ್ ಟರ್ಮಿನಲ್ Oneindia Kannada</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/silk-board-metro-oneindia-kannada.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Silk Board Metro ನಿಲ್ದಾಣದ ಬಳಿ ಬಸ್ ಟರ್ಮಿನಲ್ Oneindia Kannada" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:12:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:12:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/silk-board-metro-oneindia-kannada</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/silk-board-metro-oneindia-kannada.html">&lt;p&gt;ನಿರ್ಮಾಣ ಹಂತದಲ್ಲಿರುವ ಕಲ್ಯಾಣ ಮಂಟಪವನ್ನು (ಮದುವೆ ಮಂಟಪ) ನೆಲಸಮ ಮಾಡಲು ಮತ್ತು ಪಕ್ಕದ ಜಮೀನಿನಲ್ಲಿ 20 ಕೋಟಿ ರೂ.ಗಳ ವೆಚ್ಚದಲ್ಲಿ ಹೊಸದನ್ನು ನಿರ್ಮಿಸಲು ಬಿಎಂಆರ್‌ಸಿಎಲ್  &lt;br /&gt;ಮುಂದಾಗಿದೆ  &lt;br /&gt;#SilkBoard  &lt;br /&gt;#BMRCL has gone ahead to build a new one at a cost of Rs 20 crore.  The agreement was signed after approval from the government.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">ನಿರ್ಮಾಣ ಹಂತದಲ್ಲಿರುವ ಕಲ್ಯಾಣ ಮಂಟಪವನ್ನು (ಮದುವೆ ಮಂಟಪ) ನೆಲಸಮ ಮಾಡಲು ಮತ್ತು ಪಕ್ಕದ ಜಮೀನಿನಲ್ಲಿ 20 ಕೋಟಿ ರೂ.ಗಳ ವೆಚ್ಚದಲ್ಲಿ ಹೊಸದನ್ನು ನಿರ್ಮಿಸಲು ಬಿಎಂಆರ್‌ಸಿಎಲ್ ಮುಂದಾಗಿದೆ #SilkBoard #BMRCL has gone ahead to build a new one at a cost of Rs 20 crore. The agreement was signed after approval from the government.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPgT11VFeo9wef5Dv/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPgT11VFeo9wef5Dv/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Dave D’Mello - Another Chance</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/dave-d-mello-another-chance.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dave D’Mello - Another Chance" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:12:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:12:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/dave-d-mello-another-chance</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/dave-d-mello-another-chance.html">&lt;p&gt;Released - 16th January 2017   &lt;br /&gt;Dave D’Mello - Another Chance   &lt;br /&gt;Download Dave D’Mello tracks:    &lt;br /&gt;————–   &lt;br /&gt;Follow Dave D’Mello:   &lt;br /&gt;Facebook:    &lt;br /&gt;Instagram:    &lt;br /&gt;Soundcloud:    &lt;br /&gt;Spotify:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="music" />
  <summary type="html">Released - 16th January 2017 Dave D’Mello - Another Chance Download Dave D’Mello tracks: ————– Follow Dave D’Mello: Facebook: Instagram: Soundcloud: Spotify:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPycM1VHNZ-xso8oz/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPycM1VHNZ-xso8oz/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">First trans neighborhood in Argentina: initiative of a nun</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/first-trans-neighborhood-in-argentina-initiative-of-a-nun.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First trans neighborhood in Argentina: initiative of a nun" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:11:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:11:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/first-trans-neighborhood-in-argentina-initiative-of-a-nun</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/first-trans-neighborhood-in-argentina-initiative-of-a-nun.html">&lt;p&gt;The first housing complex for transexual people in Argentina, according to the promoters of the project, was inaugurated this week in the city of Neuquén, in Argentine Patagonia, at the initiative of a nun on land made available to her convent by the administration of the city and with funds from the provincial government, an experience that even deserved the congratulations of Pope Francis.  &lt;br /&gt;This &quot;Tutored Social Condominium for Trans Women&quot; has 12 individual rooms, which offer a permanent living solution to a dozen trans people aged between 40 and 70 years, who live in a vulnerable situation, received in a format of bailment and, in the event of death, they are delivered to other people in the same situation.  &lt;br /&gt;The houses were built by the Provincial Institute of Housing and Urbanism (IPVU) in the district of Confluencia and delivered to the Order of the Discalced Carmelites for its administration, based on the original idea of ​​Mónica Astorga Cremona (53), the so-called “Nun of the Trans ”.  &lt;br /&gt;Astorga Cremona, promoter of the idea, said that Pope Francis responded to the email where she told him about the recent inauguration of the housing complex for trans people.  &lt;br /&gt;The Supreme Pontiff replied: &quot;Dear Monica, God who did not go to the seminary or study theology will repay you abundantly. I pray for you and your girls. Do not forget to pray for me. May Jesus blesses you and may the Holy Virgin take care of you.&quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;The houses were built by the Provincial Institute of Housing and are managed by the Discalced Carmelites.  &lt;br /&gt;During the ceremony, the religious accompanied each of them to open the door of their new home for the first time. &quot;They couldn’t even hold the key because they were crying, they couldn’t believe what was happening, and I remember one of them told me, ‘The bathroom is bigger than the room where I lived,’&quot; she said.  &lt;br /&gt;It is a two-story building with six 40-square-meter apartments on each level, a multipurpose room, and a 120-square-meter park that will be used as a vegetable garden, recreation area and parking lot; the investment is 27.6 million pesos (approximately $ 280,000).  &lt;br /&gt;The apartments are equipped with kitchen and bathroom, heating and water heater, and have an individual balcony or small patio.  &lt;br /&gt;The nun Astorga makes it clear that it is not &quot;an accommodation or a trans house&quot;, but houses that are granted on loan, &quot;as if it were rent, but without paying anything and without conditions.&quot;  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;If they respect the rules of rental, they stay for life, but if they don’t respect them, they are warned and taken away,&quot; she explained.  &lt;br /&gt;One of the beneficiaries is Erika Díaz (60), who is convinced that &quot;from now on my life will be a miracle.&quot;  &lt;br /&gt;“We have always lived in the worst places, but now everything will change for us; I will start living during the day because I was in prostitution, always at night ”, she added.  &lt;br /&gt;SOUNDBITE: MONICA ASTORGA CREMONA, Nun who created the project  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;My dream was that transsexuals have a decent home because they were never given this opportunity, they have no rights to anything. The apartments are very bright, they lived in the dark because we made them live in the dark, because we buried them, and they always lived at night, they have to take advantage of the light, from this place that is unique in the world, there are no houses for trans people anywhere in the world&quot;.  &lt;br /&gt;SOUNDBITE: TRANSSEXUAL WOMAN BENEFICIARY OF A HOUSING  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;The places where we always live and have always been renting, people always take advantage of our condition of being transsexuals, we pay rent that you pay 5 thousand pesos, we pay 15 thousand, just for being trans women, and I’m not telling you of a rental like this, clean, with all services, we have lived in places with humidity, vermin, insects, transsexual women always live badly&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The first housing complex for transexual people in Argentina, according to the promoters of the project, was inaugurated this week in the city of Neuquén, in Argentine Patagonia, at the initiative of a nun on land made available to her convent by the administration of the city and with funds from the provincial government, an experience that even deserved the congratulations of Pope Francis. This &quot;Tutored Social Condominium for Trans Women&quot; has 12 individual rooms, which offer a permanent living solution to a dozen trans people aged between 40 and 70 years, who live in a vulnerable situation, received in a format of bailment and, in the event of death, they are delivered to other people in the same situation. The houses were built by the Provincial Institute of Housing and Urbanism (IPVU) in the district of Confluencia and delivered to the Order of the Discalced Carmelites for its administration, based on the original idea of ​​Mónica Astorga Cremona (53), the so-called “Nun of the Trans ”. Astorga Cremona, promoter of the idea, said that Pope Francis responded to the email where she told him about the recent inauguration of the housing complex for trans people. The Supreme Pontiff replied: &quot;Dear Monica, God who did not go to the seminary or study theology will repay you abundantly. I pray for you and your girls. Do not forget to pray for me. May Jesus blesses you and may the Holy Virgin take care of you.&quot;. The houses were built by the Provincial Institute of Housing and are managed by the Discalced Carmelites. During the ceremony, the religious accompanied each of them to open the door of their new home for the first time. &quot;They couldn’t even hold the key because they were crying, they couldn’t believe what was happening, and I remember one of them told me, ‘The bathroom is bigger than the room where I lived,’&quot; she said. It is a two-story building with six 40-square-meter apartments on each level, a multipurpose room, and a 120-square-meter park that will be used as a vegetable garden, recreation area and parking lot; the investment is 27.6 million pesos (approximately $ 280,000). The apartments are equipped with kitchen and bathroom, heating and water heater, and have an individual balcony or small patio. The nun Astorga makes it clear that it is not &quot;an accommodation or a trans house&quot;, but houses that are granted on loan, &quot;as if it were rent, but without paying anything and without conditions.&quot; &quot;If they respect the rules of rental, they stay for life, but if they don’t respect them, they are warned and taken away,&quot; she explained. One of the beneficiaries is Erika Díaz (60), who is convinced that &quot;from now on my life will be a miracle.&quot; “We have always lived in the worst places, but now everything will change for us; I will start living during the day because I was in prostitution, always at night ”, she added. SOUNDBITE: MONICA ASTORGA CREMONA, Nun who created the project &quot;My dream was that transsexuals have a decent home because they were never given this opportunity, they have no rights to anything. The apartments are very bright, they lived in the dark because we made them live in the dark, because we buried them, and they always lived at night, they have to take advantage of the light, from this place that is unique in the world, there are no houses for trans people anywhere in the world&quot;. SOUNDBITE: TRANSSEXUAL WOMAN BENEFICIARY OF A HOUSING &quot;The places where we always live and have always been renting, people always take advantage of our condition of being transsexuals, we pay rent that you pay 5 thousand pesos, we pay 15 thousand, just for being trans women, and I’m not telling you of a rental like this, clean, with all services, we have lived in places with humidity, vermin, insects, transsexual women always live badly&quot;.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPIHV1VEj8zvVVd-O/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPIHV1VEj8zvVVd-O/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Reopening of Schools and Colleges ఇప్పట్లో పాఠశాలలు తెరిచే ఆలోచనే లేదు !</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/reopening-of-schools-and-colleges.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reopening of Schools and Colleges ఇప్పట్లో పాఠశాలలు తెరిచే ఆలోచనే లేదు !" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:11:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:11:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/reopening-of-schools-and-colleges</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/reopening-of-schools-and-colleges.html">&lt;p&gt;Union health ministry said that the home ministry has not formulated any guidelines to reopening of schools and Colleges, Reports    &lt;br /&gt;#SchoolsReopen    &lt;br /&gt;#ReopeningSchoolsColleges   &lt;br /&gt;#Unionhealthministry   &lt;br /&gt;#JEENEET2020   &lt;br /&gt;#NEETJEEExamPostponement   &lt;br /&gt;#coronavirusindia   &lt;br /&gt;#students   &lt;br /&gt;#coronavaccine   &lt;br /&gt;#apSchoolsreopen   &lt;br /&gt;#unlockguidelines    &lt;br /&gt;దేశంలో కరోనా మహమ్మారి వ్యాప్తి ఇంకా కొనసాగుతున్నది. కేంద్ర ఆరోగ్య శాఖ మంగళవారం తెలిపిన వివరాల ప్రకారం గడిచిన 24 గంటల్లో కొత్తగా 60,975 కేసులు, 848 మరణాలు నమోదయ్యాయి. దీంతో మొత్తం ఇన్ఫెక్షన్ల సంఖ్య 31.72లక్షలకు, మరణాల సంఖ్య 58,562కు పెరిగింది. రికవరీలు, మరణాల సంఖ్య పరంగా భారత్ మెరుగైన స్థితిలో ఉన్నప్పటికీ.. స్కూళ్లు, కాలేజీలను మాత్రం ఇప్పుడప్పుడే తెరవబోమని కేంద్ర ప్రభుత్వం స్పష్టం చేసింది.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Union health ministry said that the home ministry has not formulated any guidelines to reopening of schools and Colleges, Reports #SchoolsReopen #ReopeningSchoolsColleges #Unionhealthministry #JEENEET2020 #NEETJEEExamPostponement #coronavirusindia #students #coronavaccine #apSchoolsreopen #unlockguidelines దేశంలో కరోనా మహమ్మారి వ్యాప్తి ఇంకా కొనసాగుతున్నది. కేంద్ర ఆరోగ్య శాఖ మంగళవారం తెలిపిన వివరాల ప్రకారం గడిచిన 24 గంటల్లో కొత్తగా 60,975 కేసులు, 848 మరణాలు నమోదయ్యాయి. దీంతో మొత్తం ఇన్ఫెక్షన్ల సంఖ్య 31.72లక్షలకు, మరణాల సంఖ్య 58,562కు పెరిగింది. రికవరీలు, మరణాల సంఖ్య పరంగా భారత్ మెరుగైన స్థితిలో ఉన్నప్పటికీ.. స్కూళ్లు, కాలేజీలను మాత్రం ఇప్పుడప్పుడే తెరవబోమని కేంద్ర ప్రభుత్వం స్పష్టం చేసింది.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQHx01VHVzJhSeXpI/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQHx01VHVzJhSeXpI/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Coronavirus Unlock 4.0: 1 सितंबर से स्कूल-कॉलेज समेत क्या-क्या खुलने की संभावना वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/coronavirus-unlock-4-0-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Coronavirus Unlock 4.0: 1 सितंबर से स्कूल-कॉलेज समेत क्या-क्या खुलने की संभावना वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:09:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:09:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/coronavirus-unlock-4-0-1</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/coronavirus-unlock-4-0-1.html">&lt;p&gt;The lockdown was announced on March 25 in the country due to the corona virus, the process of unlocking is being carried out in a phased manner after almost two months of lockdown. Now the unlock 3 is coming to an end on August 31, such In the government, once again the unlock-4 can be announced, in which some more concession can be given. Although almost all the services have been restored in the current guideline, the government has not given any concession regarding educational institutions, schools, colleges, shopping malls, cinema halls, theaters, so people are hopeful that this time Unlock can be discounted in these areas    &lt;br /&gt;कोरोना वायरस के चलते देश में 25 मार्च को लॉकडाउन का ऐलान किया गया था, तकरीबन दो महीने के लॉकडाउन के बाद चरणबद्ध तरीके से अनलॉक की प्रक्रिया को आगे बढ़ाया जा रहा है।अब अनलॉक 3 की मियाद 31 अगस्त को खत्म हो रही है, ऐसे में सरकार एक बार फिर से अनलॉक-4 का ऐलान कर सकती है, जिसमे कुछ और रियायत दी जा सकती है। हालांकि मौजूदा गाइडलाइन में तकरीबन सभी सेवाओं को बहाल कर दिया गया है लेकिन अभी भी शैक्षणिक संस्थान, स्कूल, कॉलेज, शॉपिंग मॉल सिनेमा हॉल, थिएटर को लेकर सरकार ने किसी तरह की रियायत नहीं दी है, लिहाजा लोगों को उम्मीद है कि इस बार के अनलॉक में इन क्षेत्रों में छूट दी जा सकती है    &lt;br /&gt;#Coronavirus #Lockdown #Unlock&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The lockdown was announced on March 25 in the country due to the corona virus, the process of unlocking is being carried out in a phased manner after almost two months of lockdown. Now the unlock 3 is coming to an end on August 31, such In the government, once again the unlock-4 can be announced, in which some more concession can be given. Although almost all the services have been restored in the current guideline, the government has not given any concession regarding educational institutions, schools, colleges, shopping malls, cinema halls, theaters, so people are hopeful that this time Unlock can be discounted in these areas कोरोना वायरस के चलते देश में 25 मार्च को लॉकडाउन का ऐलान किया गया था, तकरीबन दो महीने के लॉकडाउन के बाद चरणबद्ध तरीके से अनलॉक की प्रक्रिया को आगे बढ़ाया जा रहा है।अब अनलॉक 3 की मियाद 31 अगस्त को खत्म हो रही है, ऐसे में सरकार एक बार फिर से अनलॉक-4 का ऐलान कर सकती है, जिसमे कुछ और रियायत दी जा सकती है। हालांकि मौजूदा गाइडलाइन में तकरीबन सभी सेवाओं को बहाल कर दिया गया है लेकिन अभी भी शैक्षणिक संस्थान, स्कूल, कॉलेज, शॉपिंग मॉल सिनेमा हॉल, थिएटर को लेकर सरकार ने किसी तरह की रियायत नहीं दी है, लिहाजा लोगों को उम्मीद है कि इस बार के अनलॉक में इन क्षेत्रों में छूट दी जा सकती है #Coronavirus #Lockdown #Unlock</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4RX1VGyAiZHNI3L/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4RX1VGyAiZHNI3L/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Judge Sets Steve Bannon’s Bail, Demands Passport</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/judge-sets-steve-bannon-s-bail-demands-passport.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Judge Sets Steve Bannon’s Bail, Demands Passport" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:09:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:09:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/judge-sets-steve-bannon-s-bail-demands-passport</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/judge-sets-steve-bannon-s-bail-demands-passport.html">&lt;p&gt;From his arrest on a yacht to a holding cell Thursday, Steve Bannon pleaded not guilty during his arraignment in New York on federal fraud charges.  &lt;br /&gt;Bannon, 66, appeared before the judge handcuffed and wearing a white mask. He could be seen on video rocking back and forth throughout the hearing.  &lt;br /&gt;Newser reports the former adviser to President Donald Trump is charged with defrauding donors to a ‘We Build the Wall’ Kickstarter campaign.  &lt;br /&gt;A judge approved Bannon’s release on a $5 million bond package, secured by $1.75 million in cash or real property. Bannon has until September 3rd to produce it.  &lt;br /&gt;There’ll be no more traveling on yachts or private jets. Besides being limited to Connecticut and New York states, he’ll have to turn over his passport.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">From his arrest on a yacht to a holding cell Thursday, Steve Bannon pleaded not guilty during his arraignment in New York on federal fraud charges. Bannon, 66, appeared before the judge handcuffed and wearing a white mask. He could be seen on video rocking back and forth throughout the hearing. Newser reports the former adviser to President Donald Trump is charged with defrauding donors to a ‘We Build the Wall’ Kickstarter campaign. A judge approved Bannon’s release on a $5 million bond package, secured by $1.75 million in cash or real property. Bannon has until September 3rd to produce it. There’ll be no more traveling on yachts or private jets. Besides being limited to Connecticut and New York states, he’ll have to turn over his passport.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPk7Y1VFoiPIOpwhN/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPk7Y1VFoiPIOpwhN/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">The new Porsche 911 Targa 4 in Dolomite Silver Driving Video</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/the-new-porsche-911-targa-4-in-dolomite-silver-driving-video.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The new Porsche 911 Targa 4 in Dolomite Silver Driving Video" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:08:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:08:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/the-new-porsche-911-targa-4-in-dolomite-silver-driving-video</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/the-new-porsche-911-targa-4-in-dolomite-silver-driving-video.html">&lt;p&gt;Porsche completes its sports car trio in time for summer: following on from the Coupé and Cabriolet, the third body variant of the new 911 generation now makes its debut with the all-wheel drive 911 Targa 4 and 911 Targa 4S models. The distinguishing feature of the Targa remains its innovative, fully automatic roof system and, just like the legendary original Targa model from 1965, it features a characteristic wide roll hoop, a movable roof section above the front seats and a wraparound rear window. The roof can be comfortably opened and closed in just 19 seconds.  &lt;br /&gt;It is powered by a six-cylinder, three-litre boxer engine with twin turbochargers: the 911 Targa 4 now delivers 283 kW (385 PS) and, in combination with the optional Sport Chrono package, accelerates from zero to 100 km/h in just 4.2 seconds – one tenth faster than before. The engine in the 911 Targa 4S boasts 331 kW (450 PS) and reaches the 100 km/h mark in just 3.6 seconds under the same conditions – four tenths faster than its predecessor. Top speed of the 911 Targa 4 is 289 km/h (up two km/h), while the 4S peaks at 304 km/h (up three km/h).&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="auto" />
  <summary type="html">Porsche completes its sports car trio in time for summer: following on from the Coupé and Cabriolet, the third body variant of the new 911 generation now makes its debut with the all-wheel drive 911 Targa 4 and 911 Targa 4S models. The distinguishing feature of the Targa remains its innovative, fully automatic roof system and, just like the legendary original Targa model from 1965, it features a characteristic wide roll hoop, a movable roof section above the front seats and a wraparound rear window. The roof can be comfortably opened and closed in just 19 seconds. It is powered by a six-cylinder, three-litre boxer engine with twin turbochargers: the 911 Targa 4 now delivers 283 kW (385 PS) and, in combination with the optional Sport Chrono package, accelerates from zero to 100 km/h in just 4.2 seconds – one tenth faster than before. The engine in the 911 Targa 4S boasts 331 kW (450 PS) and reaches the 100 km/h mark in just 3.6 seconds under the same conditions – four tenths faster than its predecessor. Top speed of the 911 Targa 4 is 289 km/h (up two km/h), while the 4S peaks at 304 km/h (up three km/h).</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPNrf1VEzaSSOwNn1/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPNrf1VEzaSSOwNn1/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">चीन अगर ‘दर्द’ है तो ‘दवा’ भी, जानिए कैसे</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/x7vn657.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="चीन अगर ‘दर्द’ है तो ‘दवा’ भी, जानिए कैसे" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:08:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:08:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/x7vn657</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/x7vn657.html">&lt;p&gt;#sanjeevnitodaynews चैनल ,खेल,शिक्षा ,कारोबार,फिल्म और राजनैतिक देश - विदेश से जुडी सभी बड़ी खबरों के लिए  हमारे यूट्यूब चैनल को सब्सक्राइब जरूर करे.   &lt;br /&gt;संजीवनी टुडे एप्प डाउनलोड करे —-   &lt;br /&gt;अधिक जानकारी के लिए    &lt;br /&gt;पर विजिट करे।  &lt;br /&gt;Follow us on:   &lt;br /&gt;Like The sanjeevnitoday on Facebook:   &lt;br /&gt;Follow The sanjeevnitoday on Twitter:   &lt;br /&gt;किसी भी प्रकार की न्यूज़ और वीडियो के लिए आप हमारे वॉट्स एप्प पर हमसे संपर्क कर सकते है  —-   8094811115&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">#sanjeevnitodaynews चैनल ,खेल,शिक्षा ,कारोबार,फिल्म और राजनैतिक देश - विदेश से जुडी सभी बड़ी खबरों के लिए हमारे यूट्यूब चैनल को सब्सक्राइब जरूर करे. संजीवनी टुडे एप्प डाउनलोड करे —- अधिक जानकारी के लिए पर विजिट करे। Follow us on: Like The sanjeevnitoday on Facebook: Follow The sanjeevnitoday on Twitter: किसी भी प्रकार की न्यूज़ और वीडियो के लिए आप हमारे वॉट्स एप्प पर हमसे संपर्क कर सकते है —- 8094811115</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPNdR1VG8fiA7nuhc/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPNdR1VG8fiA7nuhc/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">E-Junkies: How Singaporean is Nathan Hartono?</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/e-junkies-how-singaporean-is-nathan-hartono.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="E-Junkies: How Singaporean is Nathan Hartono?" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:07:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:07:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/e-junkies-how-singaporean-is-nathan-hartono</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/e-junkies-how-singaporean-is-nathan-hartono.html">&lt;p&gt;Full story:   &lt;br /&gt;For the extended version of the interview, head on over to Spotify:   &lt;br /&gt;With National Day just a day away, we checked in with Nathan Hartono to find out what this year’s NDP theme song means to him, and how Singaporean he really is.  &lt;br /&gt;AsiaOne wishes everyone a Happy National Day!  &lt;br /&gt;#NathanHartono #NDP2020 #EverythingIAm  &lt;br /&gt;—  &lt;br /&gt;Read more:   &lt;br /&gt;FOLLOW us on   &lt;br /&gt;- Facebook:   &lt;br /&gt;- Twitter:    &lt;br /&gt;- Instagram:    &lt;br /&gt;EMAIL:   &lt;br /&gt;For story leads, business enquiries, contact editor@asiaone.com&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="people" />
  <summary type="html">Full story: For the extended version of the interview, head on over to Spotify: With National Day just a day away, we checked in with Nathan Hartono to find out what this year’s NDP theme song means to him, and how Singaporean he really is. AsiaOne wishes everyone a Happy National Day! #NathanHartono #NDP2020 #EverythingIAm — Read more: FOLLOW us on - Facebook: - Twitter: - Instagram: EMAIL: For story leads, business enquiries, contact editor@asiaone.com</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPDeN1VEWs_5BIMC8/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPDeN1VEWs_5BIMC8/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Le Mans 66 - Déjà Vu - Références et influences de cinéma</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/le-mans-66-d-j-vu-r-f-rences-et-influences-de-cin-ma.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Le Mans 66 - Déjà Vu - Références et influences de cinéma" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:07:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:07:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/le-mans-66-d-j-vu-r-f-rences-et-influences-de-cin-ma</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/le-mans-66-d-j-vu-r-f-rences-et-influences-de-cin-ma.html">&lt;p&gt;Vidéo originale dévoilant les influences et références filmiques qui ont pu inspirer le réalisateur d’un film disponible sur CANAL+  www.canalplus.com/cinema/&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">Vidéo originale dévoilant les influences et références filmiques qui ont pu inspirer le réalisateur d’un film disponible sur CANAL+  www.canalplus.com/cinema/</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPOjC1VFwLB7SOQxL/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPOjC1VFwLB7SOQxL/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Tum Ho Wajah Episode 17 Promo HUM TV Drama 21 August 2020</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/tum-ho-wajah-episode-17-promo-hum-tv-drama-21-august-2020.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tum Ho Wajah Episode 17 Promo HUM TV Drama 21 August 2020" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:06:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:06:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/tum-ho-wajah-episode-17-promo-hum-tv-drama-21-august-2020</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/tum-ho-wajah-episode-17-promo-hum-tv-drama-21-august-2020.html">&lt;p&gt;Tum Ho Wajah, Episode 17 Promo, Official HD Video - 21 August 2020  &lt;br /&gt;Tum Ho Wajah is a story of lust, lies, deceit and karma. Penned by Samina Ejaz and directed by Samia Waseem, the drama serial is an intertwined story of Mansoor Ahmed, Ghafoor and Mansoor’s younger brother Murad Ahmed’s families. Mansoor Ahmed’s wife Sahiba, daughters Chanda and Sitara and sons Zain and Babar are a closed knit, typical happy middle-class family. Things seem to be working for the family until Chanda makes a terrible mistake that not only shatters everyone but opens up the family to a bizarre web of lies and deceit by people with sinister plans and personal grudges. The serial has a stellar cast comprising the industry’s finest artists Sawera Nadeem, Shahood Alvi, Sumbul Iqbal, Shehzad Sheikh, Saboor Aly, Ali Abbas, Raza Talish, Kashif Mehmood, Salma Hassan, Noor Ul Hassan, Shehzeen Rahat and others.   &lt;br /&gt;Starring:  &lt;br /&gt;Sawera Nadeem, Shahood Alvi, Sumbul Iqbal, Shehzad Sheikh, Saboor Aly, Ali Abbas, Raza Talish, Kashif Mehmood, Salma Hassan, Noor Ul Hassan, Shehzeen Rahat &amp;amp; Others.  &lt;br /&gt;Directed By: Saima Waseem  &lt;br /&gt;Written By: Samina Ejaz  &lt;br /&gt;Produced By: Dramebaaz &amp;amp; MD Production  &lt;br /&gt;#TumHoWajah #SaweraNadeem #ShehzadSheikh #ShahoodAlvi #SumbulIqbal #SaboorAly&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">Tum Ho Wajah, Episode 17 Promo, Official HD Video - 21 August 2020 Tum Ho Wajah is a story of lust, lies, deceit and karma. Penned by Samina Ejaz and directed by Samia Waseem, the drama serial is an intertwined story of Mansoor Ahmed, Ghafoor and Mansoor’s younger brother Murad Ahmed’s families. Mansoor Ahmed’s wife Sahiba, daughters Chanda and Sitara and sons Zain and Babar are a closed knit, typical happy middle-class family. Things seem to be working for the family until Chanda makes a terrible mistake that not only shatters everyone but opens up the family to a bizarre web of lies and deceit by people with sinister plans and personal grudges. The serial has a stellar cast comprising the industry’s finest artists Sawera Nadeem, Shahood Alvi, Sumbul Iqbal, Shehzad Sheikh, Saboor Aly, Ali Abbas, Raza Talish, Kashif Mehmood, Salma Hassan, Noor Ul Hassan, Shehzeen Rahat and others. Starring: Sawera Nadeem, Shahood Alvi, Sumbul Iqbal, Shehzad Sheikh, Saboor Aly, Ali Abbas, Raza Talish, Kashif Mehmood, Salma Hassan, Noor Ul Hassan, Shehzeen Rahat &amp;amp; Others. Directed By: Saima Waseem Written By: Samina Ejaz Produced By: Dramebaaz &amp;amp; MD Production #TumHoWajah #SaweraNadeem #ShehzadSheikh #ShahoodAlvi #SumbulIqbal #SaboorAly</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPplN1VGfCGVkR_2-/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPplN1VGfCGVkR_2-/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">16 மணிநேரம் வெள்ளத்தில் சிக்கியிருந்தவரை MI 17-விமானம் மூலம் உயிருடன் மீட்ட IAF</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/16-mi-17-iaf.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="16 மணிநேரம் வெள்ளத்தில் சிக்கியிருந்தவரை MI 17-விமானம் மூலம் உயிருடன் மீட்ட IAF" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:06:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:06:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/16-mi-17-iaf</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/16-mi-17-iaf.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;சண்டிகர் மாநிலத்தில் வெள்ளத்தின் நடுவில் சிக்கி 16 மணிநேரம் தவித்துக்கொண்டிந்தவர் இந்திய விமானப்படை விமானம் MI 17-மூலம் உயிருடன் மீட்கப்பட்டிருக்கிறார் மற்றும் MI 17 தொடர்பான சில தகவல்கள்     &lt;br /&gt;A man got stuck in heavy flow of Khutaghat Dam near Ratanpur area of Bilaspur after he jumped in the weir on August 16 evening but couldn’t get out due to heavy flow. He sat on a stone holding a tree to save himself. But due to bad weather and heavy flow of water, he couldn’t be rescued. On August 17 morning, Indian Air Force (IAF) chopper, Mi-17 came to rescue him. Miraculously, he got airlifted and was rescued safely&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Details of MI 17 Chopper    &lt;br /&gt;#IAFChopperMi17   &lt;br /&gt;#IndianArmy&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">சண்டிகர் மாநிலத்தில் வெள்ளத்தின் நடுவில் சிக்கி 16 மணிநேரம் தவித்துக்கொண்டிந்தவர் இந்திய விமானப்படை விமானம் MI 17-மூலம் உயிருடன் மீட்கப்பட்டிருக்கிறார் மற்றும் MI 17 தொடர்பான சில தகவல்கள் A man got stuck in heavy flow of Khutaghat Dam near Ratanpur area of Bilaspur after he jumped in the weir on August 16 evening but couldn’t get out due to heavy flow. He sat on a stone holding a tree to save himself. But due to bad weather and heavy flow of water, he couldn’t be rescued. On August 17 morning, Indian Air Force (IAF) chopper, Mi-17 came to rescue him. Miraculously, he got airlifted and was rescued safely Details of MI 17 Chopper #IAFChopperMi17 #IndianArmy</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPFxe1VEcAF11oIMQ/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPFxe1VEcAF11oIMQ/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Tens of thousands gather in Minsk for biggest protest in Belarus history – video</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/tens-of-thousands-gather-in-minsk-for-biggest-protest-in-belarus-histo.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tens of thousands gather in Minsk for biggest protest in Belarus history – video" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:06:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:06:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/tens-of-thousands-gather-in-minsk-for-biggest-protest-in-belarus-histo</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/tens-of-thousands-gather-in-minsk-for-biggest-protest-in-belarus-histo.html">&lt;p&gt;Belarusians assemble en masse in Minsk as an extraordinary week of rising sentiment comes to a close. ‘I made my choice and my vote was thrown in the bin, so I’ll keep coming out until our president leaves,’ said one demonstrator. Seven days after the country’s authoritarian ruler, Alexander Lukashenko, claimed to have secured 80% of the vote in a presidential election, his legitimacy is in tatters and his regime faces its biggest crisis since he came to power 26 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Belarusians assemble en masse in Minsk as an extraordinary week of rising sentiment comes to a close. ‘I made my choice and my vote was thrown in the bin, so I’ll keep coming out until our president leaves,’ said one demonstrator. Seven days after the country’s authoritarian ruler, Alexander Lukashenko, claimed to have secured 80% of the vote in a presidential election, his legitimacy is in tatters and his regime faces its biggest crisis since he came to power 26 years ago.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPhMT1VFgplF4P0ts/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPhMT1VFgplF4P0ts/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Bundelkhand में दूर होगा जल संकट, योगी सरकार का इजरायल के साथ हुआ एमओयू वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/bundelkhand.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bundelkhand में दूर होगा जल संकट, योगी सरकार का इजरायल के साथ हुआ एमओयू वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:05:09+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:05:09+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/bundelkhand</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/bundelkhand.html">&lt;p&gt;Uttar Pradesh is the largest state in the country and the water crisis in Bundelkhand region is well known. Now to solve this crisis, India’s partner has come forward to help, which till now makes the biggest contribution to the security of the country. Israel has entered into an agreement with UP after which the people of Bundelkhand will have no shortage of water. On Thursday, a deal has been reached between Israel and the Government of Uttar Pradesh.  &lt;br /&gt;उत्‍तर प्रदेश देश का सबसे बड़ा राज्‍य और यहां के बुंदलेखंड क्षेत्र में पानी का संकट जगजाहिर है। अब इस संकट को सुलझाने के लिए भारत का वह साथी मदद करने को आगे आया है जो अब तक देश की सुरक्षा में सबसे बड़ा योगदान करता है। इजरायल ने यूपी के साथ एक समझौता किया है जिसके बाद बुंदेलखंड के लोगों को पानी की कमी नहीं होगी। गुरुवार को इजरायल और उत्‍तर प्रदेश सरकार के बीच इसे लेकर एक डील हुई है।  &lt;br /&gt;#Bundelkhand #WaterCrisis #Israel&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Uttar Pradesh is the largest state in the country and the water crisis in Bundelkhand region is well known. Now to solve this crisis, India’s partner has come forward to help, which till now makes the biggest contribution to the security of the country. Israel has entered into an agreement with UP after which the people of Bundelkhand will have no shortage of water. On Thursday, a deal has been reached between Israel and the Government of Uttar Pradesh. उत्‍तर प्रदेश देश का सबसे बड़ा राज्‍य और यहां के बुंदलेखंड क्षेत्र में पानी का संकट जगजाहिर है। अब इस संकट को सुलझाने के लिए भारत का वह साथी मदद करने को आगे आया है जो अब तक देश की सुरक्षा में सबसे बड़ा योगदान करता है। इजरायल ने यूपी के साथ एक समझौता किया है जिसके बाद बुंदेलखंड के लोगों को पानी की कमी नहीं होगी। गुरुवार को इजरायल और उत्‍तर प्रदेश सरकार के बीच इसे लेकर एक डील हुई है। #Bundelkhand #WaterCrisis #Israel</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPpG71VG0SuggJci-/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPpG71VG0SuggJci-/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">ISIS के संदिग्ध आतंकी Abdul Yusuf के घर से तबाही का सामान बरामद Balrampur वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/isis-abdul-yusuf-balrampur.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ISIS के संदिग्ध आतंकी Abdul Yusuf के घर से तबाही का सामान बरामद Balrampur वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:05:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:05:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/isis-abdul-yusuf-balrampur</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/isis-abdul-yusuf-balrampur.html">&lt;p&gt;A Delhi Police Special Cell team seized around 8 to 9 kgs of explosives apart from suicide jackets and vests following a search at arrested ISIS operative Mohammad Mustakim Khan alias Abu Yusuf Khan’s house in Balrampur in Uttar Pradesh, a senior police officer said on Sunday.Watch video,    &lt;br /&gt;दिल्ली के धौला कुआं से 22 अगस्त को दिल्ली पुलिस की स्पेशल सेल ने ISIS के एक संदिग्ध आतंकी को गिरफ्तार किया था. ISIS के इस संदिग्ध आतंकी का नाम मोहम्मद मुस्तकीम उर्फ अब्दुल यूसुफ उर्फ अबू यूसुफ है. अब इस संदिग्ध आतंकी की निशानदेही पर स्पेशल सेल की टीम ने उत्तर प्रदेश के बलरामपुर स्थित उसके घर में छापेमारी की.तो दौरान स्पेशल सेल की टीम के होश उड़ गए.देखें वीडियो    &lt;br /&gt;#ISIS #Balrampur #TerroristAbdulYusuf&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">A Delhi Police Special Cell team seized around 8 to 9 kgs of explosives apart from suicide jackets and vests following a search at arrested ISIS operative Mohammad Mustakim Khan alias Abu Yusuf Khan’s house in Balrampur in Uttar Pradesh, a senior police officer said on Sunday.Watch video, दिल्ली के धौला कुआं से 22 अगस्त को दिल्ली पुलिस की स्पेशल सेल ने ISIS के एक संदिग्ध आतंकी को गिरफ्तार किया था. ISIS के इस संदिग्ध आतंकी का नाम मोहम्मद मुस्तकीम उर्फ अब्दुल यूसुफ उर्फ अबू यूसुफ है. अब इस संदिग्ध आतंकी की निशानदेही पर स्पेशल सेल की टीम ने उत्तर प्रदेश के बलरामपुर स्थित उसके घर में छापेमारी की.तो दौरान स्पेशल सेल की टीम के होश उड़ गए.देखें वीडियो #ISIS #Balrampur #TerroristAbdulYusuf</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPzB41VGbs94sGKgu/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPzB41VGbs94sGKgu/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">ಹಿಂದಿ ಹೇರಿಕೆ ವಿರುದ್ಧ HDK ಬ್ಯಾಟಿಂಗ್ Oneindia Kannada</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/hdk-oneindia-kannada.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ಹಿಂದಿ ಹೇರಿಕೆ ವಿರುದ್ಧ HDK ಬ್ಯಾಟಿಂಗ್ Oneindia Kannada" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:05:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:05:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/hdk-oneindia-kannada</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/hdk-oneindia-kannada.html">&lt;p&gt;ಹಿಂದಿ ಮಾತನಾಡಲು ಆಗದವರು ಹೊರ ಹೋಗಿ ಎನ್ನುವ ಆಯುಷ್‌ ಇಲಾಖೆಯ ಕಾರ್ಯದರ್ಶಿ ರಾಜೇಶ್‌ ಕೊಟೆಚಾ ಹೇಳಿಕೆಗೆ ಮಾಜಿ ಸಿಎಂ ಎಚ್‌.ಡಿ ಕುಮಾರಸ್ವಾಮಿ ಸರಣಿ ಟ್ವೀಟ್​ ಮೂಲಕ ಆಕ್ರೋಶ ವ್ಯಕ್ತಪಡಿಸಿದ್ದಾರೆ.  &lt;br /&gt;#HDK #Hindi  &lt;br /&gt;Former CM HD Kumaraswamy has tweeted out a statement from Ayush department secretary Rajesh Kotecha saying that those who  cannot speak Hindi should go out.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">ಹಿಂದಿ ಮಾತನಾಡಲು ಆಗದವರು ಹೊರ ಹೋಗಿ ಎನ್ನುವ ಆಯುಷ್‌ ಇಲಾಖೆಯ ಕಾರ್ಯದರ್ಶಿ ರಾಜೇಶ್‌ ಕೊಟೆಚಾ ಹೇಳಿಕೆಗೆ ಮಾಜಿ ಸಿಎಂ ಎಚ್‌.ಡಿ ಕುಮಾರಸ್ವಾಮಿ ಸರಣಿ ಟ್ವೀಟ್​ ಮೂಲಕ ಆಕ್ರೋಶ ವ್ಯಕ್ತಪಡಿಸಿದ್ದಾರೆ. #HDK #Hindi Former CM HD Kumaraswamy has tweeted out a statement from Ayush department secretary Rajesh Kotecha saying that those who cannot speak Hindi should go out.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ3811VGxugfdOL8K/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQ3811VGxugfdOL8K/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Gardeners World episode 23 2020</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/gardeners-world-episode-23-2020.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gardeners World episode 23 2020" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:04:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:04:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/gardeners-world-episode-23-2020</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/gardeners-world-episode-23-2020.html">&lt;p&gt;Gardeners World episode 23 2020: At Longmeadow, Monty plans for next spring when he plants some early-flowering wildflowers and gives his recipes for the different compost mixes he uses to take successful cuttings.  &lt;br /&gt;Last gardening post on HDclump.com:  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">Gardeners World episode 23 2020: At Longmeadow, Monty plans for next spring when he plants some early-flowering wildflowers and gives his recipes for the different compost mixes he uses to take successful cuttings. Last gardening post on HDclump.com:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPqdP1VHGfqD06arF/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPqdP1VHGfqD06arF/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">NEYMAR JR, FELIPE SIMAS E MAIS: CONFIRA AS CELEBRIDADES QUE FORAM PAIS JOVENS (2020)</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/neymar-jr-felipe-simas-e-mais-confira-as-celebridades-que-foram-pais-j.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NEYMAR JR, FELIPE SIMAS E MAIS: CONFIRA AS CELEBRIDADES QUE FORAM PAIS JOVENS (2020)" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:03:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:03:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/neymar-jr-felipe-simas-e-mais-confira-as-celebridades-que-foram-pais-j</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/neymar-jr-felipe-simas-e-mais-confira-as-celebridades-que-foram-pais-j.html">&lt;p&gt;O dia dos pais já passou, mas nunca é tarde para enaltecer alguns dos papais famosos que tanto amamos, né? Nesse especial, a CARAS preparou uma lista de algumas celebridades que conheceram a paternidade superjovens. Confira! #NeymarJr #FelipeTitto #FelipeSimas&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="fun" />
  <summary type="html">O dia dos pais já passou, mas nunca é tarde para enaltecer alguns dos papais famosos que tanto amamos, né? Nesse especial, a CARAS preparou uma lista de algumas celebridades que conheceram a paternidade superjovens. Confira! #NeymarJr #FelipeTitto #FelipeSimas</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPKOK1VHUwDy3m6Qa/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPKOK1VHUwDy3m6Qa/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Attack on Titan S1 E14 ‘Can’t Look Into His Eyes Yet: Eve of the Counterattack, ‘ Reaction &amp;amp; Review!</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/attack-on-titan-s1-e14-can-t-look-into-his-eyes-yet-eve-of-the-counter.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Attack on Titan S1 E14 ‘Can’t Look Into His Eyes Yet: Eve of the Counterattack, ‘ Reaction &amp;amp; Review!" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:03:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:03:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/attack-on-titan-s1-e14-can-t-look-into-his-eyes-yet-eve-of-the-counter</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/attack-on-titan-s1-e14-can-t-look-into-his-eyes-yet-eve-of-the-counter.html">&lt;p&gt;YouTube:   &lt;br /&gt;In this video we are reviewing Attack on Titan Season 1 Episode 14 &quot;Can’t Look Into His Eyes Yet: Eve of the Counterattack, Part 1&quot;.  A special military tribunal is called as the Military Police demand Eren’s execution, but the Scout Regiment argue that he’s a powerful resource for humankind.  &lt;br /&gt;Please don’t forget to subscribe and leave us a comment to let us know what you think!  We will see you all in our next video.   &lt;br /&gt;Join our Patreon for exclusive content, extended reactions, bloopers, and more:   &lt;br /&gt;Follow us on Instagram:  &lt;br /&gt;Kacee: @kaceecavazos   &lt;br /&gt;Anthony: @anthonyjcavazos   &lt;br /&gt;Contact Us: doscavazos@gmail.com  &lt;br /&gt;You can also find us here:  &lt;br /&gt;Bitchute:   &lt;br /&gt;Dailymotion:   &lt;br /&gt;Sign up for a free Bitchute account here:   &lt;br /&gt;If you would like to donate to our channel: paypal.me/doscavazos  &lt;br /&gt;Is there something you would like to see? Leave a request in the comments below! ↓  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;Copyright Disclaimer Under Section 107 of the Copyright Act 1976, allowance is made for &quot;fair use&quot; for purposes such as criticism, commenting, news reporting, teaching, scholarship, and research. Fair use is a use permitted by copyright statute that might otherwise be infringing.&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;Everything is about people. Everything in this life that’s worth a damn.&quot; -Eastman (The Walking Dead)  &lt;br /&gt;&quot;I have spent my whole life scared, frightened of things that could happen, might happen, might not happen, 50-years I spent like that. Finding myself awake at three in the morning. But you know what? Ever since my diagnosis, I sleep just fine. What I came to realize is that fear, that’s the worst of it. That’s the real enemy. So, get up, get out in the real world and you kick that bastard as hard you can right in the teeth.&quot; -Walter White (Breaking Bad)  &lt;br /&gt;Intro/Outro Song: Always Dreaming - Same Town Forever   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;This post may contain affiliate links. If you use one of these links to buy something we may earn a commission at no extra cost to you. Thanks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="fun" />
  <summary type="html">YouTube: In this video we are reviewing Attack on Titan Season 1 Episode 14 &quot;Can’t Look Into His Eyes Yet: Eve of the Counterattack, Part 1&quot;. A special military tribunal is called as the Military Police demand Eren’s execution, but the Scout Regiment argue that he’s a powerful resource for humankind. Please don’t forget to subscribe and leave us a comment to let us know what you think! We will see you all in our next video. Join our Patreon for exclusive content, extended reactions, bloopers, and more: Follow us on Instagram: Kacee: @kaceecavazos Anthony: @anthonyjcavazos Contact Us: doscavazos@gmail.com You can also find us here: Bitchute: Dailymotion: Sign up for a free Bitchute account here: If you would like to donate to our channel: paypal.me/doscavazos Is there something you would like to see? Leave a request in the comments below! ↓ Copyright Disclaimer Under Section 107 of the Copyright Act 1976, allowance is made for &quot;fair use&quot; for purposes such as criticism, commenting, news reporting, teaching, scholarship, and research. Fair use is a use permitted by copyright statute that might otherwise be infringing. &quot;Everything is about people. Everything in this life that’s worth a damn.&quot; -Eastman (The Walking Dead) &quot;I have spent my whole life scared, frightened of things that could happen, might happen, might not happen, 50-years I spent like that. Finding myself awake at three in the morning. But you know what? Ever since my diagnosis, I sleep just fine. What I came to realize is that fear, that’s the worst of it. That’s the real enemy. So, get up, get out in the real world and you kick that bastard as hard you can right in the teeth.&quot; -Walter White (Breaking Bad) Intro/Outro Song: Always Dreaming - Same Town Forever This post may contain affiliate links. If you use one of these links to buy something we may earn a commission at no extra cost to you. Thanks.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPUUL1VF6cSW3V95R/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPUUL1VF6cSW3V95R/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">The new Porsche Cayenne GTS Coupé in Moonlight blue Driving Video</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/the-new-porsche-cayenne-gts-coup-in-moonlight-blue-driving-video.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The new Porsche Cayenne GTS Coupé in Moonlight blue Driving Video" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:03:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:03:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/the-new-porsche-cayenne-gts-coup-in-moonlight-blue-driving-video</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/the-new-porsche-cayenne-gts-coup-in-moonlight-blue-driving-video.html">&lt;p&gt;Dynamism and exclusivity together: with the Porsche Cayenne GTS and Cayenne GTS Coupé, Porsche is supplementing its SUV line-up with two new models designed with superb driving performance in mind. Typically for the GTS models, the powertrain plays a particularly important part: instead of the 3.6-litre V6 biturbo engine from its predecessor, a V8 heart now beats once more under the bonnet of the Porsche Cayenne GTS. With an output of 338 kW (460 PS) and torque of 620 Nm, the four-litre biturbo engine offers significantly improved performance in all disciplines. Both GTS models sprint from 0 - 100 km/h in 4.5 seconds with the Sport Chrono package and have a top speed of 270 km/h. A lowered performance-oriented chassis, a unique design and enhanced equipment round off the new GTS package.  &lt;br /&gt;With the Porsche-developed four-litre V8 biturbo engine from the flagship Cayenne model, the new Porsche Cayenne GTS now delivers 14 kW (20 PS) and 20 Nm more than its predecessor. This leads to significantly improved performance, something which applies equally to the new Cayenne GTS Coupé: the standard sprint from 0 - 100 km/h is now 0.6 seconds faster than before with the Sport Chrono package. Top speed has been increased by eight km/h. At the same time, great importance has been placed on efficiency. Among other things, this has been achieved by the optimally matched Tiptronic S eight-speed automatic transmission, adaptive cylinder control, direct petrol injection with central injector position and an intelligently designed thermal management system. According to the NEDC combined cycle, the sportiest Cayenne models offer a fuel consumption of 11.4 to 11.2 l/100 km.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="auto" />
  <summary type="html">Dynamism and exclusivity together: with the Porsche Cayenne GTS and Cayenne GTS Coupé, Porsche is supplementing its SUV line-up with two new models designed with superb driving performance in mind. Typically for the GTS models, the powertrain plays a particularly important part: instead of the 3.6-litre V6 biturbo engine from its predecessor, a V8 heart now beats once more under the bonnet of the Porsche Cayenne GTS. With an output of 338 kW (460 PS) and torque of 620 Nm, the four-litre biturbo engine offers significantly improved performance in all disciplines. Both GTS models sprint from 0 - 100 km/h in 4.5 seconds with the Sport Chrono package and have a top speed of 270 km/h. A lowered performance-oriented chassis, a unique design and enhanced equipment round off the new GTS package. With the Porsche-developed four-litre V8 biturbo engine from the flagship Cayenne model, the new Porsche Cayenne GTS now delivers 14 kW (20 PS) and 20 Nm more than its predecessor. This leads to significantly improved performance, something which applies equally to the new Cayenne GTS Coupé: the standard sprint from 0 - 100 km/h is now 0.6 seconds faster than before with the Sport Chrono package. Top speed has been increased by eight km/h. At the same time, great importance has been placed on efficiency. Among other things, this has been achieved by the optimally matched Tiptronic S eight-speed automatic transmission, adaptive cylinder control, direct petrol injection with central injector position and an intelligently designed thermal management system. According to the NEDC combined cycle, the sportiest Cayenne models offer a fuel consumption of 11.4 to 11.2 l/100 km.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPlwU1VF_Ls4ELfaZ/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPlwU1VF_Ls4ELfaZ/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Police carried out raids on Wellingborough’s Hemmingwell estate last week</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/police-carried-out-raids-on-wellingborough-s-hemmingwell-estate-last-w.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Police carried out raids on Wellingborough’s Hemmingwell estate last week" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:02:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:02:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/police-carried-out-raids-on-wellingborough-s-hemmingwell-estate-last-w</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/police-carried-out-raids-on-wellingborough-s-hemmingwell-estate-last-w.html">&lt;p&gt;Here’s footage of the drugs raids from Northants Police&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Police carried out raids on Wellingborough’s Hemmingwell estate last week&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Police carried out raids on Wellingborough’s Hemmingwell estate last week&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Police carried out raids on Wellingborough's Hemmingwell estate last week&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Here’s footage of the drugs raids from Northants PolicePolice carried out raids on Wellingborough’s Hemmingwell estate last week Police carried out raids on Wellingborough’s Hemmingwell estate last week Police carried out raids on Wellingborough's Hemmingwell estate last week</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQCqu1VHIVoj9GvGZ/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQCqu1VHIVoj9GvGZ/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Guy Carlier : sa touchante déclaration à son fils Carlito</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/guy-carlier-sa-touchante-d-claration-son-fils-carlito.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Guy Carlier : sa touchante déclaration à son fils Carlito" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:02:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:02:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/guy-carlier-sa-touchante-d-claration-son-fils-carlito</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/guy-carlier-sa-touchante-d-claration-son-fils-carlito.html">&lt;p&gt;Guy Carlier : sa touchante déclaration   &lt;br /&gt;à son fils Carlito.  &lt;br /&gt;Comme tous les parents, pères et mères confondus, Guy Carlier éprouve des regrets. .  &lt;br /&gt;Il s’est notamment exprimé sur l’éducation de ses fils aînés, à savoir Stéphane et Raphaël, lui qui se cache derrière   &lt;br /&gt;le pseudonyme de Carlito sur YouTube. .  &lt;br /&gt;Lorsqu’il était enfant, ce dernier était déposé à trois rues   &lt;br /&gt;de son école pour que ses camarades ne croisent jamais   &lt;br /&gt;le journaliste de 71 ans.  &lt;br /&gt;Je m’en veux. Avec mon plus grand enfant, c’était encore pire : je n’étais pas là, Guy Carlier.  &lt;br /&gt;Des liens que le trio d’hommes n’évoque jamais. .  &lt;br /&gt;Je regrette la souffrance que j’ai imposée à Carlito. C’est désastreux. C’est une défaite dans ma vie, Guy Carlier .  &lt;br /&gt;Ce fut finalement avec son troisième fils, Antoine,   &lt;br /&gt;né en 2007 qu’il a pu se faire pardonner, renforçant   &lt;br /&gt;dans la foulée ses liens avec ses deux premiers fils. .  &lt;br /&gt;Carlito a sa vie de star, mais il est là. Il envoie un mot ‘love dad’ et ça me suffit. Stéphane, c’est pareil mais il est assez solitaire. Quand je l’ai eu, j’avais 20 ans et n’avait pas une image désastreuse. J’étais beaucoup en voyage, j’étais absent. Il a été construit, lui, par sa mère, Guy Carlier&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Guy Carlier : sa touchante déclaration à son fils Carlito. Comme tous les parents, pères et mères confondus, Guy Carlier éprouve des regrets. . Il s’est notamment exprimé sur l’éducation de ses fils aînés, à savoir Stéphane et Raphaël, lui qui se cache derrière le pseudonyme de Carlito sur YouTube. . Lorsqu’il était enfant, ce dernier était déposé à trois rues de son école pour que ses camarades ne croisent jamais le journaliste de 71 ans. Je m’en veux. Avec mon plus grand enfant, c’était encore pire : je n’étais pas là, Guy Carlier. Des liens que le trio d’hommes n’évoque jamais. . Je regrette la souffrance que j’ai imposée à Carlito. C’est désastreux. C’est une défaite dans ma vie, Guy Carlier . Ce fut finalement avec son troisième fils, Antoine, né en 2007 qu’il a pu se faire pardonner, renforçant dans la foulée ses liens avec ses deux premiers fils. . Carlito a sa vie de star, mais il est là. Il envoie un mot ‘love dad’ et ça me suffit. Stéphane, c’est pareil mais il est assez solitaire. Quand je l’ai eu, j’avais 20 ans et n’avait pas une image désastreuse. J’étais beaucoup en voyage, j’étais absent. Il a été construit, lui, par sa mère, Guy Carlier</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBmK1VHFhu80ZeB1/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQBmK1VHFhu80ZeB1/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">All angles: Bubba gets bumped on the last lap at Daytona</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/all-angles-bubba-gets-bumped-on-the-last-lap-at-daytona.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="All angles: Bubba gets bumped on the last lap at Daytona" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:01:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:01:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/all-angles-bubba-gets-bumped-on-the-last-lap-at-daytona</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/all-angles-bubba-gets-bumped-on-the-last-lap-at-daytona.html">&lt;p&gt;Watch Bubba Wallace’s day fall apart as he takes a shot from Alex Bowman, who got shoved by Joey Logano on the last lap of the Cup Series race at the Daytona Road Course.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">Watch Bubba Wallace’s day fall apart as he takes a shot from Alex Bowman, who got shoved by Joey Logano on the last lap of the Cup Series race at the Daytona Road Course.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPJZM1VFdGuuosxh7/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPJZM1VFdGuuosxh7/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">CWC Meeting के बाद Kapil Sibal के नए Tweet पर क्यों मचा बवाल Sonia Gandhi वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/cwc-meeting-kapil-sibal-tweet-sonia-gandhi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CWC Meeting के बाद Kapil Sibal के नए Tweet पर क्यों मचा बवाल Sonia Gandhi वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T10:01:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T10:01:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/cwc-meeting-kapil-sibal-tweet-sonia-gandhi</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/cwc-meeting-kapil-sibal-tweet-sonia-gandhi.html">&lt;p&gt;The ‘Mahabharata’ going on in the Congress is not over yet. Congress is constantly getting jerks on shocks, then there is increasing infighting in the Congress. Rebels in the Congress for the last several months are not ending. The result of this is that today the Congress is standing at this point. Where the end of any party begins. Know now why there was a ruckus with Kapil Sibal’s tweet?    &lt;br /&gt;कांग्रेस में चल रही महाभारत का अभी अंत नहीं हुआ है. कांग्रेस को लगातार झटके पर झटके लग रहे हैं तो कहीं कांग्रेस में अंदरूनी कलह बढ़ता जा रहा है. पिछले कई महीनों से कांग्रेस में उठे बगावती सुर खत्म नहीं हो रहे. इसी का नतीजा है कि आज कांग्रेस इस मोड़ पर खड़ी है. जहां से किसी भी पार्टी के अंत की शुरुआत होती है. जानिए अब कपिल सिब्बल के ट्वीट से क्यों मचा बवाल?    &lt;br /&gt;#Congress #KapilSibal #CWCMeeting&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The ‘Mahabharata’ going on in the Congress is not over yet. Congress is constantly getting jerks on shocks, then there is increasing infighting in the Congress. Rebels in the Congress for the last several months are not ending. The result of this is that today the Congress is standing at this point. Where the end of any party begins. Know now why there was a ruckus with Kapil Sibal’s tweet? कांग्रेस में चल रही महाभारत का अभी अंत नहीं हुआ है. कांग्रेस को लगातार झटके पर झटके लग रहे हैं तो कहीं कांग्रेस में अंदरूनी कलह बढ़ता जा रहा है. पिछले कई महीनों से कांग्रेस में उठे बगावती सुर खत्म नहीं हो रहे. इसी का नतीजा है कि आज कांग्रेस इस मोड़ पर खड़ी है. जहां से किसी भी पार्टी के अंत की शुरुआत होती है. जानिए अब कपिल सिब्बल के ट्वीट से क्यों मचा बवाल? #Congress #KapilSibal #CWCMeeting</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQB111VHDUVNqXmY8/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQB111VHDUVNqXmY8/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 </feed>