<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
<updated>2020-08-26T06:18:50+03:00</updated>
<id>https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml</id>
<title type="html">Adowsom</title>
<subtitle>Duct Tape is like the force. There's a dark side and a light side, and it holds the universe together.</subtitle>
<author>
 <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
 <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
 <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
</author>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Corona Crisis : Education Ministry ने स्कूली बच्चों के लिए जारी किए ये निर्देश वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/corona-crisis-education-ministry.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Corona Crisis : Education Ministry ने स्कूली बच्चों के लिए जारी किए ये निर्देश वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:48:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:48:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/corona-crisis-education-ministry</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/corona-crisis-education-ministry.html">&lt;p&gt;The number of corona infected in the country is continuously increasing. Now the situation is that about 70 thousand new cases are coming out. But in the meantime the process of unlocking continues in the country. Meanwhile, the Ministry of Education has issued guidelines for the promotion of education for school children. Union Education Minister Ramesh Pokhriyal Nishank issued education promotion guidelines here.    &lt;br /&gt;देश में कोरोना संक्रमित की संख्या में लगातार इजाफा हो रहा है. अब हालात ये है कि करीब 70 हजार नए मामले सामने आ रहे है. लेकिन इस बीच अनलॉक की प्रक्रिया देश में जारी है . इस बीच शिक्षा मंत्रालय ने स्कूली बच्चों के लिए शिक्षा संवर्धन दिशा-निर्देश जारी किए है. केंद्रीय शिक्षा मंत्री रमेश पोखरियाल निशंक ने यहां शिक्षा संवर्धन दिशा-निर्देश जारी किए.    &lt;br /&gt;#EducationMinistry #RameshPokhriyalNishank #oneindiahindi&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The number of corona infected in the country is continuously increasing. Now the situation is that about 70 thousand new cases are coming out. But in the meantime the process of unlocking continues in the country. Meanwhile, the Ministry of Education has issued guidelines for the promotion of education for school children. Union Education Minister Ramesh Pokhriyal Nishank issued education promotion guidelines here. देश में कोरोना संक्रमित की संख्या में लगातार इजाफा हो रहा है. अब हालात ये है कि करीब 70 हजार नए मामले सामने आ रहे है. लेकिन इस बीच अनलॉक की प्रक्रिया देश में जारी है . इस बीच शिक्षा मंत्रालय ने स्कूली बच्चों के लिए शिक्षा संवर्धन दिशा-निर्देश जारी किए है. केंद्रीय शिक्षा मंत्री रमेश पोखरियाल निशंक ने यहां शिक्षा संवर्धन दिशा-निर्देश जारी किए. #EducationMinistry #RameshPokhriyalNishank #oneindiahindi</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPhNO1VHSrcHZj7-U/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPhNO1VHSrcHZj7-U/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">L’OMS met en garde: ‘même un vaccin ne mettra pas fin au Covid-19’</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/l-oms-met-en-garde-m-me-un-vaccin-ne-mettra-pas-fin-au-covid-19.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="L’OMS met en garde: ‘même un vaccin ne mettra pas fin au Covid-19’" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:48:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:48:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/l-oms-met-en-garde-m-me-un-vaccin-ne-mettra-pas-fin-au-covid-19</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/l-oms-met-en-garde-m-me-un-vaccin-ne-mettra-pas-fin-au-covid-19.html">&lt;p&gt;Selon l’Organisation mondiale de la santé, seuls les comportements des uns et des autres face au virus peuvent mettre fin à la pandémie.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Selon l’Organisation mondiale de la santé, seuls les comportements des uns et des autres face au virus peuvent mettre fin à la pandémie.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPi1S1VFiPyfgQIfC/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPi1S1VFiPyfgQIfC/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Top 20 John Oliver Moments</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/top-20-john-oliver-moments.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top 20 John Oliver Moments" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:47:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:47:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/top-20-john-oliver-moments</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/top-20-john-oliver-moments.html">&lt;p&gt;These John Oliver moments left us all wiser. For this list, we’ll be breaking down the funniest, most memorable and culturally relevant segments from the HBO news satire program.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">These John Oliver moments left us all wiser. For this list, we’ll be breaking down the funniest, most memorable and culturally relevant segments from the HBO news satire program.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPikk1VHMRrS6gOix/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPikk1VHMRrS6gOix/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Pemandangan Udara Detik-detik Bangunan Dibakar di Wisconsin</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/pemandangan-udara-detik-detik-bangunan-dibakar-di-wisconsin.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pemandangan Udara Detik-detik Bangunan Dibakar di Wisconsin" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:47:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:47:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/pemandangan-udara-detik-detik-bangunan-dibakar-di-wisconsin</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/pemandangan-udara-detik-detik-bangunan-dibakar-di-wisconsin.html">&lt;p&gt;Para pengunjuk rasa menyerang dan membakar beberapa kendaraan dan bangunan, termasuk toko dan Danish Brotherhood Lodge di Kenosha, Wisconsin.   &lt;br /&gt;Hal ini merupakan malam kedua kerusuhan sejak peristiwa polisi yang menembak seorang pria kulit hitam, Jacob Blake, pada Minggu (23/8/2020). Blake ditembak sebanyak tujuh kali dibagian punggung di Kenosha, Wisconsin.  &lt;br /&gt;Masyarakat AS marah dan ngamuk atas kekerasan rasial yang lagi-lagi diinisiasi polisi kulit putih. Kawasan Kenosha, Wisconsin bahkan harus memberlakukan jam malam darurat akibat kejadian itu. (Anadolu Agency/Sibel Uygun/Tafyun Coskun/Firdaus Wajidi)  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Para pengunjuk rasa menyerang dan membakar beberapa kendaraan dan bangunan, termasuk toko dan Danish Brotherhood Lodge di Kenosha, Wisconsin. Hal ini merupakan malam kedua kerusuhan sejak peristiwa polisi yang menembak seorang pria kulit hitam, Jacob Blake, pada Minggu (23/8/2020). Blake ditembak sebanyak tujuh kali dibagian punggung di Kenosha, Wisconsin. Masyarakat AS marah dan ngamuk atas kekerasan rasial yang lagi-lagi diinisiasi polisi kulit putih. Kawasan Kenosha, Wisconsin bahkan harus memberlakukan jam malam darurat akibat kejadian itu. (Anadolu Agency/Sibel Uygun/Tafyun Coskun/Firdaus Wajidi)</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQC_d1VHHJHO3suv3/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQC_d1VHHJHO3suv3/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Scottish NHS Staff protest For Better Pay</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/scottish-nhs-staff-protest-for-better-pay.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Scottish NHS Staff protest For Better Pay" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:46:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:46:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/scottish-nhs-staff-protest-for-better-pay</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/scottish-nhs-staff-protest-for-better-pay.html">&lt;p&gt;NHS Staff Strike For Better Pay  &lt;br /&gt;GLASGOW, SCOTLAND - AUGUST 18: NHS nurses stage a protest outside Queen Elizabeth University Hospital after being left out of a public sector pay rise on August 18, 2020 in Glasgow, United Kingdom. NHS staff across Scotland are protesting today demanding an early salary increase after they were not included in the government’s above-inflation coronavirus pay rise for public sector workers because of a three-year pay deal negotiated in 2018&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">NHS Staff Strike For Better Pay GLASGOW, SCOTLAND - AUGUST 18: NHS nurses stage a protest outside Queen Elizabeth University Hospital after being left out of a public sector pay rise on August 18, 2020 in Glasgow, United Kingdom. NHS staff across Scotland are protesting today demanding an early salary increase after they were not included in the government’s above-inflation coronavirus pay rise for public sector workers because of a three-year pay deal negotiated in 2018</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPSOJ1VF1Ma1qoFQy/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPSOJ1VF1Ma1qoFQy/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Bermain Ketapel dan Balogo, Latih Ketangkasan dan Konsentrasi</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/bermain-ketapel-dan-balogo-latih-ketangkasan-dan-konsentrasi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bermain Ketapel dan Balogo, Latih Ketangkasan dan Konsentrasi" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:46:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:46:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/bermain-ketapel-dan-balogo-latih-ketangkasan-dan-konsentrasi</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/bermain-ketapel-dan-balogo-latih-ketangkasan-dan-konsentrasi.html">&lt;p&gt;BANJARMASIN, KOMPAS.TV - Anak indonesia punya beragam permainan dan juga alat perlengkapannya. Diantaranya adalah bermain ketapel dan balogo.   &lt;br /&gt;Permainan ini biasanya dimainkan anak-anak seperti di Banjarmasin, Kalimantan Selatan untuk mengisi waktu di sela-sela permainan lain.   &lt;br /&gt;Namun seiring perkembangan zaman permainan ini juga sudah mulai  jarang dilakukan anak anak terutama di kawasan pusat kota.   &lt;br /&gt;Melestarikan permainan tradisional ini, aktivis Kampung Permainan Tradisional Banua Pendamai, Banjarmasin tetap  berupaya menjaganya.   &lt;br /&gt;Permainan ketapel dimainkan dengan menembakkan peluru buatan dengan pelontar dari karet yang dikaitkan pada batang ketapel berbahan kayu berbentuk seperti huruf Y.   &lt;br /&gt;Permainan ini ditujukan untuk menguji ketangkasan dan berkonsentrasi dengan berfokus ke satu sasaran.   &lt;br /&gt;&quot;Jadi kita mengajak anak-anak mengadakan ketangkasan untuk membidik satu sasaran dengan berkonsentrasi,&quot; ucap Inisiator Kampung Permainan Tradisional Banua Pendamai, Muhammad Suriani kepada jurnalis kompas.tv.   &lt;br /&gt;Tak hanya itu, mereka juga memainkan balogo. Ini adalah permainan uji tepat bidikan. Dengan cara meruntuhkan logo yang disusun berbaris dari jarak jauh menggunakan alat bernama penapak.   &lt;br /&gt;Dengan terus mengenalkan dan memberikan edukasi pada anak agar tetap melakukan permainan tradisional  diharapkan tumbuhkembang anak semakin tinggi beriringan dengan minat dan kemampuan bermain dengan game online yang marak di era modern ini.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">BANJARMASIN, KOMPAS.TV - Anak indonesia punya beragam permainan dan juga alat perlengkapannya. Diantaranya adalah bermain ketapel dan balogo. Permainan ini biasanya dimainkan anak-anak seperti di Banjarmasin, Kalimantan Selatan untuk mengisi waktu di sela-sela permainan lain. Namun seiring perkembangan zaman permainan ini juga sudah mulai jarang dilakukan anak anak terutama di kawasan pusat kota. Melestarikan permainan tradisional ini, aktivis Kampung Permainan Tradisional Banua Pendamai, Banjarmasin tetap berupaya menjaganya. Permainan ketapel dimainkan dengan menembakkan peluru buatan dengan pelontar dari karet yang dikaitkan pada batang ketapel berbahan kayu berbentuk seperti huruf Y. Permainan ini ditujukan untuk menguji ketangkasan dan berkonsentrasi dengan berfokus ke satu sasaran. &quot;Jadi kita mengajak anak-anak mengadakan ketangkasan untuk membidik satu sasaran dengan berkonsentrasi,&quot; ucap Inisiator Kampung Permainan Tradisional Banua Pendamai, Muhammad Suriani kepada jurnalis kompas.tv. Tak hanya itu, mereka juga memainkan balogo. Ini adalah permainan uji tepat bidikan. Dengan cara meruntuhkan logo yang disusun berbaris dari jarak jauh menggunakan alat bernama penapak. Dengan terus mengenalkan dan memberikan edukasi pada anak agar tetap melakukan permainan tradisional diharapkan tumbuhkembang anak semakin tinggi beriringan dengan minat dan kemampuan bermain dengan game online yang marak di era modern ini.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4Xa1VGyD9szVeOY/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4Xa1VGyD9szVeOY/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Samson Waithaka’s placards taken down by security within the Ministry of Health</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/samson-waithaka-s-placards-taken-down-by-security-within-the-ministry.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Samson Waithaka’s placards taken down by security within the Ministry of Health" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:45:09+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:45:09+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/samson-waithaka-s-placards-taken-down-by-security-within-the-ministry</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/samson-waithaka-s-placards-taken-down-by-security-within-the-ministry.html">&lt;p&gt;Samson Waithaka who has been spreading covid-19 awareness had his placards taken down by security guards of the Ministry of Health claiming that he has been causing disturbance within the facility.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Samson Waithaka who has been spreading covid-19 awareness had his placards taken down by security guards of the Ministry of Health claiming that he has been causing disturbance within the facility.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPZdd1VFMZAjU3I1T/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPZdd1VFMZAjU3I1T/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">STAR TREK - The Coolest COLLECTIBLE TRADING CARDS Out There (Presented by eBay)</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/star-trek-the-coolest-collectible-trading-cards-out-there-presented-by.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="STAR TREK - The Coolest COLLECTIBLE TRADING CARDS Out There (Presented by eBay)" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:44:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:44:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/star-trek-the-coolest-collectible-trading-cards-out-there-presented-by</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/star-trek-the-coolest-collectible-trading-cards-out-there-presented-by.html">&lt;p&gt;Forget space being the final frontier, we all know the true undiscovered country is collecting. And when it comes to fandom there is none greater than Star Trek. After all, Trekkies (or Trekkers, they are awesome either way) were the first fans in history to revive a fandom that would have otherwise vanished into the past.  &lt;br /&gt;Since the first Star Trek trading cards were produced, there have been millions of the things circulated across the globe based on every era of the franchise. They endure to this day.  &lt;br /&gt;Read on:   &lt;br /&gt;Follow Den of Geek for more!  &lt;br /&gt;Website:   &lt;br /&gt;Facebook:   &lt;br /&gt;Twitter:   &lt;br /&gt;Instagram:   &lt;br /&gt;Tumblr:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">Forget space being the final frontier, we all know the true undiscovered country is collecting. And when it comes to fandom there is none greater than Star Trek. After all, Trekkies (or Trekkers, they are awesome either way) were the first fans in history to revive a fandom that would have otherwise vanished into the past. Since the first Star Trek trading cards were produced, there have been millions of the things circulated across the globe based on every era of the franchise. They endure to this day. Read on: Follow Den of Geek for more! Website: Facebook: Twitter: Instagram: Tumblr:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPqmp1VH2LcqFMuYC/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPqmp1VH2LcqFMuYC/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Sanjay Dutt की wife Maanayata ने बताया कहां होगा Husband का इलाज, Fans से की ये अपील वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/sanjay-dutt-wife-maanayata-husband-fans.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sanjay Dutt की wife Maanayata ने बताया कहां होगा Husband का इलाज, Fans से की ये अपील वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:44:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:44:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/sanjay-dutt-wife-maanayata-husband-fans</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/sanjay-dutt-wife-maanayata-husband-fans.html">&lt;p&gt;Actor Sanjay Dutt’s wife Maanayata in a statement said While our family is shaken up we are determined to fight tooth and nail. Maanayata also thanked well-wishers for showering Sanjay Dutt with a whole lot of love after he announced he has taken a break from work because of medical treatment.    &lt;br /&gt;बॉलीवुड के लिए साल 2020 काफी बुरा जा रहा है। पिछले तीन महीने में कई दिग्गज कलाकारों का निधन हुआ, तो वहीं अमिताभ बच्चन समेत कई कलाकार बीमार पड़े। एक हफ्ते पहले संजय दत्त को भी सांस लेने में दिक्कत हो रही थी, जिसके बाद उन्हें मुंबई के एक अस्पताल में भर्ती करवाया गया। इस दौरान पता चला कि संजय दत्त को फेफड़ों का कैंसर है। जिसके बाद कयास लगाए जा रहे थे कि वो इलाज के लिए विदेश जाएंगे    &lt;br /&gt;#SanjayDutt #MaanayataDutt #KokilabenHospital&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Actor Sanjay Dutt’s wife Maanayata in a statement said While our family is shaken up we are determined to fight tooth and nail. Maanayata also thanked well-wishers for showering Sanjay Dutt with a whole lot of love after he announced he has taken a break from work because of medical treatment. बॉलीवुड के लिए साल 2020 काफी बुरा जा रहा है। पिछले तीन महीने में कई दिग्गज कलाकारों का निधन हुआ, तो वहीं अमिताभ बच्चन समेत कई कलाकार बीमार पड़े। एक हफ्ते पहले संजय दत्त को भी सांस लेने में दिक्कत हो रही थी, जिसके बाद उन्हें मुंबई के एक अस्पताल में भर्ती करवाया गया। इस दौरान पता चला कि संजय दत्त को फेफड़ों का कैंसर है। जिसके बाद कयास लगाए जा रहे थे कि वो इलाज के लिए विदेश जाएंगे #SanjayDutt #MaanayataDutt #KokilabenHospital</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPYmB1VFKrqRLwqaZ/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPYmB1VFKrqRLwqaZ/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Δείτε τον Αλεξάνδρου πριν από έντεκα χρόνια όταν πόζαρε για το Next Top Model!</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/next-top-model.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Δείτε τον Αλεξάνδρου πριν από έντεκα χρόνια όταν πόζαρε για το Next Top Model!" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:43:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:43:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/next-top-model</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/next-top-model.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Δείτε τον Αλεξάνδρου πριν από έντεκα χρόνια όταν πόζαρε για το Next Top Model!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Δείτε τον Αλεξάνδρου πριν από έντεκα χρόνια όταν πόζαρε για το Next Top Model!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Δείτε τον Αλεξάνδρου πριν από έντεκα χρόνια όταν πόζαρε για το Next Top Model!&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tv" />
  <summary type="html">Δείτε τον Αλεξάνδρου πριν από έντεκα χρόνια όταν πόζαρε για το Next Top Model! Δείτε τον Αλεξάνδρου πριν από έντεκα χρόνια όταν πόζαρε για το Next Top Model! Δείτε τον Αλεξάνδρου πριν από έντεκα χρόνια όταν πόζαρε για το Next Top Model!</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPgCO1VFeSMc2klM5/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPgCO1VFeSMc2klM5/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Tech Jungle: realme 6 Pro Review</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/tech-jungle-realme-6-pro-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tech Jungle: realme 6 Pro Review" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:43:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:43:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/tech-jungle-realme-6-pro-review</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/tech-jungle-realme-6-pro-review.html">&lt;p&gt;The Realme 6 Pro is the company’s latest mid-ranger. It’s got the top specs, a stunning design, high refresh rate display, and an extremely versatile set of cameras.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tech" />
  <summary type="html">The Realme 6 Pro is the company’s latest mid-ranger. It’s got the top specs, a stunning design, high refresh rate display, and an extremely versatile set of cameras.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPnQm1VG-puX84sFk/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPnQm1VG-puX84sFk/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">‘Deux personnes ont dit sur ce plateau qui ne fallait pas dire autre choses qu’un seul type d’information..(.) Nous n’avons pas une épidémie infectieuses..nous avons une épidémie d’angoisse.’</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/deux-personnes-ont-dit-sur-ce-plateau-qui-ne-fallait-pas-dire-autre-ch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="‘Deux personnes ont dit sur ce plateau qui ne fallait pas dire autre choses qu’un seul type d’information..(.) Nous n’avons pas une épidémie infectieuses..nous avons une épidémie d’angoisse.’" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:42:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:42:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/deux-personnes-ont-dit-sur-ce-plateau-qui-ne-fallait-pas-dire-autre-ch</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/deux-personnes-ont-dit-sur-ce-plateau-qui-ne-fallait-pas-dire-autre-ch.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;‘Deux personnes ont dit sur ce plateau qui ne fallait pas dire autre choses qu’un seul type d’information..(.) Nous n’avons pas une épidémie infectieuses..nous avons une épidémie d’angoisse.’&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;‘Deux personnes ont dit sur ce plateau qui ne fallait pas dire autre choses qu’un seul type d’information..(.) Nous n’avons pas une épidémie infectieuses..nous avons une épidémie d’angoisse.’&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;'Deux personnes ont dit sur ce plateau qui ne fallait pas dire autre choses qu'un seul type d'information..(.) Nous n'avons pas une épidémie infectieuses..nous avons une épidémie d’angoisse.'&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">‘Deux personnes ont dit sur ce plateau qui ne fallait pas dire autre choses qu’un seul type d’information..(.) Nous n’avons pas une épidémie infectieuses..nous avons une épidémie d’angoisse.’ ‘Deux personnes ont dit sur ce plateau qui ne fallait pas dire autre choses qu’un seul type d’information..(.) Nous n’avons pas une épidémie infectieuses..nous avons une épidémie d’angoisse.’ 'Deux personnes ont dit sur ce plateau qui ne fallait pas dire autre choses qu'un seul type d'information..(.) Nous n'avons pas une épidémie infectieuses..nous avons une épidémie d’angoisse.'</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4-C1VGzRFYanaYD/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ4-C1VGzRFYanaYD/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">CHARACTER ஆ எந்த நடிகராலயும் மாற முடியாது Mrs. PRITHAM CHAT PART-01 FILMIBEAT TAMIL</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/character-mrs-pritham-chat-part-01-filmibeat-tamil.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CHARACTER ஆ எந்த நடிகராலயும் மாற முடியாது Mrs. PRITHAM CHAT PART-01 FILMIBEAT TAMIL" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:42:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:42:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/character-mrs-pritham-chat-part-01-filmibeat-tamil</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/character-mrs-pritham-chat-part-01-filmibeat-tamil.html">&lt;p&gt;#PSYCHOMOVIE  &lt;br /&gt;#PRITHAM  &lt;br /&gt;#ACTINGTECHNICS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;CHARACTER ஆ எந்த நடிகராலயும் மாற முடியாது Mrs. PRITHAM CHAT PART-01 FILMIBEAT TAMIL&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;CHARACTER ஆ எந்த நடிகராலயும் மாற முடியாது Mrs. PRITHAM CHAT PART-01 FILMIBEAT TAMIL&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;CHARACTER ஆ எந்த நடிகராலயும் மாற முடியாது Mrs. PRITHAM CHAT PART-01 FILMIBEAT TAMIL&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="people" />
  <summary type="html">#PSYCHOMOVIE #PRITHAM #ACTINGTECHNICSCHARACTER ஆ எந்த நடிகராலயும் மாற முடியாது Mrs. PRITHAM CHAT PART-01 FILMIBEAT TAMIL CHARACTER ஆ எந்த நடிகராலயும் மாற முடியாது Mrs. PRITHAM CHAT PART-01 FILMIBEAT TAMIL CHARACTER ஆ எந்த நடிகராலயும் மாற முடியாது Mrs. PRITHAM CHAT PART-01 FILMIBEAT TAMIL</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPYH31VFIBm7d4wVe/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPYH31VFIBm7d4wVe/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">SAFC’s suitors: All the groups and individuals ‘interested’ in buying the club from Stewart Donald</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/safc-s-suitors-all-the-groups-and-individuals-interested-in-buying-the.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SAFC’s suitors: All the groups and individuals ‘interested’ in buying the club from Stewart Donald" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:42:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:42:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/safc-s-suitors-all-the-groups-and-individuals-interested-in-buying-the</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/safc-s-suitors-all-the-groups-and-individuals-interested-in-buying-the.html">&lt;p&gt;SAFC’s suitors: All the groups and individuals ‘interested’ in buying the club from Stewart Donald&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;SAFC’s suitors: All the groups and individuals ‘interested’ in buying the club from Stewart Donald&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;SAFC’s suitors: All the groups and individuals ‘interested’ in buying the club from Stewart Donald&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;SAFC's suitors: All the groups and individuals 'interested' in buying the club from Stewart Donald&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">SAFC’s suitors: All the groups and individuals ‘interested’ in buying the club from Stewart DonaldSAFC’s suitors: All the groups and individuals ‘interested’ in buying the club from Stewart Donald SAFC’s suitors: All the groups and individuals ‘interested’ in buying the club from Stewart Donald SAFC's suitors: All the groups and individuals 'interested' in buying the club from Stewart Donald</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPQ6I1VEz3JatWkov/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPQ6I1VEz3JatWkov/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">New Hyundai i20 and i20 Active - Highlights</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/new-hyundai-i20-and-i20-active-highlights.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Hyundai i20 and i20 Active - Highlights" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:41:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:41:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/new-hyundai-i20-and-i20-active-highlights</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/new-hyundai-i20-and-i20-active-highlights.html">&lt;p&gt;The new i20 Active’s unique crossover design sets it apart from the rest of the i20 range. With rugged good looks highlighted by skid plates, protective cladding and a higher ground clearance – this model comes ready for adventure.  &lt;br /&gt;Ready for adventure, the i20 Active’s exterior features rugged design elements like skid plates, circular fog lamps and protective cladding. On the inside, the combination of space and customisable styling elements come together creating a calm interior for all your trips through the urban jungle.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="auto" />
  <summary type="html">The new i20 Active’s unique crossover design sets it apart from the rest of the i20 range. With rugged good looks highlighted by skid plates, protective cladding and a higher ground clearance – this model comes ready for adventure. Ready for adventure, the i20 Active’s exterior features rugged design elements like skid plates, circular fog lamps and protective cladding. On the inside, the combination of space and customisable styling elements come together creating a calm interior for all your trips through the urban jungle.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPEX01VEd9sLaxWuu/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPEX01VEd9sLaxWuu/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">For Indigenous Teens, Pandemic Lockdowns Challenge Mental Health</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/for-indigenous-teens-pandemic-lockdowns-challenge-mental-health.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="For Indigenous Teens, Pandemic Lockdowns Challenge Mental Health" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:41:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:41:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/for-indigenous-teens-pandemic-lockdowns-challenge-mental-health</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/for-indigenous-teens-pandemic-lockdowns-challenge-mental-health.html">&lt;p&gt;Indigenous peoples make up nearly 5% of Canada’s population, and disparities in young peoples’ educational and recreational opportunities are acute.  &lt;br /&gt;Housing is inadequate on many reserves with some remote communities cut off from the rest of Canada for weeks or months during the year.  &lt;br /&gt;Among Canada’s First Nations’ youth, depression and suicide is already over 3 times the average of non-indigenous people.  &lt;br /&gt;CNN reports the pandemic is adding a layer of risk to young indigenous lives. Government officials say the impact on mental health may linger for years.  &lt;br /&gt;For months this year, children, parents, and entire rural, indigenous communities were left without the support they had fought so hard to establish.  &lt;br /&gt;Living in a reserve it gets depressing over time. You begin to feel isolated, you find yourself parting ways with your friends. It takes a huge toll on your health. Farrah Dixon Norway House Cree Nation, Manitoba, Canada&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Indigenous peoples make up nearly 5% of Canada’s population, and disparities in young peoples’ educational and recreational opportunities are acute. Housing is inadequate on many reserves with some remote communities cut off from the rest of Canada for weeks or months during the year. Among Canada’s First Nations’ youth, depression and suicide is already over 3 times the average of non-indigenous people. CNN reports the pandemic is adding a layer of risk to young indigenous lives. Government officials say the impact on mental health may linger for years. For months this year, children, parents, and entire rural, indigenous communities were left without the support they had fought so hard to establish. Living in a reserve it gets depressing over time. You begin to feel isolated, you find yourself parting ways with your friends. It takes a huge toll on your health. Farrah Dixon Norway House Cree Nation, Manitoba, Canada</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPC6e1VEQgKjHtozg/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPC6e1VEQgKjHtozg/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">How dummy pedestrians help test car safety systems</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/how-dummy-pedestrians-help-test-car-safety-systems.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How dummy pedestrians help test car safety systems" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:39:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:39:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/how-dummy-pedestrians-help-test-car-safety-systems</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/how-dummy-pedestrians-help-test-car-safety-systems.html">&lt;p&gt;AB Dynamics employs many tools to test advanced driver assistance systems (ADAS) according to rigorous standards by automotive safety agencies like Euro NCAP and NHTSA. One tool is the Soft Pedestrian Target, or SPT, that simulates a pedestrian in a real-world environment.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tech" />
  <summary type="html">AB Dynamics employs many tools to test advanced driver assistance systems (ADAS) according to rigorous standards by automotive safety agencies like Euro NCAP and NHTSA. One tool is the Soft Pedestrian Target, or SPT, that simulates a pedestrian in a real-world environment.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPV4t1VFrA_fmBd3L/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPV4t1VFrA_fmBd3L/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Kids Are ‘Silent Spreaders’ Of COVID-19</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/kids-are-silent-spreaders-of-covid-19.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kids Are ‘Silent Spreaders’ Of COVID-19" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:38:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:38:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/kids-are-silent-spreaders-of-covid-19</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/kids-are-silent-spreaders-of-covid-19.html">&lt;p&gt;It is believed that children may be less likely than adults to become severely sick with COVID-19.  &lt;br /&gt;However, mounting evidence shows they may be major silent spreaders of the virus.  &lt;br /&gt;A study published this week in the Journal of Pediatrics looked at nearly 200 children.  &lt;br /&gt;All came to urgent care clinics or hospitals with suspected COVID-19, reports HuffPost.  &lt;br /&gt;Almost 50 of them tested positive but most of the children were not particularly ill.  &lt;br /&gt;Only about half who tested positive for had a fever, for example.  &lt;br /&gt;Many had no symptoms, but had been in contact with someone who had the virus.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">It is believed that children may be less likely than adults to become severely sick with COVID-19. However, mounting evidence shows they may be major silent spreaders of the virus. A study published this week in the Journal of Pediatrics looked at nearly 200 children. All came to urgent care clinics or hospitals with suspected COVID-19, reports HuffPost. Almost 50 of them tested positive but most of the children were not particularly ill. Only about half who tested positive for had a fever, for example. Many had no symptoms, but had been in contact with someone who had the virus.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPqjc1VGFp1LuPCOC/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPqjc1VGFp1LuPCOC/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Critérium du Dauphiné 2020 - Race highlights</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/crit-rium-du-dauphin-2020-race-highlights.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Critérium du Dauphiné 2020 - Race highlights" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:38:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:38:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/crit-rium-du-dauphin-2020-race-highlights</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/crit-rium-du-dauphin-2020-race-highlights.html">&lt;p&gt;After 5 days of racing, the winner of the Critérium du Dauphiné 2020 is MARTINEZ POVEDA Daniel !   &lt;br /&gt;Now it’s time to enjoy the best moments of the race.  &lt;br /&gt;General Ranking:   &lt;br /&gt;1 - MARTINEZ POVEDA Daniel (EF PRO CYCLING)  &lt;br /&gt;2 - PINOT Thibaut (GROUPAMA - FDJ)  &lt;br /&gt;3 - MARTIN Guillaume (COFIDIS)  &lt;br /&gt;More information on:  &lt;br /&gt;www.criterium-du-dauphine.fr   &lt;br /&gt;www.facebook.com/CriteriumDuDauphine   &lt;br /&gt;www.twitter.com/dauphine   &lt;br /&gt;www.instagram.com/criteriumdudauphine   &lt;br /&gt;© Amaury Sport Organisation - www.aso.fr&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">After 5 days of racing, the winner of the Critérium du Dauphiné 2020 is MARTINEZ POVEDA Daniel ! Now it’s time to enjoy the best moments of the race. General Ranking: 1 - MARTINEZ POVEDA Daniel (EF PRO CYCLING) 2 - PINOT Thibaut (GROUPAMA - FDJ) 3 - MARTIN Guillaume (COFIDIS) More information on: www.criterium-du-dauphine.fr www.facebook.com/CriteriumDuDauphine www.twitter.com/dauphine www.instagram.com/criteriumdudauphine © Amaury Sport Organisation - www.aso.fr</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPBdC1VEibeRhBNK1/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPBdC1VEibeRhBNK1/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 72 ( Phần 2 ) Full</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/h-nh-ph-c-mu-n-m-ng-t-p-72-ph-n-2-full.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 72 ( Phần 2 ) Full" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:37:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:37:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/h-nh-ph-c-mu-n-m-ng-t-p-72-ph-n-2-full</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/h-nh-ph-c-mu-n-m-ng-t-p-72-ph-n-2-full.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 72 ( Phần 2 )&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Full  &lt;br /&gt;Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 72 ( Phần 2 )&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Full&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="shortfilms" />
  <summary type="html">Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 72 ( Phần 2 )   Full Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 72 ( Phần 2 )   Full</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPB2Q1VEPPA-4FnJS/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPB2Q1VEPPA-4FnJS/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 79 ( Phần 2 ) Full</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/h-nh-ph-c-mu-n-m-ng-t-p-79-ph-n-2-full.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 79 ( Phần 2 ) Full" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:37:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:37:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/h-nh-ph-c-mu-n-m-ng-t-p-79-ph-n-2-full</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/h-nh-ph-c-mu-n-m-ng-t-p-79-ph-n-2-full.html">&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 79 ( Phần 2 )&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Full  &lt;br /&gt;Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 79 ( Phần 2 )&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Full&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="shortfilms" />
  <summary type="html">Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 79 ( Phần 2 )   Full Hạnh Phúc Muộn Màng - Tập 79 ( Phần 2 )   Full</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SP-HG1VGqTU0GVJ2N/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SP-HG1VGqTU0GVJ2N/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">The 10 Best Cruisers Under $10,000</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/the-10-best-cruisers-under-10-000.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 10 Best Cruisers Under $10,000" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:37:02+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:37:02+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/the-10-best-cruisers-under-10-000</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/the-10-best-cruisers-under-10-000.html">&lt;p&gt;Cruiser motorcycles are notoriously expensive. Here are the 10 best cruisers you can buy right now for less than 10 grand.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="tech" />
  <summary type="html">Cruiser motorcycles are notoriously expensive. Here are the 10 best cruisers you can buy right now for less than 10 grand.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPTp11VF43125cvfM/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPTp11VF43125cvfM/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">PAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONS</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/paw-patrol-toys-tracing-letters-with-colorful-crayons.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONS" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:36:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:36:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/paw-patrol-toys-tracing-letters-with-colorful-crayons</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/paw-patrol-toys-tracing-letters-with-colorful-crayons.html">&lt;p&gt;PAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;PAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;PAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONS&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;PAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="kids" />
  <summary type="html">PAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONSPAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONS PAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONS PAW PATROL Toys Tracing Letters with COLORFUL CRAYONS</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPJ7G1VEm2idnRPR0/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPJ7G1VEm2idnRPR0/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Rahul Gandhi का Modi Government पर Employment को लेकर हमला, जानिए क्या बोले वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/rahul-gandhi-modi-government-employment.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rahul Gandhi का Modi Government पर Employment को लेकर हमला, जानिए क्या बोले वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:35:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:35:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/rahul-gandhi-modi-government-employment</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/rahul-gandhi-modi-government-employment.html">&lt;p&gt;Due to the economic recession and the economy facing Corona, the Congress is constantly engaged in besieging the Modi government at the Center on the issue of fast rising unemployment. In this sequence, former Congress President Rahul Gandhi once again targeted the Central Government. Rahul Gandhi said my country cannot provide employment to the youth, if you do not agree with this, just wait for 6-7 months.  &lt;br /&gt;आर्थिक मंदी और कोरोना की मार झेल रही अर्थव्यवस्था के कारण तेजी से बढ़ती बेरोजगारी के मुद्दे पर कांग्रेस लगातार केंद्र की मोदी सरकार को घेरने में लगी है. इस क्रम में कांग्रेस के पूर्व अध्यक्ष राहुल गांधी ने एक फिर केंद्र सरकार पर निशाना साधा. राहुल गांधी ने मेरा देश युवाओं को रोजगार मुहैया नहीं करा सकता, अगर आप इससे सहमत नहीं हैं तो बस 6-7 महीनों तक इंतजार करें.   &lt;br /&gt;#RahulGandhi #ModiGovernment #oneindiahindi&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Due to the economic recession and the economy facing Corona, the Congress is constantly engaged in besieging the Modi government at the Center on the issue of fast rising unemployment. In this sequence, former Congress President Rahul Gandhi once again targeted the Central Government. Rahul Gandhi said my country cannot provide employment to the youth, if you do not agree with this, just wait for 6-7 months. आर्थिक मंदी और कोरोना की मार झेल रही अर्थव्यवस्था के कारण तेजी से बढ़ती बेरोजगारी के मुद्दे पर कांग्रेस लगातार केंद्र की मोदी सरकार को घेरने में लगी है. इस क्रम में कांग्रेस के पूर्व अध्यक्ष राहुल गांधी ने एक फिर केंद्र सरकार पर निशाना साधा. राहुल गांधी ने मेरा देश युवाओं को रोजगार मुहैया नहीं करा सकता, अगर आप इससे सहमत नहीं हैं तो बस 6-7 महीनों तक इंतजार करें. #RahulGandhi #ModiGovernment #oneindiahindi</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPfdG1VFdP1lIcv3O/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPfdG1VFdP1lIcv3O/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Wonder Woman 1984 - New TV Spot - DC FanDome Gal Gadot</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/wonder-woman-1984-new-tv-spot-dc-fandome-gal-gadot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wonder Woman 1984 - New TV Spot - DC FanDome Gal Gadot" />
  <published>2020-08-26T05:35:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-26T05:35:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/wonder-woman-1984-new-tv-spot-dc-fandome-gal-gadot</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/wonder-woman-1984-new-tv-spot-dc-fandome-gal-gadot.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wonder Woman 1984 - New TV Spot - DC FanDome Gal Gadot&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Wonder Woman 1984 - New TV Spot - DC FanDome Gal Gadot&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Wonder Woman 1984 - New TV Spot - DC FanDome Gal Gadot&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="shortfilms" />
  <summary type="html">Wonder Woman 1984 - New TV Spot - DC FanDome Gal Gadot Wonder Woman 1984 - New TV Spot - DC FanDome Gal Gadot Wonder Woman 1984 - New TV Spot - DC FanDome Gal Gadot</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPnTq1VGtin0uI2aW/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPnTq1VGtin0uI2aW/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 </feed>