<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
<link href="https://adowsom.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
<updated>2020-08-29T00:18:50+03:00</updated>
<id>https://adowsom.github.io/feed.xml</id>
<title type="html">Adowsom</title>
<subtitle>Duct Tape is like the force. There's a dark side and a light side, and it holds the universe together.</subtitle>
<author>
 <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
 <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
 <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
</author>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Comment aller en date en pleine pandémie ?</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/comment-aller-en-date-en-pleine-pand-mie.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Comment aller en date en pleine pandémie ?" />
  <published>2020-08-29T00:14:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-29T00:14:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/comment-aller-en-date-en-pleine-pand-mie</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/comment-aller-en-date-en-pleine-pand-mie.html">&lt;p&gt;Comment aller en date en pleine pandémie ?  &lt;br /&gt;La pandémie du coronavirus a radicalement changé chaque aspect  &lt;br /&gt;de notre vie quotidienne, y compris les rencontres.  &lt;br /&gt;Voici les nouvelles règles à garder à l’esprit pour faire de nouvelle rencontre en toute sécurité.  &lt;br /&gt;Essayez de ne pas avoir de préjugés…  &lt;br /&gt;Les gens ont une large gamme de confort et inconfort lié à la proximité physique et au contact. C’est une excellente idée de demander directement à votre date leurs propres frontières de distanciation sociale.  &lt;br /&gt;Si vous passez d’un date virtuel à un date réel, demandez-lui ce qu’il en est pour lui, du contact physique.  &lt;br /&gt;Les experts disent clarifier les limites  &lt;br /&gt;est plus que jamais indispensable.  &lt;br /&gt;Oui, vous devriez porter un masque…  &lt;br /&gt;C’est une excellente idée d’être franc avec votre date sur vos intentions de porter un masque. Vous pourriez même vous entraîner à demander à votre date de porter son masque s’il refuse.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">Comment aller en date en pleine pandémie ? La pandémie du coronavirus a radicalement changé chaque aspect de notre vie quotidienne, y compris les rencontres. Voici les nouvelles règles à garder à l’esprit pour faire de nouvelle rencontre en toute sécurité. Essayez de ne pas avoir de préjugés… Les gens ont une large gamme de confort et inconfort lié à la proximité physique et au contact. C’est une excellente idée de demander directement à votre date leurs propres frontières de distanciation sociale. Si vous passez d’un date virtuel à un date réel, demandez-lui ce qu’il en est pour lui, du contact physique. Les experts disent clarifier les limites est plus que jamais indispensable. Oui, vous devriez porter un masque… C’est une excellente idée d’être franc avec votre date sur vos intentions de porter un masque. Vous pourriez même vous entraîner à demander à votre date de porter son masque s’il refuse.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPov91VHXDO-jZpQA/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPov91VHXDO-jZpQA/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">It Pays To Know</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/it-pays-to-know.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It Pays To Know" />
  <published>2020-08-29T00:11:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-29T00:11:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/it-pays-to-know</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/it-pays-to-know.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;It Pays To Know&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;It Pays To Know&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;It Pays To Know&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">It Pays To Know It Pays To Know It Pays To Know</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQQMa1VHsq-6q6CJ2/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQQMa1VHsq-6q6CJ2/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Still Game Season 8 Episode 1 FLY FISHING REACTION</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/still-game-season-8-episode-1-fly-fishing-reaction.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Still Game Season 8 Episode 1 FLY FISHING REACTION" />
  <published>2020-08-29T00:09:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-29T00:09:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/still-game-season-8-episode-1-fly-fishing-reaction</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/still-game-season-8-episode-1-fly-fishing-reaction.html">&lt;p&gt;Newly created if you would like to support the channel fam please Donate to our Patreon at  Also I want you all to know if you can not afford to donate that is ok! One of the best forms of support fam is liking, commenting and sharing my videos. Thank you all truly. Wolf Pack 4 Life.    &lt;br /&gt;Here is some of our social media below:   &lt;br /&gt;Twitch ►    &lt;br /&gt;Twitter ►    &lt;br /&gt;Instagram ►    &lt;br /&gt;Facebook ►    &lt;br /&gt;MERCH ►    &lt;br /&gt;Amazon Wishlist ►    &lt;br /&gt;JOIN THE DISCORD:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="fun" />
  <summary type="html">Newly created if you would like to support the channel fam please Donate to our Patreon at Also I want you all to know if you can not afford to donate that is ok! One of the best forms of support fam is liking, commenting and sharing my videos. Thank you all truly. Wolf Pack 4 Life. Here is some of our social media below: Twitch ► Twitter ► Instagram ► Facebook ► MERCH ► Amazon Wishlist ► JOIN THE DISCORD:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQK9D1VI6WbYh2uOb/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQK9D1VI6WbYh2uOb/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Vijaysethupathi &amp;amp; Parthiban Book Launch • சென்னையின் பொக்கிஷம்</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/vijaysethupathi-parthiban-book-launch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vijaysethupathi &amp;amp; Parthiban Book Launch • சென்னையின் பொக்கிஷம்" />
  <published>2020-08-29T00:08:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-29T00:08:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/vijaysethupathi-parthiban-book-launch</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/vijaysethupathi-parthiban-book-launch.html">&lt;p&gt;#Vijaysethupathi  &lt;br /&gt;#Parthiban  &lt;br /&gt;சென்னையின் பெருமையை எடுத்துகாட்டடும் வகையில் வெளியான புத்தக விழாவில் கலந்து கொண்ட விஜய் சேதுபதி, பார்த்திபன்  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">#Vijaysethupathi #Parthiban சென்னையின் பெருமையை எடுத்துகாட்டடும் வகையில் வெளியான புத்தக விழாவில் கலந்து கொண்ட விஜய் சேதுபதி, பார்த்திபன்</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPpms1VG1DY4_lyi3/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPpms1VG1DY4_lyi3/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">VID-20200820-WA0000</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/vid-20200820-wa0000.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="VID-20200820-WA0000" />
  <published>2020-08-29T00:00:20+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-29T00:00:20+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/vid-20200820-wa0000</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/vid-20200820-wa0000.html">&lt;p&gt;दुकान में जुआ खेलते 46 गिरफ्तार, 84 हजार जब्त  &lt;br /&gt;- खाईवाली कर रहे 14 जनों से 61 हजार रुपए जब्त  &lt;br /&gt;जोधपुर.  &lt;br /&gt;ताश के पत्तों व गुब्बा खाई करने वालों के खिलाफ पुलिस ने बुधवार को सूरसागर में कालूराम की बावड़ी और बासनी में पशु आहार की फैक्ट्री के सामने दबिश देकर साठ लोगों को गिरफ्तार कर 1.45 लाख रुपए जब्त कर साठ व्यक्तियों को गिरफ्तार किया। सूरसागर व बासनी थाने में अलग-अलग मामले दर्ज किए गए हैं।  &lt;br /&gt;पुलिस उपायुक्त (पश्चिम) आलोक श्रीवास्तव ने बताया कि सूरसागर थानान्तर्गत कालूराम की बावड़ी के पास सिथत आनंदसिंह उर्फ सेठू सोलंकी की दुकान में बड़े स्तर पर जुआघर संचालित होने की सूचना मिली। एसीपी (प्रतापनगर) नीरज शर्मा व सरदारपुरा थानाधिकारी लिखमाराम के नेतृत्व में डीएसटी प्रभारी एसआई सरजिल मलिक व टीम ने वहां दबिश दी।  &lt;br /&gt;ताश के पत्तों से जुआ खेल रहे आनंदसिंह उर्फ सेठू, गेनाराम, भागीरथ, भैराराम, श्रवण, नरपत, टीकू, सुनील, पप्पूराम, धन्नाराम, अशोक, मोहम्मद उमर, देवेन्द्र, मनीष, साऊराम, गणपतलाल, फिरोज खान, कैलाश उर्फ लाला, दीपक सोलंकी, धीरेन्द्र, मोहसिन, राजू, राहुल, महेन्द्र, सोनाराम, सतीश, रवि, भगवानसिंह, मनोहरसिंह, ओमप्रकाश, नेमीचंद, राजूराम, राजेन्द्र, फुसााम, जेठूसिंह, सूर्यदेव उर्फ जज्जा, जगदीश, सोनू, सत्यम, रतनाराम, रहिश अहमद, हनवंतसिंह, एेजाज, जगदीश व धन्नूराम को गिरफ्तार किया गया। एसीपी नीरज शर्मा ने बताया कि आरोपियों के कब्जे से दांव पर लगे ८४ हजार रुपए व ताश के पत्ते जब्त किए गए। आरोपियों को पकड़कर थाने ले जाने के लिए पुलिस को सिटी बस की व्यवस्था करनी पड़ी।  &lt;br /&gt;उधर, बासनी थानाधिकारी देवेन्द्रसिंह ने बताया कि सालावास रोड पर पशु आहार फैक्ट्री के सामने खाईवाली कर रहे मनीष से २४३६५ रुपए, नरेन्द्र से २३५३०, दिनेश से १३३६० रुपए जब्त किए गए। इनके साथ मौजूद उमेश, दिनेश, सन्नी कुमार, नरेन्द्र, प्रकाश, नटवरदास, ईश्वर, रामनिवास, मुकेशदास व चंपालाल को भी गिरफ्तार किया गया।&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">दुकान में जुआ खेलते 46 गिरफ्तार, 84 हजार जब्त - खाईवाली कर रहे 14 जनों से 61 हजार रुपए जब्त जोधपुर. ताश के पत्तों व गुब्बा खाई करने वालों के खिलाफ पुलिस ने बुधवार को सूरसागर में कालूराम की बावड़ी और बासनी में पशु आहार की फैक्ट्री के सामने दबिश देकर साठ लोगों को गिरफ्तार कर 1.45 लाख रुपए जब्त कर साठ व्यक्तियों को गिरफ्तार किया। सूरसागर व बासनी थाने में अलग-अलग मामले दर्ज किए गए हैं। पुलिस उपायुक्त (पश्चिम) आलोक श्रीवास्तव ने बताया कि सूरसागर थानान्तर्गत कालूराम की बावड़ी के पास सिथत आनंदसिंह उर्फ सेठू सोलंकी की दुकान में बड़े स्तर पर जुआघर संचालित होने की सूचना मिली। एसीपी (प्रतापनगर) नीरज शर्मा व सरदारपुरा थानाधिकारी लिखमाराम के नेतृत्व में डीएसटी प्रभारी एसआई सरजिल मलिक व टीम ने वहां दबिश दी। ताश के पत्तों से जुआ खेल रहे आनंदसिंह उर्फ सेठू, गेनाराम, भागीरथ, भैराराम, श्रवण, नरपत, टीकू, सुनील, पप्पूराम, धन्नाराम, अशोक, मोहम्मद उमर, देवेन्द्र, मनीष, साऊराम, गणपतलाल, फिरोज खान, कैलाश उर्फ लाला, दीपक सोलंकी, धीरेन्द्र, मोहसिन, राजू, राहुल, महेन्द्र, सोनाराम, सतीश, रवि, भगवानसिंह, मनोहरसिंह, ओमप्रकाश, नेमीचंद, राजूराम, राजेन्द्र, फुसााम, जेठूसिंह, सूर्यदेव उर्फ जज्जा, जगदीश, सोनू, सत्यम, रतनाराम, रहिश अहमद, हनवंतसिंह, एेजाज, जगदीश व धन्नूराम को गिरफ्तार किया गया। एसीपी नीरज शर्मा ने बताया कि आरोपियों के कब्जे से दांव पर लगे ८४ हजार रुपए व ताश के पत्ते जब्त किए गए। आरोपियों को पकड़कर थाने ले जाने के लिए पुलिस को सिटी बस की व्यवस्था करनी पड़ी। उधर, बासनी थानाधिकारी देवेन्द्रसिंह ने बताया कि सालावास रोड पर पशु आहार फैक्ट्री के सामने खाईवाली कर रहे मनीष से २४३६५ रुपए, नरेन्द्र से २३५३०, दिनेश से १३३६० रुपए जब्त किए गए। इनके साथ मौजूद उमेश, दिनेश, सन्नी कुमार, नरेन्द्र, प्रकाश, नटवरदास, ईश्वर, रामनिवास, मुकेशदास व चंपालाल को भी गिरफ्तार किया गया।</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPb671VIBR-K8rEWz/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPb671VIBR-K8rEWz/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">NEWS: What stocks should you consider buying?</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/news-what-stocks-should-you-consider-buying.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NEWS: What stocks should you consider buying?" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:58:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:58:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/news-what-stocks-should-you-consider-buying</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/news-what-stocks-should-you-consider-buying.html">&lt;p&gt;UOB Asset Management (Malaysia) presents its list of preferred stocks to invest in during a pandemic.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">UOB Asset Management (Malaysia) presents its list of preferred stocks to invest in during a pandemic.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQJRH1VHasrsAkt8K/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQJRH1VHasrsAkt8K/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">10 Most Expensive Designer Slippers Seen on Local Celebrities</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/10-most-expensive-designer-slippers-seen-on-local-celebrities.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Most Expensive Designer Slippers Seen on Local Celebrities" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:58:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:58:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/10-most-expensive-designer-slippers-seen-on-local-celebrities</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/10-most-expensive-designer-slippers-seen-on-local-celebrities.html">&lt;p&gt;When it comes to celebrity fashion, one prominent trend that most celebs have embraced is designer slippers. Perhaps these stylish doyennes miss dressing up in heels or boots when they head outside, so they’re finding sartorial solace in designer slippers. They’re wearing them with polished pieces—think babydoll dresses, puff sleeve frocks, and tonal OOTDs.   &lt;br /&gt;Below, we’ve rounded up the most expensive designer slippers and slides as seen on your favorite celebrities:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">When it comes to celebrity fashion, one prominent trend that most celebs have embraced is designer slippers. Perhaps these stylish doyennes miss dressing up in heels or boots when they head outside, so they’re finding sartorial solace in designer slippers. They’re wearing them with polished pieces—think babydoll dresses, puff sleeve frocks, and tonal OOTDs. Below, we’ve rounded up the most expensive designer slippers and slides as seen on your favorite celebrities:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQc3r1VIJg_LiydJ3/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQc3r1VIJg_LiydJ3/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Unlock-4 : School-College खुलने को लेकर Health Ministry ने दिया ये जवाब वनइंडिया हिंदी</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/unlock-4-school-college-health-ministry.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unlock-4 : School-College खुलने को लेकर Health Ministry ने दिया ये जवाब वनइंडिया हिंदी" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:56:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:56:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/unlock-4-school-college-health-ministry</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/unlock-4-school-college-health-ministry.html">&lt;p&gt;The lockdown was announced across the country after the rapidly growing Corona cases. Now the unlocking process is going on in the country. In such a situation, the question in everyone’s mind is, will the government open schools and colleges that have been closed for 6 months? Before the guidelines issued by the Home Ministry, the Health Ministry has made it clear on Tuesday that there are no instructions from the government to open schools and colleges.    &lt;br /&gt;तेजी से बढ़ रहे कोरोना मामलों के बाद पूरे देश में लॉकडाउन की घोषणा की गई थी. अब देश में अनलॉक की प्रक्रिया चल रही है.  ऐसे में सबके मन में यही सवाल है कि क्या 6 महीने से बंद पड़े स्कूलों और कॉलेजों को सरकार खोलेगी? गृह मंत्रालय की ओर से जारी होने वाली गाइडलाइंस से पहले स्वास्थ्य मंत्रालय ने मंगलवार को साफ कर दिया है कि सरकार की ओर से स्कूल और कॉलेज खोलने को लेकर कोई निर्देश नहीं हैं.    &lt;br /&gt;#Unlock-4  #SchoolCollege #oneindiahindi&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">The lockdown was announced across the country after the rapidly growing Corona cases. Now the unlocking process is going on in the country. In such a situation, the question in everyone’s mind is, will the government open schools and colleges that have been closed for 6 months? Before the guidelines issued by the Home Ministry, the Health Ministry has made it clear on Tuesday that there are no instructions from the government to open schools and colleges. तेजी से बढ़ रहे कोरोना मामलों के बाद पूरे देश में लॉकडाउन की घोषणा की गई थी. अब देश में अनलॉक की प्रक्रिया चल रही है. ऐसे में सबके मन में यही सवाल है कि क्या 6 महीने से बंद पड़े स्कूलों और कॉलेजों को सरकार खोलेगी? गृह मंत्रालय की ओर से जारी होने वाली गाइडलाइंस से पहले स्वास्थ्य मंत्रालय ने मंगलवार को साफ कर दिया है कि सरकार की ओर से स्कूल और कॉलेज खोलने को लेकर कोई निर्देश नहीं हैं. #Unlock-4 #SchoolCollege #oneindiahindi</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQDW81VHILm0gBQxc/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQDW81VHILm0gBQxc/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Kamala Harris Becomes 1st Black and South Asian Woman To Be Nominated To Major Party’s National Ticket</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/kamala-harris-becomes-1st-black-and-south-asian-woman-to-be-nominated.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kamala Harris Becomes 1st Black and South Asian Woman To Be Nominated To Major Party’s National Ticket" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:48:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:48:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/kamala-harris-becomes-1st-black-and-south-asian-woman-to-be-nominated</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/kamala-harris-becomes-1st-black-and-south-asian-woman-to-be-nominated.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kamala Harris Becomes 1st Black and South Asian Woman To Be Nominated To Major Party’s National Ticket&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Kamala Harris Becomes 1st Black and South Asian Woman To Be Nominated To Major Party’s National Ticket&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Kamala Harris Becomes 1st Black and South Asian Woman To Be Nominated To Major Party’s National Ticket&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Kamala Harris Becomes 1st Black and South Asian Woman To Be Nominated To Major Party’s National Ticket Kamala Harris Becomes 1st Black and South Asian Woman To Be Nominated To Major Party’s National Ticket Kamala Harris Becomes 1st Black and South Asian Woman To Be Nominated To Major Party’s National Ticket</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPpfY1VG4JcpGcKRI/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPpfY1VG4JcpGcKRI/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Donald Trump RNC fact check</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/donald-trump-rnc-fact-check.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Donald Trump RNC fact check" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:42:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:42:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/donald-trump-rnc-fact-check</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/donald-trump-rnc-fact-check.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Donald Trump RNC fact check&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Donald Trump RNC fact check&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Donald Trump RNC fact check&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Donald Trump RNC fact check Donald Trump RNC fact check Donald Trump RNC fact check</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQY3I1VI8_pTPbhB6/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQY3I1VI8_pTPbhB6/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Months After Rishi Kapoor’s Demise, Wife Neetu To Start Shooting?</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/months-after-rishi-kapoor-s-demise-wife-neetu-to-start-shooting.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Months After Rishi Kapoor’s Demise, Wife Neetu To Start Shooting?" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:42:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:42:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/months-after-rishi-kapoor-s-demise-wife-neetu-to-start-shooting</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/months-after-rishi-kapoor-s-demise-wife-neetu-to-start-shooting.html">&lt;p&gt;Neetu Kapoor has signed her first film after Rishi Kapoor’s demise. #NeetuKapoor #RishiKapoor #RanbirKapoor  &lt;br /&gt;Log On To Our Official Website :   &lt;br /&gt;For More Such News &amp;amp; Gossips Subscribe now! :   &lt;br /&gt;Lehren On Podcast:   &lt;br /&gt;Download The ‘Lehren App’:   &lt;br /&gt;Facebook :   &lt;br /&gt;Twitter:&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="people" />
  <summary type="html">Neetu Kapoor has signed her first film after Rishi Kapoor’s demise. #NeetuKapoor #RishiKapoor #RanbirKapoor Log On To Our Official Website : For More Such News &amp;amp; Gossips Subscribe now! : Lehren On Podcast: Download The ‘Lehren App’: Facebook : Twitter:</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPYCO1VFTKQCShhmT/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPYCO1VFTKQCShhmT/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Tom Cruise Watches Tenet on ‘Big Screen,’ Surprises Moviegoers at London Theatre</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/tom-cruise-watches-tenet-on-big-screen-surprises-moviegoers-at-london.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tom Cruise Watches Tenet on ‘Big Screen,’ Surprises Moviegoers at London Theatre" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:41:04+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:41:04+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/tom-cruise-watches-tenet-on-big-screen-surprises-moviegoers-at-london</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/tom-cruise-watches-tenet-on-big-screen-surprises-moviegoers-at-london.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tom Cruise Watches Tenet on ‘Big Screen,’ Surprises Moviegoers at London Theatre&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Tom Cruise Watches Tenet on ‘Big Screen,’ Surprises Moviegoers at London Theatre&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Tom Cruise Watches Tenet on 'Big Screen,' Surprises Moviegoers at London Theatre&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="shortfilms" />
  <summary type="html">Tom Cruise Watches Tenet on ‘Big Screen,’ Surprises Moviegoers at London Theatre Tom Cruise Watches Tenet on ‘Big Screen,’ Surprises Moviegoers at London Theatre Tom Cruise Watches Tenet on 'Big Screen,' Surprises Moviegoers at London Theatre</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQIhi1VHwEpwOPDDn/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQIhi1VHwEpwOPDDn/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">All Authoritarian Systems are Inherently Leftist</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/all-authoritarian-systems-are-inherently-leftist.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="All Authoritarian Systems are Inherently Leftist" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:41:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:41:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/all-authoritarian-systems-are-inherently-leftist</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/all-authoritarian-systems-are-inherently-leftist.html">&lt;p&gt;If a state, or any other empowered entity, has the ability to dissolve contracts, confiscate property, command production or its cessation, the system must necessarily be leftist; since at most, in such a system, however capitalistic in name it may be, those enterprises are merely a farce.  &lt;br /&gt;Website:   &lt;br /&gt;Merch:   &lt;br /&gt;Support via donation:  &lt;br /&gt;Patreon:   &lt;br /&gt;Subscribestar:   &lt;br /&gt;My books:  &lt;br /&gt;Blogger:   &lt;br /&gt;Wordpress:   &lt;br /&gt;My other platforms:  &lt;br /&gt;Twitter:   &lt;br /&gt;Gab:   &lt;br /&gt;Facebook:   &lt;br /&gt;Minds:   &lt;br /&gt;Bitchute:   &lt;br /&gt;Dailymotion:   &lt;br /&gt;Brighteon:   &lt;br /&gt;LBRY:   &lt;br /&gt;BTC: 17q1BfF2up8orEKN8DQgpEPX83RfbAZ5QL  &lt;br /&gt;ETH: 0x956e7aF6706C3b5E2cf7e15c16c7018c4f42aF79  &lt;br /&gt;LTC: LQNJed6vDhR4U4LB7g8jGep4UQ7yeqJdPw&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">If a state, or any other empowered entity, has the ability to dissolve contracts, confiscate property, command production or its cessation, the system must necessarily be leftist; since at most, in such a system, however capitalistic in name it may be, those enterprises are merely a farce. Website: Merch: Support via donation: Patreon: Subscribestar: My books: Blogger: Wordpress: My other platforms: Twitter: Gab: Facebook: Minds: Bitchute: Dailymotion: Brighteon: LBRY: BTC: 17q1BfF2up8orEKN8DQgpEPX83RfbAZ5QL ETH: 0x956e7aF6706C3b5E2cf7e15c16c7018c4f42aF79 LTC: LQNJed6vDhR4U4LB7g8jGep4UQ7yeqJdPw</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPy861VGYyuchl04T/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPy861VGYyuchl04T/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Féminicides : en 2019, 146 femmes ont été tuées par leur conjoint ou ex</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/f-minicides-en-2019-146-femmes-ont-t-tu-es-par-leur-conjoint-ou-ex.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Féminicides : en 2019, 146 femmes ont été tuées par leur conjoint ou ex" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:35:07+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:35:07+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/f-minicides-en-2019-146-femmes-ont-t-tu-es-par-leur-conjoint-ou-ex</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/f-minicides-en-2019-146-femmes-ont-t-tu-es-par-leur-conjoint-ou-ex.html">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;C’est le nombre de décès liés aux violences conjugales recensés par la police et la gendarmerie en 2019. 84 % des victimes sont des femmes. Et 88 % des criminels sont des hommes.  &lt;br /&gt;Retrouver toutes les infos sur la vidéo sur :&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">C’est le nombre de décès liés aux violences conjugales recensés par la police et la gendarmerie en 2019. 84 % des victimes sont des femmes. Et 88 % des criminels sont des hommes. Retrouver toutes les infos sur la vidéo sur :</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPXT51VFLUe26wkO1/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPXT51VFLUe26wkO1/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">4 Orang Di Universitas Mulawarman Positif Covid-19</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/4-orang-di-universitas-mulawarman-positif-covid-19.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="4 Orang Di Universitas Mulawarman Positif Covid-19" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:35:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:35:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/4-orang-di-universitas-mulawarman-positif-covid-19</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/4-orang-di-universitas-mulawarman-positif-covid-19.html">&lt;p&gt;SAMARINDA, KOMPAS.TV  Sebelumnya, rektor universitas mulawarman Samarinda sudah mengeluarkan rilis terkait 4 orang di lingkungan universitas yang terkonfirmasi positif covid-19, antara lain 1 mahasiswa 1 dosen dan 2 staf universitas untuk itu pihak universitas telah melakukan kebijakan untuk work from home bagi seluruh karyawan dan juga para dosen.   &lt;br /&gt;Kendati demikian dinas kesehatan Kota Samarinda belum menentukan apakah universitas mulawarman Samarinda menjadi kluster baru penyebaran virus corona.   &lt;br /&gt;Untuk itu, pihak satgas covid-19 Samarinda akan segera melakukan treking kepada mereka yang melakukan kontak erat terhadap 4 orang yang terkonfirmasi positif covid-19.   &lt;br /&gt;Tim satgas juga menghimbau agar para staf dan dosen yang kontak dengan pasien dan mendapat gejala yang mengarah ke unsur covid-19, segera melaporkan ke commend center 112 agar segera dilakukan penanganan lebih lanjut.   &lt;br /&gt;Saat ini, ke-4 pasien terkonfirmasi positif covid-19 sudah melakukan karantina mandiri di rumah pribadi.   &lt;br /&gt;#4OrangPositif#LingkunganUnmul#WorkFromHome   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">SAMARINDA, KOMPAS.TV Sebelumnya, rektor universitas mulawarman Samarinda sudah mengeluarkan rilis terkait 4 orang di lingkungan universitas yang terkonfirmasi positif covid-19, antara lain 1 mahasiswa 1 dosen dan 2 staf universitas untuk itu pihak universitas telah melakukan kebijakan untuk work from home bagi seluruh karyawan dan juga para dosen. Kendati demikian dinas kesehatan Kota Samarinda belum menentukan apakah universitas mulawarman Samarinda menjadi kluster baru penyebaran virus corona. Untuk itu, pihak satgas covid-19 Samarinda akan segera melakukan treking kepada mereka yang melakukan kontak erat terhadap 4 orang yang terkonfirmasi positif covid-19. Tim satgas juga menghimbau agar para staf dan dosen yang kontak dengan pasien dan mendapat gejala yang mengarah ke unsur covid-19, segera melaporkan ke commend center 112 agar segera dilakukan penanganan lebih lanjut. Saat ini, ke-4 pasien terkonfirmasi positif covid-19 sudah melakukan karantina mandiri di rumah pribadi. #4OrangPositif#LingkunganUnmul#WorkFromHome</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQEal1VHKd4q3wEyl/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQEal1VHKd4q3wEyl/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">La recherche d’emploi quand on est en vacances</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/la-recherche-d-emploi-quand-on-est-en-vacances.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="La recherche d’emploi quand on est en vacances" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:34:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:34:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/la-recherche-d-emploi-quand-on-est-en-vacances</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/la-recherche-d-emploi-quand-on-est-en-vacances.html">&lt;p&gt;Vous êtes à la recherche d’un emploi mais vous craignez que la période estivale ne soit un frein ?  &lt;br /&gt;Détrompez-vous ! , Les vacances d’été peuvent être le moment idéal pour décrocher un nouveau travail.  &lt;br /&gt;Moins de concurrence : , Durant cette période, on constate moins de postulants. Résultat : Cela fait plus de chances pour vous de vous faire remarquer !  &lt;br /&gt;1. Soignez vos candidatures  &lt;br /&gt;Prenez le temps de réactualiser votre CV et votre lettre de motivation.  &lt;br /&gt;2. Anticipez  &lt;br /&gt;Les nouveaux contrats démarrent généralement en septembre mais le processus commence souvent à la fin de l’été. Donc n’attendez pas !  &lt;br /&gt;3. Faites une veille d’emplois  &lt;br /&gt;Suivez les dernières offres d’emplois et le traitement de vos candidatures sur internet.  &lt;br /&gt;4. Multipliez les candidatures spontanées  &lt;br /&gt;Par manque de temps, on limite souvent les candidatures spontanées. C’est donc le moment !  &lt;br /&gt;Les recruteurs auront davantage le temps de s’y intéresser également !  &lt;br /&gt;5. Restez connecté et joignable  &lt;br /&gt;Ne manquez pas une belle   &lt;br /&gt;opportunité : même si vous êtes en vacances, ayez à porter de main votre téléphone !  &lt;br /&gt;6. Entrez en contact avec les responsables des recrutements  &lt;br /&gt;Ils sont moins sollicités durant cette période et donc plus disponibles !  &lt;br /&gt;Tentez de mettre un pied dans l’entreprise :  Si l’occasion se présente, venez en remplacement des salariés partis en vacances.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">Vous êtes à la recherche d’un emploi mais vous craignez que la période estivale ne soit un frein ? Détrompez-vous ! , Les vacances d’été peuvent être le moment idéal pour décrocher un nouveau travail. Moins de concurrence : , Durant cette période, on constate moins de postulants. Résultat : Cela fait plus de chances pour vous de vous faire remarquer ! 1. Soignez vos candidatures Prenez le temps de réactualiser votre CV et votre lettre de motivation. 2. Anticipez Les nouveaux contrats démarrent généralement en septembre mais le processus commence souvent à la fin de l’été. Donc n’attendez pas ! 3. Faites une veille d’emplois Suivez les dernières offres d’emplois et le traitement de vos candidatures sur internet. 4. Multipliez les candidatures spontanées Par manque de temps, on limite souvent les candidatures spontanées. C’est donc le moment ! Les recruteurs auront davantage le temps de s’y intéresser également ! 5. Restez connecté et joignable Ne manquez pas une belle opportunité : même si vous êtes en vacances, ayez à porter de main votre téléphone ! 6. Entrez en contact avec les responsables des recrutements Ils sont moins sollicités durant cette période et donc plus disponibles ! Tentez de mettre un pied dans l’entreprise : Si l’occasion se présente, venez en remplacement des salariés partis en vacances.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPp361VF_iIMZE4IO/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPp361VF_iIMZE4IO/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">CBI teams question Rhea and other accused, ED probes SSR’s finances</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/cbi-teams-question-rhea-and-other-accused-ed-probes-ssr-s-finances.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CBI teams question Rhea and other accused, ED probes SSR’s finances" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:33:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:33:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/cbi-teams-question-rhea-and-other-accused-ed-probes-ssr-s-finances</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/cbi-teams-question-rhea-and-other-accused-ed-probes-ssr-s-finances.html">&lt;p&gt;Separate teams of the Central Bureau of Investigation are questioning all the accused in the case of Sushant Singh Rajput’s death. These include Rhea Chakraborty, Showik Chakraborty, Keshav Bachner, Dipesh Sawant, Rajat Mewati, Sandeep Shridhar, Samuel Miranda, Neeraj Singh and Siddharth Pithani.    &lt;br /&gt;CBI is also likely to confront Rhea infront of Sushant Singh’s house manager.    &lt;br /&gt;Probing the money laundering angle in the case, the Enforcement Directorate revealed that it has cloned two mobile phones of Rhea Chakraborty and are also probing her digital data.    &lt;br /&gt;Earlier, Rhea Chakraborty has been questioned by the ED twice in a money laundering case related to the death of actor Sushant Singh Rajput but has failed to answer questions asked by the team on her finances. &lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Separate teams of the Central Bureau of Investigation are questioning all the accused in the case of Sushant Singh Rajput’s death. These include Rhea Chakraborty, Showik Chakraborty, Keshav Bachner, Dipesh Sawant, Rajat Mewati, Sandeep Shridhar, Samuel Miranda, Neeraj Singh and Siddharth Pithani.  CBI is also likely to confront Rhea infront of Sushant Singh’s house manager.  Probing the money laundering angle in the case, the Enforcement Directorate revealed that it has cloned two mobile phones of Rhea Chakraborty and are also probing her digital data.  Earlier, Rhea Chakraborty has been questioned by the ED twice in a money laundering case related to the death of actor Sushant Singh Rajput but has failed to answer questions asked by the team on her finances. </summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQa7V1VIHLMuCGeUj/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQa7V1VIHLMuCGeUj/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Ehpad : la crainte d’un reconfinement</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/ehpad-la-crainte-d-un-reconfinement.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ehpad : la crainte d’un reconfinement" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:32:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:32:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/ehpad-la-crainte-d-un-reconfinement</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/ehpad-la-crainte-d-un-reconfinement.html">&lt;p&gt;A l’heure où l’épidémie montre des signes de rebond à travers le pays, certains Ehpad remettent en place des mesures de confinement.   &lt;br /&gt;Les directeurs d’établissements sont appelés à réactiver leurs cellules «Covid» et à stocker du matériel, afin de protéger au mieux leurs 600.000 résidents.  &lt;br /&gt;Les familles de résidents n’adhèrent pas à l’idée d’un reconfinement.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">A l’heure où l’épidémie montre des signes de rebond à travers le pays, certains Ehpad remettent en place des mesures de confinement.  Les directeurs d’établissements sont appelés à réactiver leurs cellules «Covid» et à stocker du matériel, afin de protéger au mieux leurs 600.000 résidents. Les familles de résidents n’adhèrent pas à l’idée d’un reconfinement. </summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQIPT1VHYXA_pxIef/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SQIPT1VHYXA_pxIef/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">典当定情钻戒 大条了！ 单亲妈妈控接受赃物罪</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/x7vrkhp.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="典当定情钻戒 大条了！ 单亲妈妈控接受赃物罪" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:26:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:26:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/x7vrkhp</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/x7vrkhp.html">&lt;p&gt;典当定情钻戒始知属前男友妹妹所有，单亲妈妈今日被控非法接受赃物罪，她否认有罪，允许以4000令吉外加一名担保人保外。  &lt;br /&gt;被告侯女士被指于今年8月8日，在伯乐泰广场宝光珠宝店，持有一枚市值2万2480令吉的Hemera钻戒，该钻戒属原持有人陈盈婷（译音，44岁）报失的赃物。  &lt;br /&gt;侯女士的行为被指牴触刑事法典第411条文（非法接受赃物）；罪成可被判坐牢最高5年、罚款或两者兼施。  &lt;br /&gt;（本报张景扬摄）  &lt;br /&gt;即时新闻每天为您送上  &lt;br /&gt;✌中国报App   &lt;br /&gt;iOS:    &lt;br /&gt;Google Play:   &lt;br /&gt;✌WhatsApp中国报追新闻服务   &lt;br /&gt;✌中国报新闻网：  &lt;br /&gt;✌霹雳人看霹雳事   &lt;br /&gt;✌北马人告诉你北马大小事   &lt;br /&gt;✌东海岸人报你知   &lt;br /&gt;✌看KL人KL事    &lt;br /&gt;✌看柔佛人最新最快   &lt;br /&gt;#今日中国报  &lt;br /&gt;马上按赞追踪  &lt;br /&gt;●中国报面子书：  &lt;br /&gt;●中国报推特：  &lt;br /&gt;●中国报微博：  &lt;br /&gt;●中国报IG：  &lt;br /&gt;●中国报YouTube官方频道：  &lt;br /&gt;●中国报Dailymotion官方频道：&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">典当定情钻戒始知属前男友妹妹所有，单亲妈妈今日被控非法接受赃物罪，她否认有罪，允许以4000令吉外加一名担保人保外。 被告侯女士被指于今年8月8日，在伯乐泰广场宝光珠宝店，持有一枚市值2万2480令吉的Hemera钻戒，该钻戒属原持有人陈盈婷（译音，44岁）报失的赃物。 侯女士的行为被指牴触刑事法典第411条文（非法接受赃物）；罪成可被判坐牢最高5年、罚款或两者兼施。 （本报张景扬摄） 即时新闻每天为您送上 ✌中国报App iOS: Google Play: ✌WhatsApp中国报追新闻服务 ✌中国报新闻网： ✌霹雳人看霹雳事 ✌北马人告诉你北马大小事 ✌东海岸人报你知 ✌看KL人KL事 ✌看柔佛人最新最快 #今日中国报 马上按赞追踪 ●中国报面子书： ●中国报推特： ●中国报微博： ●中国报IG： ●中国报YouTube官方频道： ●中国报Dailymotion官方频道：</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ9jz1VIMXUMis8Go/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQ9jz1VIMXUMis8Go/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown split</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/gerard-butler-and-morgan-brown-split.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown split" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:24:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:24:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/gerard-butler-and-morgan-brown-split</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/gerard-butler-and-morgan-brown-split.html">&lt;p&gt;Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown have split after six years together.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown split&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown split&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown split&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="people" />
  <summary type="html">Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown have split after six years together.Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown split Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown split Gerard Butler and Morgan Brown split</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPc2n1VFUlhVoFrtR/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPc2n1VFUlhVoFrtR/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Ca sent la fin de l’été… Bulletin du samedi 22 août 2020</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/ca-sent-la-fin-de-l-e-te-bulletin-du-samedi-22-aou-t-2020.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ca sent la fin de l’été… Bulletin du samedi 22 août 2020" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:22:06+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:22:06+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/ca-sent-la-fin-de-l-e-te-bulletin-du-samedi-22-aou-t-2020</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/ca-sent-la-fin-de-l-e-te-bulletin-du-samedi-22-aou-t-2020.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ca sent la fin de l’été… Bulletin du samedi 22 août 2020&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;i&gt;Ca sent la fin de l’été… Bulletin du samedi 22 août 2020&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;u&gt;Ca sent la fin de l'été... Bulletin du samedi 22 août 2020&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Ca sent la fin de l’été… Bulletin du samedi 22 août 2020 Ca sent la fin de l’été… Bulletin du samedi 22 août 2020 Ca sent la fin de l'été... Bulletin du samedi 22 août 2020</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPvC11VGKqecFoIWD/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPvC11VGKqecFoIWD/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">How to Engage Time-Crunched Audiences</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/how-to-engage-time-crunched-audiences.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Engage Time-Crunched Audiences" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:18:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:18:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/how-to-engage-time-crunched-audiences</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/how-to-engage-time-crunched-audiences.html">&lt;p&gt;The founder of a social platform focused on making meal and snacks for toddlers talks about how she built an online community.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="lifestyle" />
  <summary type="html">The founder of a social platform focused on making meal and snacks for toddlers talks about how she built an online community.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPhZ41VGCMAVApIgr/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SPhZ41VGCMAVApIgr/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Schneiderlin : «Un match spécial pour moi» - Foot - L1 - Nice</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/schneiderlin-un-match-sp-cial-pour-moi-foot-l1-nice.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Schneiderlin : «Un match spécial pour moi» - Foot - L1 - Nice" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:17:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:17:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/schneiderlin-un-match-sp-cial-pour-moi-foot-l1-nice</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/schneiderlin-un-match-sp-cial-pour-moi-foot-l1-nice.html">&lt;p&gt;VIDÉO FOOT - Le nouveau milieu de terrain de l’OGC Nice, Morgan Schneiderlin, a évoqué en conférence de presse son retour sur la pelouse de Strasbourg (samedi, 21h), son club formateur.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="sport" />
  <summary type="html">VIDÉO FOOT - Le nouveau milieu de terrain de l’OGC Nice, Morgan Schneiderlin, a évoqué en conférence de presse son retour sur la pelouse de Strasbourg (samedi, 21h), son club formateur.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQSlV1VICRB0h-TaV/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQSlV1VICRB0h-TaV/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Anne Souyris, adjointe à la mairie de Paris en charge de la santé, sur le port du masque obligatoire dans la capitale : «Il est interdit de fumer dans la rue, il est interdit d’enlever le masque» #LaMatinale</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/anne-souyris-adjointe-la-mairie-de-paris-en-charge-de-la-sant-sur-le-p.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Anne Souyris, adjointe à la mairie de Paris en charge de la santé, sur le port du masque obligatoire dans la capitale : «Il est interdit de fumer dans la rue, il est interdit d’enlever le masque» #LaMatinale" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:17:03+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:17:03+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/anne-souyris-adjointe-la-mairie-de-paris-en-charge-de-la-sant-sur-le-p</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/anne-souyris-adjointe-la-mairie-de-paris-en-charge-de-la-sant-sur-le-p.html">&lt;p&gt;Anne Souyris, adjointe à la mairie de Paris en charge de la santé, sur le port du masque obligatoire dans la capitale : «Il est interdit de fumer dans la rue, il est interdit d’enlever le masque» #LaMatinale&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Anne Souyris, adjointe à la mairie de Paris en charge de la santé, sur le port du masque obligatoire dans la capitale : «Il est interdit de fumer dans la rue, il est interdit d’enlever le masque» #LaMatinale</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQYlx1VIFx_xP3HdE/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s1.dmcdn.net/v/SQYlx1VIFx_xP3HdE/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 <entry>
  <title type="html">Didier Raoult : « Comment expliquer cette guerre complètement folle contre l’hydroxychloroquine ? »</title>
  <link href="https://adowsom.github.io/didier-raoult-comment-expliquer-cette-guerre-compl-tement-folle-contre.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Didier Raoult : « Comment expliquer cette guerre complètement folle contre l’hydroxychloroquine ? »" />
  <published>2020-08-28T23:16:05+03:00</published>
  <updated>2020-08-28T23:16:05+03:00</updated>
  <id>https://adowsom.github.io/didier-raoult-comment-expliquer-cette-guerre-compl-tement-folle-contre</id>
  <content type="html" xml:base="https://adowsom.github.io/didier-raoult-comment-expliquer-cette-guerre-compl-tement-folle-contre.html">&lt;p&gt;Le Professeur Didier Raoult était interviewé par Laurence Ferrari ce mercredi matin. Il a répondu à toutes les questions concernant le coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <author>
   <name>Eyygelena Fteras</name>
   <uri>https://adowsom.github.io</uri>
   <email>eygimokress@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <category term="news" />
  <summary type="html">Le Professeur Didier Raoult était interviewé par Laurence Ferrari ce mercredi matin. Il a répondu à toutes les questions concernant le coronavirus.</summary>
  <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPWlJ1VFMaY5ciaGC/x240" />
  <media:content medium="image" url="https://s2.dmcdn.net/v/SPWlJ1VFMaY5ciaGC/x240" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" />
 </entry>
 </feed>